{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/lauslim12-old/ignite-grocerycrud/blob/4743154d8e8b325b51486b93538db8ebc1ea30af/assets/sql/sql-db.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "Pembeli": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Customer": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "C0001",
            "C0002",
            "C0003",
            "C0004",
            "C0005",
            "C0006",
            "C0007",
            "C0008",
            "C0009",
            "C0010",
            "C0011",
            "C0012",
            "C0013",
            "C0014",
            "C0015",
            "C0016",
            "C0017",
            "C0018",
            "C0019",
            "C0020",
            "C0021",
            "C0022",
            "C0023",
            "C0024",
            "C0025",
            "C0026",
            "C0027",
            "C0028",
            "C0029",
            "C0030",
            "C0031",
            "C0032",
            "C0033",
            "C0034",
            "C0035",
            "C0036",
            "C0037",
            "C0038",
            "C0039",
            "C0040",
            "C0041",
            "C0042",
            "C0043",
            "C0044",
            "C0045",
            "C0046",
            "C0047",
            "C0048",
            "C0049",
            "C0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaDepan": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Gery",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Irvan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ahmad",
            "Ilham",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Puja",
            "Robi",
            "Aga",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Asep",
            "Dendi",
            "Fahmi",
            "Indri",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Anna",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Niki",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Akino",
            "Rizal",
            "Ivy",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dimas",
            "Alfan",
            "Arie",
            "Kevin",
            "Boy",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ary",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Surya",
            "Yusuf",
            "Galih",
            "Rere",
            "Adela",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaBelakang": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Duto",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Raul",
            "Ahmad",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Oswin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "",
            "Mulia",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Agung",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kevin",
            "",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Macria",
            "Rozi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Putra",
            "Trian",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ardi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Octaviana",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Prima",
            "Hero"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "BirthDate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2000-09-03",
            "2000-06-04",
            "2000-01-10",
            "2000-05-10",
            "1988-05-20",
            "1994-08-12",
            "1996-03-30",
            "1998-07-17",
            "1997-09-12",
            "1997-11-18",
            "1993-10-23",
            "1995-09-29",
            "1995-04-12",
            "1987-05-04",
            "1999-03-08",
            "1997-03-16",
            "2001-07-15",
            "2000-05-14",
            "1992-01-13",
            "1995-12-12",
            "1996-10-04",
            "1998-03-08",
            "1998-02-25",
            "2000-06-29",
            "1994-08-27",
            "1994-09-24",
            "1994-03-23",
            "1990-09-13",
            "1997-12-18",
            "1997-10-16",
            "1982-09-15",
            "1985-04-25",
            "1997-03-17",
            "1993-02-14",
            "1990-02-08",
            "1989-11-21",
            "1978-11-20",
            "1977-09-25",
            "1990-07-30",
            "1980-05-25",
            "1982-04-24",
            "2002-07-07",
            "1975-09-09",
            "1978-02-03",
            "1974-11-30",
            "1996-10-23",
            "1992-07-26",
            "2000-03-23",
            "2001-02-27",
            "1995-12-01"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Alamat": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cokokol",
            "Pluit",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Grogol",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Braga",
            "Cibadak",
            "Cibaduyut",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sadu",
            "Dago",
            "Ciputat",
            "Gading Serpong",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sepatan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Radio Dalam",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Joglo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Braga",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sepatan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Joglo",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pluit",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Grogol",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Radio Dalam",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gading Serpong",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ZipCode": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "12220",
            "14440",
            "15550",
            "15552",
            "16600",
            "16600",
            "36601",
            "36602",
            "16603",
            "16605",
            "16605",
            "47771",
            "17772",
            "47773",
            "17774",
            "17775",
            "18880",
            "68881",
            "68882",
            "18883",
            "18884",
            "18885",
            "38886",
            "28887",
            "19990",
            "19991",
            "59992",
            "59993",
            "19994",
            "19995",
            "19996",
            "99997",
            "79998",
            "15551",
            "65552",
            "15553",
            "15554",
            "45556",
            "15555",
            "41110",
            "11111",
            "71112",
            "81113",
            "11114",
            "21115",
            "31116",
            "11117",
            "20003",
            "20005",
            "20006"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Kota": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Tangerang",
            "Tangerang",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Utara",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "Jakarta Pusat",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Tangerang",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tangerang",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Pusat",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Utara",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "Tangerang",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Pekerjaan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Anak Motor",
            "CEO",
            "<PERSON>",
            "CTO",
            "Manager",
            "Customer Service",
            "Mobile Developer",
            "Web Developer",
            "Cloud Computing",
            "Database Administrator",
            "Software Enginner",
            "Desktop Developer",
            "Data Scientist",
            "Data Engineer",
            "IT Support",
            "Game Developer",
            "Game Designer",
            "Security Engineer",
            "System Analyst",
            "UI/UX Designer",
            "Hadware Enginner",
            "Network Enginner",
            "System Support",
            "Software Enginner",
            "Mobile Developer",
            "Mobile Developer",
            "Data Scientist",
            "IT Support",
            "Database Administrator",
            "UI/UX Designer",
            "Web Designer",
            "Game Designer",
            "Customer Service",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Desktop Developer",
            "Mobile Developer",
            "Android Developer",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Web Designer",
            "Network Enginner",
            "IT Support",
            "Mobile Developer",
            "Data Enginner",
            "Cloud Computing",
            "Game Developer",
            "UI/UX Designer",
            "System Analyst",
            "Database Administrator",
            "System Support",
            "Mobile Developer"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Customer"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "PhonePembeli": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Customer": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "C0001",
            "C0002",
            "C0003",
            "C0004",
            "C0005",
            "C0006",
            "C0007",
            "C0008",
            "C0009",
            "C0010",
            "C0011",
            "C0012",
            "C0013",
            "C0014",
            "C0015",
            "C0016",
            "C0017",
            "C0018",
            "C0019",
            "C0020",
            "C0021",
            "C0022",
            "C0023",
            "C0024",
            "C0025",
            "C0026",
            "C0027",
            "C0028",
            "C0029",
            "C0030",
            "C0031",
            "C0032",
            "C0033",
            "C0034",
            "C0035",
            "C0036",
            "C0037",
            "C0038",
            "C0039",
            "C0040",
            "C0041",
            "C0042",
            "C0043",
            "C0044",
            "C0045",
            "C0046",
            "C0047",
            "C0048",
            "C0049",
            "C0050",
            "C0001",
            "C0002",
            "C0003",
            "C0004",
            "C0007",
            "C0008",
            "C0011",
            "C0014",
            "C0016",
            "C0019",
            "C0020",
            "C0022",
            "C0023",
            "C0024",
            "C0027",
            "C0029",
            "C0031",
            "C0033",
            "C0035",
            "C0036",
            "C0037",
            "C0039",
            "C0044",
            "C0047",
            "C0048",
            "C0050",
            "C0001",
            "C0002",
            "C0003",
            "C0004",
            "C0007",
            "C0008",
            "C0011",
            "C0014",
            "C0016",
            "C0019",
            "C0020",
            "C0022",
            "C0023",
            "C0024",
            "C0027",
            "C0029",
            "C0031",
            "C0033",
            "C0035",
            "C0036",
            "C0037",
            "C0039",
            "C0044",
            "C0047",
            "C0048",
            "C0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NoTelp": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "099834874832",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "097834034129",
            "008934272304",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "012390876511",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "012483247823",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "001818181823",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "088837317123",
            "097802783921",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "009213498763",
            "009078659831",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "013873412781",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "012345812432",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "008934732927",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "088829123892",
            "012881881230",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "123789823825",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "013484992225",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "031298923489",
            "008349989123",
            "012345992432",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "008234932927",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "012348992312",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "003247996421",
            "088829923892",
            "012881981230",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "123789923825",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "013484192225",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "031298493489",
            "008349399123"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "NoTelp"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Customer"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Pembeli",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Customer"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "Cascade",
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Job": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "JobID": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "J0001",
            "J0002",
            "J0003",
            "J0004",
            "J0005",
            "J0006",
            "J0007",
            "J0008",
            "J0009",
            "J0010"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "JobDesc": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Manager",
            "Sales",
            "Mekanik",
            "Resepsionis",
            "Intern",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Office Boy",
            "Operasional",
            "Security"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Salary": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "50000000",
            "7500000",
            "4000000",
            "4500000",
            "3500000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "50000000",
            "1500000",
            "2500000",
            "2000000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "JobID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Bengkel": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Bengkel": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "B0001",
            "B0002",
            "B0003",
            "B0004",
            "B0005",
            "B0006",
            "B0007",
            "B0008",
            "B0009",
            "B0010"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Jasa": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bengkel Body Mobil",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "HargaJasa": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "500000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "750000",
            "1500000",
            "3500000",
            "550000",
            "5500000",
            "7500000",
            "10000000",
            "250000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Bengkel"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Sparepart": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Sparepart": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "S0001",
            "S0002",
            "S0003",
            "S0004",
            "S0005",
            "S0006",
            "S0007",
            "S0008",
            "S0009",
            "S0010",
            "S0011",
            "S0012",
            "S0013",
            "S0014",
            "S0015",
            "S0016",
            "S0017",
            "S0018",
            "S0019",
            "S0020",
            "S0021",
            "S0022",
            "S0023",
            "S0024",
            "S0025"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Harga": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "250000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "250000",
            "100000",
            "125000",
            "400000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "2205000",
            "13000000",
            "16000000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "5800000",
            "3700000",
            "840000",
            "6500000",
            "27000000",
            "23700000",
            "35000",
            "75000",
            "90000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "500000",
            "250000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "MerekSP": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Brembo",
            "K-Sports",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "HKS",
            "Fujitsubo",
            "Cadillac",
            "BMW",
            "Cadillac",
            "Toyota",
            "Shell",
            "Fastron",
            "BSS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "J-Fit",
            "Unichip",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Varis",
            "M3",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Premium",
            "Autosculpting",
            "Bridgestone",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "DescSP": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "R-17 Sport",
            "Spooring",
            "Balancing",
            "Knalpot Racing",
            "Knalpot S Racing",
            "Spoiler Wing",
            "Car Tail",
            "Twin Turbo V8",
            "V8 Toyota",
            "Helix Ultra",
            "10W-40",
            "Vleg BSS R-17",
            "Vleg 3Volk Ray ce28 R-15",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dastek Q+",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Engine Flush",
            "Fabrication",
            "R-21 Racing",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Qty": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "50",
            "25",
            "5",
            "1",
            "1",
            "5",
            "2",
            "2",
            "4",
            "2",
            "2",
            "10",
            "10",
            "10",
            "5",
            "5",
            "10",
            "5",
            "5",
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "10",
            "1"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ID_Bengkel": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "B0001",
            "B0001",
            "B0002",
            "B0002",
            "B0002",
            "B0003",
            "B0003",
            "B0004",
            "B0004",
            "B0005",
            "B0005",
            "B0006",
            "B0006",
            "B0007",
            "B0007",
            "B0008",
            "B0008",
            "B0009",
            "B0009",
            "B0010",
            "B0010",
            "B0005",
            "B0009",
            "B0002",
            "B0008"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Sparepart"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Bengkel"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Bengkel",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Bengkel"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Mobil": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "SerialNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "M0001",
            "M0002",
            "M0003",
            "M0004",
            "M0005",
            "M0006",
            "M0007",
            "M0008",
            "M0009",
            "M0010",
            "M0011",
            "M0012",
            "M0013",
            "M0014",
            "M0015",
            "M0016",
            "M0017",
            "M0018",
            "M0019",
            "M0020",
            "M0021",
            "M0022",
            "M0023",
            "M0024",
            "M0025",
            "M0026",
            "M0027",
            "M0028",
            "M0029",
            "M0030",
            "M0031",
            "M0032",
            "M0033",
            "M0034",
            "M0035",
            "M0036",
            "M0037",
            "M0038",
            "M0039",
            "M0040",
            "M0041",
            "M0042",
            "M0043",
            "M0044",
            "M0045",
            "M0046",
            "M0047",
            "M0048",
            "M0049",
            "M0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Merek": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Ferrari",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Volvo",
            "Ferrari",
            "Suzuki",
            "Mazda",
            "Dodge",
            "Honda",
            "Toyota",
            "Lincoln",
            "Lexus",
            "Nissan",
            "Chevrolet",
            "Minicooper",
            "Mustang",
            "Chevrolete",
            "Plymouth",
            "Dodge",
            "Honda",
            "Astonmartin",
            "Audi",
            "BMW",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chevrolet",
            "Ferrari",
            "Pontiac",
            "Ford",
            "Honda",
            "Honda",
            "Mitsubishi",
            "Nissan",
            "Nissan",
            "Jaguar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lotus",
            "McLaren",
            "Mercedes-Benz",
            "Mercedes-Benz",
            "Morgan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Porsche",
            "Toyota",
            "Toyota",
            "TVR",
            "JEEP",
            "LandRover",
            "Maserati",
            "Rolls-Royce",
            "Subaru",
            "BMW"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaMobil": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Murcielago LP640",
            "XC90",
            "488",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Rx-8",
            "Viper",
            "New Acura NSX",
            "Trueno GT Apex",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LFA",
            "370z Fairlady",
            "Camaro SS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ford Mustang Boss 302",
            "Chevrolet Chevelle SS 454",
            "Plymouth Hemi Cuda",
            "Dodge Charger R/T-SE",
            "NXS",
            "DB10",
            "R8",
            "M4",
            "Bugatti Veryon EB 16.4",
            "Corvette Z06",
            "225 S",
            "Firebird 400 Coupe",
            "GT40",
            "CR-X",
            "S2000",
            "Lancer Evo 9",
            "Silvia S15",
            "GTR R35",
            "F-type",
            "CCX",
            "Exige",
            "12C",
            "CLK",
            "SLR McLaren",
            "Plus4",
            "Zonda",
            "991",
            "2000GT",
            "MR-S",
            "Tuscan",
            "F-Pace SVR",
            "Range Rover Sport",
            "Levante",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Foresta",
            "i8"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Model": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Supercar",
            "Supercar",
            "SUV",
            "Supercar",
            "Hatchback",
            "Sportcar",
            "Supercar",
            "Supercar",
            "Hatchback",
            "Sedan Coupe",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Citycar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Coupe",
            "Coupe",
            "Supercar",
            "Executivecar",
            "Supersport",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sedan",
            "Sedan",
            "Supercar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Supercar",
            "Classiccar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "Sportcar",
            "SUV",
            "SUV",
            "SUV",
            "SUV",
            "SUV",
            "Sportcar"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "TahunPembuatan": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2012",
            "2010",
            "2020",
            "2015",
            "2019",
            "2003",
            "1992",
            "2020",
            "1972",
            "1969",
            "2008",
            "2011",
            "2009",
            "1963",
            "1970",
            "1970",
            "1971",
            "1969",
            "1990",
            "2015",
            "2019",
            "2014",
            "2019",
            "2000",
            "1952",
            "1969",
            "2004",
            "1991",
            "2009",
            "2002",
            "1999",
            "2007",
            "2013",
            "2006",
            "2000",
            "2011",
            "1997",
            "2003",
            "1969",
            "1997",
            "1963",
            "1967",
            "1999",
            "1967",
            "2018",
            "2005",
            2017,
            "2018",
            "2013",
            "2017"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "HargaJual": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "5000000000",
            "3500000000",
            "1300000000",
            "15000000000",
            "<AU_TFN>",
            "840000000",
            "1000000000",
            "2500000000",
            "1300000000",
            "1000000000",
            "5250000000",
            "925000000",
            "994000000",
            "318668000",
            "2000000000",
            "750000000",
            "18200000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2200000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2700000000",
            "2000000000",
            "33000000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "511000000",
            "25200000000",
            "92400000",
            "497000000",
            "531930000",
            "170410850",
            "1399860000",
            "3000000000",
            "64700000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "514360000",
            "20300000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "19600000000",
            "1582000000",
            "16240000000",
            "<AU_TFN>",
            "697500000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Qty": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "1",
            "5",
            "5",
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "5",
            "1",
            "3",
            "2",
            "1",
            "4",
            "3",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "2",
            "2",
            "5",
            "1",
            "2",
            "1",
            "2",
            "2",
            "5",
            "3",
            "2",
            "4",
            "3",
            "2",
            "4",
            "3",
            "2",
            "2",
            "3",
            "2",
            "3",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "3",
            "2",
            "4",
            "5"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "SerialNumber"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "WarnaMobil": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "SerialNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "M0001",
            "M0002",
            "M0003",
            "M0004",
            "M0005",
            "M0006",
            "M0007",
            "M0008",
            "M0009",
            "M0010",
            "M0011",
            "M0012",
            "M0013",
            "M0013",
            "M0014",
            "M0015",
            "M0016",
            "M0017",
            "M0018",
            "M0019",
            "M0019",
            "M0019",
            "M0020",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0022",
            "M0023",
            "M0024",
            "M0024",
            "M0025",
            "M0026",
            "M0027",
            "M0028",
            "M0029",
            "M0030",
            "M0030",
            "M0031",
            "M0032",
            "M0032",
            "M0033",
            "M0034",
            "M0035",
            "M0036",
            "M0037",
            "M0038",
            "M0039",
            "M0040",
            "M0040",
            "M0041",
            "M0042",
            "M0043",
            "M0044",
            "M0044",
            "M0045",
            "M0046",
            "M0047",
            "M0048",
            "M0049",
            "M0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "WarnaMobil": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Fire Red",
            "Lambo Orange",
            "Beige",
            "Fire Red",
            "Metallic Premium Silver",
            "Metallic Black",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Electric Orange",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Black",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lime Green",
            "Dusk Red",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Coupe Blue",
            "Le Mans Quattro",
            "<PERSON>",
            "BMW Blue",
            "Electric Blue",
            "Corvette Yellow",
            "Azure",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Silver-Black Stripes",
            "Solid Red",
            "S200 Yellow",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Electric Green",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Premium Silver",
            "Darkness Returns",
            "Soft Yellow",
            "Metallic Purple",
            "Mercedes Silver",
            "Mercedes Silver",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pagani Silver",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Black",
            "Silver",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Metallic Silver",
            "Metallic Red",
            "Premium Black",
            "<PERSON>",
            "i8 Signature"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "SerialNumber",
        "WarnaMobil"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Mobil",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "Cascade",
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Modifikasi": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "SerialNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "M0001",
            "M0002",
            "M0009",
            "M0011",
            "M0013",
            "M0014",
            "M0019",
            "M0020",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0021",
            "M0023",
            "M0023",
            "M0023",
            "M0024",
            "M0025",
            "M0026",
            "M0027",
            "M0027",
            "M0027",
            "M0027",
            "M0027",
            "M0027",
            "M0030",
            "M0030",
            "M0031",
            "M0031",
            "M0031",
            "M0031",
            "M0032",
            "M0050",
            "M0050",
            "M0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "TipeModif": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Bodykit",
            "Exhaust",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Interior",
            "Full Modification",
            "Interior",
            "Bodykit",
            "Glass",
            "Exhaust",
            "Bodykit",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Interior",
            "Wheels",
            "Engine",
            "Doors",
            "Lights",
            "Wheels",
            "Body",
            "Interior",
            "Wheels",
            "Wheels",
            "Engine",
            "Engine",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Wheels",
            "Doors",
            "Engine",
            "Lights",
            "Engine",
            "Wheels",
            "Wheels",
            "Engine",
            "Engine",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Engine",
            "Battery",
            "Engine",
            "Engine"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "HargaModif": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "10000000",
            "2500000",
            "5000000",
            "10000000",
            "25000000",
            "100000",
            "10000000",
            "3500000",
            "15000000",
            "20000000",
            "5000000",
            "2500000",
            "10000000",
            "50000000",
            "10000000",
            "5000000",
            "50000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000",
            "10000000",
            "25000000",
            "10000000",
            "10000000",
            "10000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000",
            "10000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000",
            "15000000",
            "10000000",
            "15000000",
            "25000000",
            "5000000",
            "5000000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "DescModif": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Sport Bodykit",
            "Magnaflow Performance Exhaust",
            "Initial D Paintjob",
            "Luxury Seats",
            "Optimus Prime",
            "Leather Dashboard",
            "Sport Bodykit",
            "Tempered Film Glass 80%",
            "Stacked Deck Exhaust",
            "Stacked Deck Body",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Racing Rollbars",
            "Atomic Wheels",
            "Stacked Deck Engine",
            "Automatic Theft Detector",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Special Bugatti Wheels",
            "Parachute",
            "Automatic Cosinetta",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bridgestone",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Stacked Deck Engine (Ford GT Special)",
            "<PERSON>",
            "GT Radial Sport",
            "Automatic Theft Detector",
            "Nitrous Oxide (N20)",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Drift Engines",
            "Drift Wheels",
            "Drift Wheels",
            "Nitrous Oxide (N20)",
            "Magnaflow Performance Drift",
            "Drift Vinyls",
            "Supercharged",
            "Rechargeable Battery",
            "Nitrous Oxide Electric",
            "Engine Overhaul"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "SerialNumber",
        "DescModif"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Mobil",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "Cascade",
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Perusahaan": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Perusahaan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "P0001",
            "P0002",
            "P0003",
            "P0004",
            "P0005",
            "P0006",
            "P0007",
            "P0008",
            "P0009",
            "P0010"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaPerusahaan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Prestige Image Motorsports",
            "PT. Astra Auto 2000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "PT. Toyota",
            "PT. BMW Corporad",
            "PT. Oplet Company",
            "<PERSON>",
            "PT. Mobil Anak Lippo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Kota": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Pusat",
            "Tangerang",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "Bali",
            "Tangerang",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Jakarta Pusat"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Alamat": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Lebak Bulus",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gading Serpong",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cilandak",
            "Joglo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ZipCode": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "12440",
            "15550",
            "14440",
            "14045",
            "15440",
            "12260",
            "17941",
            "16660",
            "17111",
            "13330"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NoTelp": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ID_Pusat": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ID_Bengkel": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "B0001",
            "B0002",
            "B0004",
            "B0003",
            "B0005",
            "B0009",
            "B0007",
            "B0010",
            "B0006",
            "B0008"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Perusahaan"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Pusat"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Perusahaan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Perusahaan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Bengkel"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Bengkel",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Bengkel"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "PenyediaanMobil": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Perusahaan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0003",
            "P0003",
            "P0003",
            "P0004",
            "P0004",
            "P0004",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0006",
            "P0006",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0008",
            "P0008",
            "P0009",
            "P0010",
            "P0010"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "SerialNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "M0007",
            "M0001",
            "M0004",
            "M0008",
            "M0021",
            "M0023",
            "M0025",
            "M0017",
            "M0021",
            "M0020",
            "M0014",
            "M0003",
            "M0002",
            "M0006",
            "M0009",
            "M0010",
            "M0011",
            "M0012",
            "M0018",
            "M0024",
            "M0037",
            "M0026",
            "M0030",
            "M0049",
            "M0050",
            "M0047",
            "M0036",
            "M0035",
            "M0039",
            "M0027",
            "M0034",
            "M0032"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ProsesDate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-10-22",
            "2019-12-10",
            "2019-10-01",
            "2019-04-01",
            "2019-04-07",
            "2019-03-07",
            "2019-05-02",
            "2019-02-02",
            "2019-04-01",
            "2019-01-01",
            "2019-02-02",
            "2019-03-20",
            "2019-01-02",
            "2019-03-04",
            "2019-04-07",
            "2019-04-07",
            "2019-04-07",
            "2019-02-02",
            "2019-01-04",
            "2019-03-04",
            "2019-01-01",
            "2019-05-05",
            "2019-05-01",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-01-02",
            "2019-03-10",
            "2019-07-07",
            "2019-09-10",
            "2019-10-10",
            "2019-11-20",
            "2019-11-10",
            "2019-10-10"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "TotalHarga": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1000000000",
            "5000000000",
            "15000000000",
            "2500000000",
            "2700000000",
            "33000000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "18200000000",
            "2700000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "318668000",
            "1300000000",
            "3500000000",
            "840000000",
            "1300000000",
            "1000000000",
            "5250000000",
            "925000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "514360000",
            "511000000",
            "531930000",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "25200000000",
            "64700000000",
            "1399860000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Perusahaan",
        "SerialNumber"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Perusahaan"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Perusahaan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Perusahaan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Mobil",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Karyawan": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Karyawan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "K0001",
            "K0002",
            "K0003",
            "K0004",
            "K0005",
            "K0006",
            "K0007",
            "K0008",
            "K0009",
            "K0010",
            "K0011",
            "K0012",
            "K0013",
            "K0014",
            "K0015",
            "K0016",
            "K0017",
            "K0018",
            "K0019",
            "K0020",
            "K0021",
            "K0022",
            "K0023",
            "K0024",
            "K0025",
            "K0026",
            "K0027",
            "K0028",
            "K0029",
            "K0030",
            "K0031",
            "K0032",
            "K0033",
            "K0034",
            "K0035",
            "K0036",
            "K0037",
            "K0038",
            "K0039",
            "K0040",
            "K0041",
            "K0042",
            "K0043",
            "K0044",
            "K0045",
            "K0046",
            "K0047",
            "K0048",
            "K0049",
            "K0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaDepan": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Fadla",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Raul",
            "Gery",
            "Juan",
            "Andi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gusti",
            "Rido",
            "Deka",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Attar",
            "Dinda",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Hananto",
            "Zipora",
            "Bambang",
            "Alan",
            "Susi",
            "Yudi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ariel",
            "Hokky",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Maria",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ian",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chaca",
            "Dinka",
            "Ethan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Hanif",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Karin",
            "Simon",
            "Venno",
            "Theo",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaBelakang": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Akmal",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "Arya",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Fatu",
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ayu",
            null,
            "Dewi",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "Elsa",
            null,
            "Ezra",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bambang",
            "Ozawa",
            "Fanny",
            null,
            "Ketut",
            "Kulo",
            "Vidal",
            "Steel",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            "Suhartanto",
            "Aldo",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Klopp",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Putra",
            "Kipli",
            "Rheza",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Kota": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Tangerang",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Pusat",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Tangerang",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "Jakarta Utara",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Utara",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Timur",
            "Bali",
            "Bali",
            "Bali",
            "Bali",
            "Bali",
            "Tangerang",
            "Tangerang",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "Jakarta Barat",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Jakarta Pusat",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Tangerang",
            "Jakarta Selatan",
            "Jakarta Selatan"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ZipCode": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "12440",
            "12240",
            "13550",
            "13450",
            "12240",
            "11240",
            "10510",
            "12420",
            "11650",
            "11240",
            "12520",
            "14230",
            "14620",
            "14310",
            "14320",
            "40266",
            "40267",
            "40867",
            "40286",
            "40257",
            "11650",
            "12650",
            "12670",
            "13650",
            "13390",
            "11510",
            "12888",
            "12898",
            "11460",
            "19088",
            "14588",
            "14798",
            "14738",
            "13598",
            "10098",
            "15800",
            "13377",
            "15899",
            "16700",
            "16800",
            "14221",
            "15621",
            "19821",
            "13781",
            "19021",
            "19832",
            "15500",
            "15980",
            "17903",
            "15500"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Alamat": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "BSD Cisauk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Joglo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Radio Dalam",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sepatan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gading Serpong",
            "Ciputat",
            "Dago",
            "Cidadap",
            "Cibaduyut",
            "Cibadak",
            "Braga",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Grogol",
            "PIK",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pluit",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Cikokol",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tabanan",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Kulon Progo",
            "Gunungkidul",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pancoran",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "JobID": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "J0001",
            "J0002",
            "J0007",
            "J0007",
            "J0007",
            "J0002",
            "J0009",
            "J0005",
            "J0010",
            "J0003",
            "J0002",
            "J0003",
            "J0003",
            "J0006",
            "J0010",
            "J0002",
            "J0005",
            "J0003",
            "J0003",
            "J0010",
            "J0002",
            "J0003",
            "J0004",
            "J0009",
            "J0010",
            "J0002",
            "J0005",
            "J0006",
            "J0003",
            "J0010",
            "J0002",
            "J0003",
            "J0004",
            "J0006",
            "J0004",
            "J0002",
            "J0006",
            "J0005",
            "J0009",
            "J0004",
            "J0002",
            "J0003",
            "J0009",
            "J0005",
            "J0006",
            "J0002",
            "J0004",
            "J0003",
            "J0006",
            "J0009"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ID_Manager": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "K0006",
            "K0006",
            "K0006",
            "K0006",
            null,
            "K0011",
            "K0011",
            "K0011",
            "K0011",
            null,
            "K0016",
            "K0016",
            "K0016",
            "K0016",
            null,
            "K0021",
            "K0021",
            "K0021",
            "K0021",
            null,
            "K0026",
            "K0026",
            "K0026",
            "K0026",
            null,
            "K0031",
            "K0031",
            "K0031",
            "K0031",
            null,
            "K0036",
            "K0036",
            "K0036",
            "K0036",
            null,
            "K0041",
            "K0041",
            "K0041",
            "K0041",
            null,
            "K0046",
            "K0046",
            "K0046",
            "K0046"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ID_Perusahaan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0001",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0002",
            "P0003",
            "P0003",
            "P0003",
            "P0003",
            "P0003",
            "P0004",
            "P0004",
            "P0004",
            "P0004",
            "P0004",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0005",
            "P0006",
            "P0006",
            "P0006",
            "P0006",
            "P0006",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0007",
            "P0008",
            "P0008",
            "P0008",
            "P0008",
            "P0008",
            "P0009",
            "P0009",
            "P0009",
            "P0009",
            "P0009",
            "P0010",
            "P0010",
            "P0010",
            "P0010",
            "P0010"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Karyawan"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "JobID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Job",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "JobID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Manager"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Karyawan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Perusahaan"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Perusahaan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Perusahaan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "OrderMobil": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Customer": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "C0001",
            "C0002",
            "C0003",
            "C0004",
            "C0005",
            "C0006",
            "C0007",
            "C0008",
            "C0009",
            "C0010",
            "C0011",
            "C0012",
            "C0013",
            "C0014",
            "C0015",
            "C0016",
            "C0017",
            "C0018",
            "C0019",
            "C0020",
            "C0021",
            "C0022",
            "C0023",
            "C0024",
            "C0025",
            "C0026",
            "C0027",
            "C0028",
            "C0029",
            "C0030",
            "C0031",
            "C0032",
            "C0033",
            "C0034",
            "C0035",
            "C0036",
            "C0037",
            "C0038",
            "C0039",
            "C0040",
            "C0041",
            "C0042",
            "C0043",
            "C0044",
            "C0045",
            "C0046",
            "C0047",
            "C0048",
            "C0049",
            "C0050",
            "C0010",
            "C0031",
            "C0015",
            "C0037",
            "C0039",
            "C0018",
            "C0033",
            "C0025",
            "C0029",
            "C0047",
            "C0045"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ID_Karyawan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "K0005",
            "K0002",
            "K0004",
            "K0008",
            "K0001",
            "K0006",
            "K0009",
            "K0003",
            "K0007",
            "K0015",
            "K0013",
            "K0020",
            "K0014",
            "K0016",
            "K0026",
            "K0027",
            "K0024",
            "K0038",
            "K0010",
            "K0012",
            "K0018",
            "K0011",
            "K0032",
            "K0018",
            "K0017",
            "K0019",
            "K0014",
            "K0021",
            "K0047",
            "K0022",
            "K0043",
            "K0025",
            "K0023",
            "K0048",
            "K0042",
            "K0028",
            "K0044",
            "K0050",
            "K0049",
            "K0041",
            "K0029",
            "K0040",
            "K0033",
            "K0034",
            "K0037",
            "K0035",
            "K0039",
            "K0045",
            "K0046",
            "K0036",
            "K0015",
            "K0019",
            "K0032",
            "K0027",
            "K0044",
            "K0039",
            "K0026",
            "K0018",
            "K0021",
            "K0020",
            "K0006"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "OrderDate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-10-12",
            "2019-04-26",
            "2019-06-17",
            "2019-03-10",
            "2019-05-09",
            "2019-03-06",
            "2019-02-22",
            "2019-04-24",
            "2019-05-15",
            "2019-06-19",
            "2019-05-22",
            "2019-08-24",
            "2019-06-23",
            "2019-06-08",
            "2019-03-01",
            "2019-07-15",
            "2019-02-03",
            "2019-10-04",
            "2019-01-26",
            "2019-02-23",
            "2019-02-22",
            "2019-09-25",
            "2019-05-18",
            "2019-03-21",
            "2019-08-12",
            "2019-02-11",
            "2019-07-07",
            "2019-07-05",
            "2019-05-07",
            "2019-07-19",
            "2019-02-28",
            "2019-10-13",
            "2019-01-03",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-02-22",
            "2019-09-01",
            "2019-05-06",
            "2019-03-13",
            "2019-08-18",
            "2019-02-19",
            "2019-07-13",
            "2019-07-05",
            "2019-02-26",
            "2019-09-05",
            "2019-05-20",
            "2019-03-21",
            "2019-08-17",
            "2019-02-19",
            "2019-07-13",
            "2019-07-05",
            "2019-02-19",
            "2019-07-13",
            "2019-07-17",
            "2019-02-26",
            "2019-09-07",
            "2019-05-30",
            "2019-03-11",
            "2019-08-28",
            "2019-02-11",
            "2019-07-13",
            "2019-07-05"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "DownPayment": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "100000000",
            "50000000",
            "750000000",
            "NULL",
            "350000000",
            "500000000",
            "NULL",
            "535000000",
            "753500000",
            "550000000",
            "NULL",
            "<AU_TFN>",
            "500050000",
            "435000000",
            "153400000",
            "555000000",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "NULL",
            "NULL",
            "539600000",
            "NULL",
            "200000000",
            "434500000",
            "100000000",
            "NULL",
            "150000000",
            "150000000",
            "400000000",
            "150000000",
            "25000000",
            "300000000",
            "NULL",
            "NULL",
            "240000000",
            "NULL",
            "<AU_TFN>",
            "400000000",
            "335000000",
            "NULL",
            "755000000",
            "520000000",
            "435000000",
            "NULL",
            "600000000",
            "150000000",
            "335000000",
            "NULL",
            "755000000",
            "100000000",
            "335000000",
            "755000000",
            "125000000",
            "435000000",
            "NULL",
            "600000000",
            "330000000",
            "335000000",
            "NULL",
            "755000000",
            "120000000",
            "335000000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "SerialNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "M0007",
            "M0003",
            "M0010",
            "M0018",
            "M0013",
            "M0002",
            "M0014",
            "M0011",
            "M0047",
            "M0024",
            "M0035",
            "M0017",
            "M0040",
            "M0036",
            "M0022",
            "M0015",
            "M0043",
            "M0020",
            "M0012",
            "M0032",
            "M0027",
            "M0030",
            "M0039",
            "M0044",
            "M0021",
            "M0008",
            "M0025",
            "M0001",
            "M0023",
            "M0031",
            "M0009",
            "M0033",
            "M0042",
            "M0048",
            "M0005",
            "M0016",
            "M0028",
            "M0037",
            "M0038",
            "M0041",
            "M0026",
            "M0050",
            "M0029",
            "M0004",
            "M0034",
            "M0046",
            "M0006",
            "M0045",
            "M0019",
            "M0049",
            "M0041",
            "M0026",
            "M0050",
            "M0029",
            "M0004",
            "M0034",
            "M0046",
            "M0006",
            "M0045",
            "M0019",
            "M0049"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Customer",
        "ID_Karyawan",
        "SerialNumber"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Customer"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Pembeli",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Customer"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Karyawan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Mobil",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "SerialNumber"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "PhoneKaryawan": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Karyawan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "K0001",
            "K0002",
            "K0003",
            "K0004",
            "K0005",
            "K0006",
            "K0007",
            "K0008",
            "K0009",
            "K0010",
            "K0011",
            "K0012",
            "K0013",
            "K0014",
            "K0015",
            "K0016",
            "K0017",
            "K0018",
            "K0019",
            "K0020",
            "K0021",
            "K0022",
            "K0023",
            "K0024",
            "K0025",
            "K0026",
            "K0027",
            "K0028",
            "K0029",
            "K0030",
            "K0031",
            "K0032",
            "K0033",
            "K0034",
            "K0035",
            "K0036",
            "K0037",
            "K0038",
            "K0039",
            "K0040",
            "K0041",
            "K0042",
            "K0043",
            "K0044",
            "K0045",
            "K0046",
            "K0047",
            "K0048",
            "K0049",
            "K0050",
            "K0001",
            "K0002",
            "K0003",
            "K0004",
            "K0007",
            "K0008",
            "K0011",
            "K0014",
            "K0016",
            "K0019",
            "K0020",
            "K0022",
            "K0023",
            "K0024",
            "K0027",
            "K0029",
            "K0031",
            "K0033",
            "K0035",
            "K0036",
            "K0037",
            "K0039",
            "K0044",
            "K0047",
            "K0048",
            "K0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NoTelp": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "083572875692",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "090197875690",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "070184048233",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "013892324141",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "070948528852",
            "009308352885",
            "008108422523",
            "090418135411",
            "009414151311",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "001949871242",
            "014673424685",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "070922222111",
            "070944225551",
            "070920924115",
            "008275287142",
            "000134414221",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "012442953253",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "009740998141",
            "009000998141",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "001314746422",
            "014140536867",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "009895822242",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "002358535353",
            "003156981443",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "001456613322",
            "000990998141",
            "009794329811",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "009719900100",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "011740999143",
            "008909797084",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "009252693533",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "009898958359",
            "009724521455",
            "002567899000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Karyawan",
        "NoTelp"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Karyawan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "Cascade",
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Keluarga": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Karyawan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "K0001",
            "K0002",
            "K0005",
            "K0007",
            "K0017",
            "K0019",
            "K0020",
            "K0021",
            "K0029",
            "K0031",
            "K0034",
            "K0037",
            "K0039",
            "K0011",
            "K0041",
            "K0044",
            "K0047",
            "K0003",
            "K0004",
            "K0050"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Nama": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Fadla",
            "Gery",
            "Andi",
            "Dinda",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Hananto",
            "Zipora",
            "Hokky",
            "Ozawa",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dinka",
            "Deka",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Simon",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Raul",
            "Maul"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "TipeAsuransi": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tidak Asuransi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tidak Asuransi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tidak Asuransi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tidak Asuransi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tidak Asuransi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tidak Asuransi"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "BirthDate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1998-01-26",
            "1992-01-21",
            "1995-09-03",
            "1993-08-26",
            "1993-02-01",
            "1978-01-23",
            "1988-04-16",
            "1997-01-17",
            "1988-07-19",
            "1978-04-23",
            "1989-03-13",
            "1999-05-22",
            "1991-03-11",
            "1997-04-15",
            "1998-09-14",
            "1989-08-06",
            "1998-09-09",
            "2001-03-10",
            "1999-05-13",
            "1987-07-21"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Gender": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Karyawan",
        "Nama"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Karyawan",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "ID_Karyawan"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "Cascade",
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Ekstra": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "ID_Ekstra": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaDepan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Attar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "NamaBelakang": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Img": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "ID_Ekstra"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}