{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/wqwang-cerealk/project1/blob/43a256e747954bedf56b494f01d8a64b629398d9/db/database.db.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "store": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_location": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "93 Rockefeller Center",
            "0 Lakewood Center",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "3 Muir Pass",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "519 Eagle Crest Center",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "102 Superior Alley",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "2 1st Way",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "7263 Thackeray Hill",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "5 Rutledge Lane",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "employee_number": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            27,
            16,
            10,
            33,
            23,
            17,
            17,
            31,
            40,
            12,
            25,
            27,
            33,
            11,
            28,
            23,
            11,
            29,
            39,
            11,
            18,
            39,
            24,
            40,
            12,
            24,
            25,
            12,
            19,
            27,
            19
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "store_id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "MakeUp_product": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "product_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "product_name": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Luminous Silk Perfect Glow Foundation",
            "Double Wear Stay-in-Place",
            "Ultra HD Invisible Cover",
            "Airflash Spray",
            "Born This Way Super Coverage",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Under Eye Brightening Corrector",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Touche Éclat All-Over Brightening Pen",
            "BACKSTAGE Glow Face Palette",
            "Ambient Lighting Powder",
            "Killawatt Freestyle Highlighter",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Match Stix Matte Skinstick",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Obsessions Palette",
            "Venus in Fleurs Luxe Palette",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mothership V",
            "Pillow Talk Collection",
            "<PERSON>",
            "You Got The Look",
            "Mercury Retrograde",
            "BADgal BANG!",
            "Lashstash To Go",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Artist Color Pencil",
            "Colorful Wink-It Felt Tip",
            "Rouge Forever",
            "Matte Revolution",
            "Rouge Pur Couture Satin Collection",
            "Power Move Creamy Matte Lip",
            "<PERSON>",
            "K.I.S.S.I.N.G",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Vinyl Cream Stain",
            "High Roller Crease Brush",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Soft Pinch Liquid",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pick It All",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Seaweed Infused Vegan Set",
            "Essential Set",
            "Big Boss Powder",
            "High Roller Crease Brush"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "product_category": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Accessories",
            "Lip",
            "Accessories",
            "Cheek",
            "Cheek",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Accessories",
            "Face",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Face",
            "Face",
            "Face",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Accessories",
            "Eye",
            "Cheek",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Eye",
            "Lip",
            "Cheek",
            "Lip",
            "Cheek",
            "Cheek",
            "Cheek",
            "Eye",
            "Eye",
            "Cheek",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Lip",
            "Cheek",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Eye",
            "Eye",
            "Face",
            "Eye",
            "Accessories",
            "Accessories",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Eye",
            "Cheek",
            "Cheek",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Accessories",
            "Lip",
            "Tools & Brushes",
            "Face",
            "Eye",
            "Face"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "product_id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "sell": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "product_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            8,
            8,
            8,
            8,
            8,
            8,
            8,
            9,
            9,
            9,
            9,
            9,
            9,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            11,
            11,
            11,
            11,
            11,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            12,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            14,
            14,
            14,
            14,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            16,
            16,
            16,
            16,
            16,
            16,
            17,
            17,
            17,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            19,
            19,
            19,
            19,
            20,
            20,
            20,
            20,
            21,
            21,
            21,
            22,
            22,
            22,
            22,
            23,
            23,
            23,
            23,
            24,
            24,
            24,
            25,
            25,
            25,
            26,
            26,
            26,
            26,
            27,
            27,
            27,
            28,
            28,
            28,
            29,
            29,
            29,
            29,
            30,
            30,
            30,
            30,
            31,
            31,
            31,
            31,
            31,
            32,
            32,
            33,
            33,
            33,
            33,
            34,
            34,
            34,
            35,
            35,
            35,
            36,
            36,
            36,
            37,
            37,
            37,
            38,
            38,
            38,
            39,
            39,
            39,
            39,
            40,
            40,
            40,
            40,
            40,
            41,
            41,
            41,
            41,
            41,
            41,
            42,
            42,
            42,
            42,
            42,
            43,
            43,
            44,
            44,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            46,
            46,
            46,
            47,
            47,
            47,
            48,
            48,
            48,
            49,
            49,
            49,
            49,
            50,
            50,
            50,
            50,
            50,
            11,
            15,
            23,
            6,
            23,
            4,
            5,
            7,
            9,
            10,
            8,
            45,
            33,
            32,
            34,
            40,
            31,
            3,
            4,
            29,
            38
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            4,
            7,
            15,
            19,
            22,
            25,
            30,
            3,
            11,
            13,
            17,
            20,
            29,
            4,
            6,
            20,
            28,
            1,
            2,
            9,
            13,
            15,
            16,
            24,
            31,
            2,
            6,
            8,
            10,
            22,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            30,
            4,
            3,
            5,
            6,
            10,
            11,
            14,
            15,
            17,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            24,
            27,
            28,
            2,
            3,
            5,
            9,
            10,
            13,
            15,
            18,
            20,
            23,
            29,
            3,
            5,
            12,
            19,
            20,
            25,
            31,
            3,
            7,
            10,
            18,
            22,
            26,
            1,
            3,
            10,
            17,
            19,
            24,
            7,
            9,
            15,
            19,
            29,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            15,
            16,
            19,
            21,
            23,
            27,
            30,
            31,
            3,
            4,
            7,
            12,
            16,
            18,
            20,
            28,
            30,
            5,
            17,
            24,
            30,
            5,
            9,
            10,
            17,
            20,
            22,
            27,
            2,
            7,
            9,
            14,
            24,
            28,
            3,
            19,
            31,
            6,
            18,
            22,
            1,
            5,
            11,
            27,
            6,
            19,
            26,
            30,
            4,
            13,
            29,
            5,
            18,
            26,
            30,
            4,
            8,
            17,
            29,
            11,
            17,
            28,
            4,
            7,
            19,
            1,
            3,
            18,
            25,
            7,
            19,
            30,
            8,
            10,
            21,
            3,
            8,
            19,
            22,
            4,
            17,
            19,
            28,
            3,
            4,
            16,
            19,
            20,
            2,
            10,
            5,
            7,
            14,
            29,
            11,
            27,
            30,
            6,
            19,
            30,
            11,
            17,
            29,
            5,
            18,
            25,
            11,
            28,
            29,
            4,
            7,
            16,
            21,
            1,
            7,
            14,
            18,
            30,
            4,
            14,
            17,
            25,
            27,
            30,
            2,
            6,
            18,
            21,
            29,
            8,
            23,
            6,
            18,
            20,
            30,
            7,
            9,
            18,
            25,
            7,
            18,
            24,
            10,
            15,
            29,
            11,
            19,
            23,
            30,
            1,
            12,
            13,
            24,
            30,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            11,
            28,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            32,
            26,
            25,
            26,
            26
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "product_id",
        "store_id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "store_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "store",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "store_id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "product_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "MakeUp_product",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "product_id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "customer": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "customer_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            105,
            106,
            107,
            108,
            109,
            110,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            114,
            115,
            116,
            117,
            118,
            119,
            120,
            121,
            122,
            123,
            124,
            125,
            126,
            127,
            128,
            129,
            130,
            131,
            132,
            133,
            134,
            135,
            136,
            137,
            138,
            139,
            140,
            141,
            142,
            143,
            144,
            145,
            146,
            147,
            148,
            149,
            150,
            151,
            152,
            153,
            154,
            155,
            156,
            157,
            158,
            159,
            160,
            161,
            162,
            163,
            164,
            165,
            166,
            167,
            168,
            169,
            170,
            171,
            172,
            173,
            174,
            175,
            176,
            177,
            178,
            179,
            180,
            181,
            182,
            183,
            184,
            185,
            186,
            187,
            188,
            189,
            190,
            191,
            192,
            193,
            194,
            195,
            196,
            197,
            198,
            199,
            200,
            201,
            202,
            203,
            204,
            205,
            206,
            207,
            208,
            209,
            210,
            211,
            212,
            213,
            214,
            215,
            216,
            217,
            218,
            219,
            220,
            221,
            222,
            223,
            224,
            225,
            226,
            227,
            228,
            229,
            230,
            231,
            232,
            233,
            234,
            235,
            236,
            237,
            238,
            239,
            240,
            241,
            242,
            243,
            244,
            245,
            246,
            247,
            248,
            249,
            250,
            251,
            252,
            253,
            254,
            255,
            256,
            257,
            258,
            259,
            260,
            261,
            262,
            263,
            264,
            265,
            266,
            267,
            268,
            269,
            270,
            271,
            272,
            273,
            274,
            275,
            276,
            277,
            278,
            279,
            280,
            281,
            282,
            283,
            284,
            285,
            286,
            287,
            288,
            289,
            290,
            291,
            292,
            293,
            294,
            295,
            296,
            297,
            298,
            299,
            300
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "customer_name": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Early Pottery",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Saxe Station",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Konstanze Collet",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Morgana Eamer",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Curtice Snooks",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sallee Desantis",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brita Searle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Price Cowderay",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Atalanta Trafford",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Regen Boots",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Marjy Reisin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Hilde Impey",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Concordia Pritchitt",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Saunderson Sellors",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brook Asals",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "9 Fieldstone Point",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "2874 8th Hill",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "92 Manley Point",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "92593 Packers Center",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "91 Karstens Alley",
            "4 Bay Hill",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "04 Packers Drive",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "9 Melrose Lane",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "9814 Westport Court",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "7988 Weeping Birch Street",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "073 International Court",
            "41 Novick Center",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "2 Fairfield Court",
            "6 Sullivan Court",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "97698 Mifflin Center",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "1 Truax Pass",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "6 Rutledge Alley",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "756 Cody Center",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "57 Drewry Plaza",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "739 Darwin Center",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "3 Blackbird Plaza",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "9 Bluejay Pass",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "6 Tony Center",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "18 Heffernan Court",
            null,
            "96 Hanson Crossing",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "4 Aberg Court",
            null,
            "0656 Spaight Crossing",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "7 Boyd Park",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "3 Declaration Way",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "41 Packers Place",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "5 Loomis Point",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "0 Mitchell Center",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "217 Pennsylvania Hill",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "9 Division Center",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "912 Artisan Pass",
            null,
            "9786 Forest Center",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "81812 Little Fleur Hill",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "914 Old Gate Hill",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "6 Tennyson Place"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "dheningamd@gov.uk",
            null,
            "lmarkovichf@gov.uk",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            null,
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2809064201",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "3939184518",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2658308570",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "5768978074",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "5501744507",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "2382998244",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "1794145622",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "3891391645",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "4601860585",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "5971423861",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "1047289351",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "1396073581",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "5921132413",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            null,
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "3261490213",
            "3691386987",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "3081906677",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "3886925040",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "5605014136",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            null,
            "2114156148",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "5463005867",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "2118072146",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            null,
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "2807282027",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "member_id": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "47-828-8493",
            "61-327-0518",
            null,
            null,
            "33-513-6259",
            "00-928-0683",
            null,
            "89-288-5966",
            "19-218-3872",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "44-634-8284",
            "56-742-4422",
            "29-692-5442",
            null,
            "32-659-9889",
            "40-978-0009",
            "58-599-4414",
            null,
            "95-978-7743",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "71-715-2537",
            "85-081-9098",
            "34-471-1229",
            null,
            "94-857-9743",
            "93-084-7343",
            "62-796-3588",
            "64-688-4193",
            null,
            null,
            "74-099-5078",
            null,
            null,
            "74-414-0694",
            "42-480-4413",
            null,
            "73-620-0361",
            "27-493-7723",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "28-690-9212",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "23-296-8092",
            "74-769-0635",
            "50-166-1416",
            null,
            "62-625-0529",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "64-415-4558",
            "26-301-6587",
            "19-479-0055",
            "59-649-1654",
            "86-903-0960",
            "98-336-8984",
            "83-201-6960",
            "46-743-6412",
            "60-816-1617",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "14-043-7071",
            null,
            null,
            "64-457-2807",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "10-020-8192",
            null,
            "72-935-1084",
            "32-546-5753",
            "92-923-9329",
            "98-532-0564",
            "87-951-9579",
            "05-898-5896",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "86-646-1103",
            null,
            "22-200-3162",
            "34-720-5737",
            null,
            "70-092-3494",
            null,
            "71-919-9533",
            null,
            "97-200-0061",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "45-639-4090",
            "74-086-8412",
            null,
            "41-949-7011",
            "85-286-5582",
            null,
            "75-553-1930",
            "69-291-2587",
            "29-756-0925",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "25-595-5125",
            "90-665-2233",
            "57-711-2285",
            "65-864-1007",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "16-733-5351",
            "25-619-2031",
            "30-019-9005",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "69-700-5225",
            "65-930-5458",
            "96-140-0698",
            "40-654-9776",
            null,
            "62-877-0218",
            "29-293-5880",
            null,
            "96-861-8463",
            "94-109-2029",
            "21-084-4629",
            "66-553-5597",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "76-128-2734",
            null,
            "30-375-0089",
            "88-619-2720",
            "40-814-8648",
            "48-574-7197",
            "68-829-7392",
            null,
            "57-253-3326",
            "20-024-7519",
            null,
            "88-945-0657",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "34-033-3845",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "27-771-0070",
            null,
            "37-644-7872",
            null,
            "50-848-8190",
            "50-183-2186",
            "29-624-2038",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "51-116-2191",
            null,
            "50-803-9836",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "50-664-7695",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "87-847-2607",
            "87-246-8281",
            "00-982-5571",
            "14-532-1001",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "38-381-7208",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "11-741-2511",
            "91-941-0748",
            null,
            "18-303-7518",
            "44-124-6905",
            null,
            "50-586-5614",
            "19-755-4471",
            null,
            "55-678-5213",
            null,
            null,
            "63-754-4289",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "45-768-0517",
            "79-812-6933",
            "34-064-5122",
            "19-853-8710",
            null,
            "34-507-1116",
            "49-596-5427",
            "01-494-8897",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "91-888-5591",
            "30-406-4141",
            null,
            "00-040-5385",
            null,
            null,
            "12-590-1367",
            null,
            "44-574-0519",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "55-601-9793",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "66-013-3729",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "36-162-0576",
            "46-815-1199",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "36-352-2839",
            null,
            "55-143-4906",
            null,
            "76-994-7159",
            null,
            "97-477-3963",
            null,
            null,
            "48-454-4635",
            null,
            null,
            "22-706-1375",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "42-220-4389",
            "63-287-7219",
            null,
            "29-894-8614",
            "38-182-8176",
            null,
            null,
            "21-133-7029",
            "74-152-5408",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "29-599-5230"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Brand": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "brand_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "brand_name": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "amika",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "BECCA Cosmetics",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dior",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "fresh",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Hourglass",
            "HUDA BEAUTY",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "La Mer",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "MAKE UP FOR EVER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "NARS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "PAT McGRATH LABS",
            "Peace Out",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sakara Life",
            "Smashbox",
            "stila",
            "TOM FORD",
            "tarte",
            "Urban Decay",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Youth To The People",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The 7 Virtues"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "brand_classification": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "luxury",
            "affordable",
            "affordable",
            "affordable"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Invoice": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "purchase_id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            105,
            106,
            107,
            108,
            109,
            110,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            114,
            115,
            116,
            117,
            118,
            119,
            120,
            121,
            122,
            123,
            124,
            125,
            126,
            127,
            128,
            129,
            130,
            131,
            132,
            133,
            134,
            135,
            136,
            137,
            138,
            139,
            140,
            141,
            142,
            143,
            144,
            145,
            146,
            147,
            148,
            149,
            150,
            151,
            152,
            153,
            154,
            155,
            156,
            157,
            158,
            159,
            160,
            161,
            162,
            163,
            164,
            165,
            166,
            167,
            168,
            169,
            170,
            171,
            172,
            173,
            174,
            175,
            176,
            177,
            178,
            179,
            180,
            181,
            182,
            183,
            184,
            185,
            186,
            187,
            188,
            189,
            190,
            191,
            192,
            193,
            194,
            195,
            196,
            197,
            198,
            199,
            200,
            201,
            202,
            203,
            204,
            205,
            206,
            207,
            208,
            209,
            210,
            211,
            212,
            213,
            214,
            215,
            216,
            217,
            218,
            219,
            220,
            221,
            222,
            223,
            224,
            225,
            226,
            227,
            228,
            229,
            230,
            231,
            232,
            233,
            234,
            235,
            236,
            237,
            238,
            239,
            240,
            241,
            242,
            243,
            244,
            245,
            246,
            247,
            248,
            249,
            250,
            251,
            252,
            253,
            254,
            255,
            256,
            257,
            258,
            259,
            260,
            261,
            262,
            263,
            264,
            265,
            266,
            267,
            268,
            269,
            270,
            271,
            272,
            273,
            274,
            275,
            276,
            277,
            278,
            279,
            280,
            281,
            282,
            283,
            284,
            285,
            286,
            287,
            288,
            289,
            290,
            291,
            292,
            293,
            294,
            295,
            296,
            297,
            298,
            299,
            300,
            301,
            302,
            303,
            304,
            305,
            306,
            307,
            308,
            309,
            310,
            311,
            312,
            313,
            314,
            315,
            316,
            317,
            318,
            319,
            320,
            321,
            322,
            323,
            324,
            325,
            326,
            327,
            328,
            329,
            330,
            331,
            332,
            333,
            334,
            335,
            336,
            337,
            338,
            339,
            340,
            341,
            342,
            343,
            344,
            345,
            346,
            347,
            348,
            349,
            350,
            351,
            352,
            353,
            354,
            355,
            356,
            357,
            358,
            359,
            360,
            361,
            362,
            363,
            364,
            365,
            366,
            367,
            368,
            369,
            370,
            371,
            372,
            373,
            374,
            375,
            376,
            377,
            378,
            379,
            380,
            381,
            382,
            383,
            384,
            385,
            386,
            387,
            388,
            389,
            390,
            391,
            392,
            393,
            394,
            395,
            396,
            397,
            398,
            399,
            400,
            401,
            402,
            403,
            404,
            405,
            406,
            407,
            408,
            409,
            410,
            411,
            412,
            413,
            414,
            415,
            416,
            417,
            418,
            419,
            420,
            421,
            422,
            423,
            424,
            425,
            426,
            427,
            428,
            429,
            430,
            431,
            432,
            433,
            434,
            435,
            436,
            437,
            438,
            439,
            440,
            441,
            442,
            443,
            444,
            445,
            446,
            447,
            448,
            449,
            450,
            451,
            452,
            453,
            454,
            455,
            456,
            457,
            458,
            459,
            460,
            461,
            462,
            463,
            464,
            465,
            466,
            467,
            468,
            469,
            470,
            471,
            472,
            473,
            474,
            475,
            476,
            477,
            478,
            479,
            480,
            481,
            482,
            483,
            484,
            485,
            486,
            487,
            488,
            489,
            490,
            491,
            492,
            493,
            494,
            495,
            496,
            497,
            498,
            499,
            500
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "total_amount": {
          "TYPE": "Real",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            59.7,
            365.4,
            381.2,
            173.2,
            413.6,
            99.3,
            157.4,
            144.2,
            461.4,
            348.0,
            46.2,
            333.1,
            78.9,
            354.7,
            109.6,
            361.1,
            262.6,
            142.2,
            273.0,
            263.1,
            87.7,
            429.7,
            363.2,
            363.9,
            230.5,
            418.9,
            494.3,
            400.7,
            245.6,
            64.2,
            453.4,
            220.8,
            136.0,
            340.1,
            372.5,
            253.7,
            340.2,
            42.1,
            240.6,
            360.1,
            242.7,
            162.8,
            299.8,
            145.0,
            495.6,
            69.1,
            117.8,
            143.9,
            330.5,
            383.6,
            417.6,
            100.0,
            86.8,
            330.9,
            384.2,
            227.2,
            77.4,
            392.3,
            360.4,
            334.1,
            467.9,
            205.5,
            145.4,
            450.2,
            245.0,
            288.2,
            413.8,
            330.1,
            466.0,
            194.1,
            336.3,
            459.7,
            362.3,
            75.7,
            69.2,
            216.3,
            302.9,
            275.3,
            370.4,
            465.0,
            145.5,
            98.7,
            145.7,
            219.6,
            356.0,
            417.7,
            228.4,
            267.5,
            80.7,
            305.8,
            163.3,
            361.7,
            263.2,
            129.9,
            321.2,
            237.5,
            412.6,
            486.9,
            247.1,
            266.5,
            387.3,
            351.3,
            364.9,
            81.7,
            420.6,
            285.1,
            35.8,
            349.0,
            150.3,
            45.7,
            177.2,
            442.6,
            476.5,
            74.5,
            172.8,
            281.9,
            303.3,
            412.2,
            380.0,
            247.8,
            309.4,
            460.8,
            337.5,
            91.8,
            355.7,
            342.3,
            127.9,
            197.4,
            331.0,
            406.8,
            474.8,
            208.5,
            289.5,
            341.3,
            370.1,
            262.5,
            193.9,
            377.4,
            103.6,
            390.2,
            476.0,
            202.1,
            166.9,
            151.4,
            306.6,
            46.2,
            85.4,
            140.3,
            343.9,
            220.1,
            251.1,
            114.0,
            348.2,
            66.7,
            128.8,
            223.0,
            174.2,
            209.2,
            338.0,
            435.7,
            413.8,
            189.0,
            488.9,
            189.8,
            286.0,
            446.2,
            481.6,
            163.1,
            79.3,
            101.4,
            229.6,
            378.8,
            201.1,
            123.6,
            406.5,
            371.6,
            427.7,
            97.4,
            415.8,
            384.4,
            459.0,
            439.3,
            325.5,
            374.1,
            446.5,
            437.1,
            469.1,
            249.1,
            494.7,
            270.3,
            362.7,
            59.7,
            208.0,
            37.7,
            291.7,
            193.8,
            86.7,
            435.7,
            159.9,
            449.9,
            314.6,
            492.8,
            217.6,
            51.1,
            350.2,
            30.5,
            480.3,
            95.0,
            403.5,
            463.0,
            355.7,
            296.7,
            42.8,
            84.3,
            84.6,
            347.5,
            470.8,
            31.4,
            71.4,
            161.1,
            239.8,
            235.3,
            102.6,
            488.7,
            78.1,
            252.7,
            64.3,
            439.5,
            177.9,
            193.8,
            448.1,
            479.2,
            173.8,
            295.4,
            350.6,
            139.1,
            340.3,
            278.4,
            124.4,
            408.1,
            187.5,
            143.9,
            130.7,
            210.7,
            472.8,
            279.3,
            311.1,
            194.8,
            137.4,
            240.8,
            447.1,
            290.9,
            485.8,
            64.5,
            434.9,
            215.7,
            374.4,
            153.3,
            128.6,
            175.7,
            236.6,
            46.5,
            80.5,
            394.1,
            134.0,
            447.4,
            152.4,
            481.1,
            49.6,
            195.8,
            389.4,
            351.7,
            33.4,
            257.7,
            245.2,
            112.2,
            396.8,
            379.3,
            250.5,
            345.1,
            251.7,
            322.7,
            179.1,
            294.9,
            249.2,
            350.3,
            25.8,
            123.0,
            289.9,
            365.6,
            133.0,
            26.6,
            291.4,
            116.6,
            167.1,
            449.5,
            133.4,
            490.0,
            204.3,
            237.5,
            376.8,
            39.5,
            221.2,
            364.1,
            398.5,
            484.1,
            128.5,
            48.5,
            325.8,
            409.3,
            108.8,
            20.4,
            435.3,
            300.8,
            116.2,
            340.3,
            147.0,
            350.3,
            492.4,
            467.5,
            219.9,
            271.3,
            391.7,
            191.4,
            69.2,
            342.9,
            324.6,
            398.3,
            370.8,
            366.1,
            287.8,
            317.1,
            204.7,
            199.0,
            150.9,
            433.0,
            325.2,
            426.7,
            491.1,
            67.2,
            200.7,
            338.6,
            163.3,
            476.2,
            103.9,
            463.2,
            457.0,
            290.0,
            207.7,
            163.9,
            325.3,
            260.6,
            86.6,
            81.6,
            68.8,
            130.8,
            480.4,
            203.8,
            246.4,
            39.3,
            490.3,
            136.4,
            191.5,
            469.2,
            178.8,
            353.3,
            338.9,
            185.3,
            402.0,
            347.2,
            145.1,
            66.8,
            429.7,
            341.9,
            210.2,
            167.8,
            159.1,
            372.2,
            354.4,
            85.6,
            201.4,
            176.6,
            221.4,
            335.7,
            312.0,
            103.4,
            187.0,
            327.8,
            274.5,
            427.2,
            325.4,
            68.3,
            337.8,
            482.9,
            196.2,
            382.5,
            273.2,
            399.5,
            446.8,
            383.6,
            152.4,
            439.8,
            464.2,
            269.9,
            490.8,
            305.6,
            304.4,
            482.7,
            165.8,
            484.2,
            124.9,
            470.2,
            105.0,
            424.8,
            499.6,
            450.3,
            477.6,
            83.5,
            276.6,
            480.6,
            497.0,
            430.4,
            270.2,
            47.8,
            237.5,
            405.0,
            214.0,
            404.6,
            372.4,
            303.3,
            54.7,
            30.8,
            272.4,
            455.8,
            321.9,
            319.3,
            329.3,
            333.4,
            241.6,
            138.0,
            471.6,
            352.6,
            434.6,
            178.6,
            153.3,
            442.9,
            47.4,
            29.7,
            131.3,
            156.1,
            229.4,
            394.1,
            84.1,
            209.5,
            402.3,
            450.3,
            43.1,
            181.0,
            231.5,
            237.5,
            165.6,
            30.9,
            360.8,
            166.9,
            339.7,
            336.5,
            389.9,
            473.5,
            205.3,
            188.0,
            133.1,
            151.4,
            470.5,
            193.4,
            436.8,
            277.1,
            157.7,
            465.9,
            239.5,
            34.5,
            59.4,
            241.9,
            307.3,
            409.3,
            414.1,
            476.6,
            158.3,
            213.7,
            232.7,
            41.5,
            159.6,
            60.9,
            226.3,
            289.2,
            475.7,
            316.7,
            379.0,
            263.6,
            101.0,
            257.1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "payment_method": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Debit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Credit Card",
            "Cash",
            "Cash"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "purchase_month": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "January",
            "December",
            "October",
            "September",
            "March",
            "<PERSON>",
            "August",
            "September",
            "January",
            "November",
            "March",
            "<PERSON>",
            "November",
            "<PERSON>",
            "March",
            "December",
            "<PERSON>",
            "October",
            "May",
            "September",
            "December",
            "October",
            "January",
            "March",
            "August",
            "July",
            "December",
            "October",
            "July",
            "August",
            "January",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "January",
            "July",
            "December",
            "June",
            "July",
            "December",
            "August",
            "May",
            "October",
            "July",
            "March",
            "September",
            "June",
            "March",
            "March",
            "October",
            "November",
            "August",
            "July",
            "November",
            "March",
            "August",
            "April",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "January",
            "July",
            "January",
            "<PERSON>",
            "July",
            "<PERSON>",
            "September",
            "<PERSON>",
            "November",
            "September",
            "April",
            "July",
            "April",
            "March",
            "September",
            "July",
            "<PERSON>",
            "April",
            "January",
            "June",
            "September",
            "March",
            "July",
            "July",
            "<PERSON>",
            "March",
            "<PERSON>",
            "October",
            "October",
            "January",
            "September",
            "June",
            "January",
            "September",
            "<PERSON>",
            "June",
            "March",
            "October",
            "December",
            "August",
            "September",
            "May",
            "September",
            "April",
            "October",
            "August",
            "August",
            "July",
            "October",
            "July",
            "<PERSON>",
            "September",
            "August",
            "January",
            "November",
            "April",
            "January",
            "<PERSON>",
            "December",
            "April",
            "May",
            "July",
            "November",
            "March",
            "<PERSON>",
            "April",
            "May",
            "September",
            "January",
            "July",
            "August",
            "July",
            "October",
            "October",
            "March",
            "October",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "April",
            "July",
            "March",
            "October",
            "April",
            "June",
            "January",
            "July",
            "December",
            "March",
            "May",
            "April",
            "November",
            "April",
            "July",
            "March",
            "June",
            "October",
            "March",
            "May",
            "November",
            "March",
            "March",
            "April",
            "August",
            "October",
            "April",
            "December",
            "January",
            "March",
            "January",
            "August",
            "May",
            "December",
            "March",
            "August",
            "July",
            "July",
            "November",
            "<PERSON>",
            "August",
            "June",
            "May",
            "November",
            "April",
