{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/Terkea/booking-system/blob/4a8f362a1fe1476cec967db801eaf9244060081e/sql.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "band": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sword",
            "Summer Light",
            "Silver Blast Wire",
            "Dub Dub",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jazz Night",
            "Elex",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "genre_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            11,
            1,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            2
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "agent_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            29,
            32,
            36,
            31,
            29,
            30,
            32,
            34,
            37,
            37,
            26
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "genre_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "genre",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "booking": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "number_of_tickets": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            2,
            40,
            40,
            20,
            2,
            4
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "event_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            31,
            21,
            25,
            26,
            31,
            27
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            40,
            47,
            50,
            51,
            54,
            55
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "payment_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "event": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            34,
            37
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "location": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-04-10",
            "2019-11-10",
            "2019-11-20",
            "2019-04-10",
            "2019-02-10",
            "2020-01-15",
            "2019-04-10",
            "2020-02-01",
            "2019-08-24",
            "2019-11-20",
            "2019-07-26",
            "2019-08-30",
            "2019-06-28"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Spanish Fiesta Mallorca",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rok Music Festival",
            "Sand Music Festival",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Canadian Country Music Fiesta ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Mar Del Plata Musica",
            "Rio Fiesta Musica",
            "Lation Fiesta Trujillo",
            "The Lake District Music Festival 2019",
            "Ostpark Munchen Rock Festival 2019",
            "London Summer Festival 2019"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "description": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Spanish Fiesta Mallorca August 2019",
            "Tokyo Jazz Musical November 2019",
            "Rok Music Festival November 2019",
            "Sand Festival November 2019",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Performers: [11.Indie Max, 5.Silver Blast Wire]",
            "Playa Festival Mexico January 2020",
            "Latio Fiesta February 2020",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Performers [11.Indie Max, 5.Silver Blast Wire, 12.Max Pop, 5.Silver Blast Wire]",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Full Address: \n81735 Munchen, BRD\nPerformance Time: \n18:00\nPerformers: \n[1.Wire Blast, 3.Sword, 5.Silver Blast Wire, 7.America, 10.Elex]\nOther Details: \nDas beste Rock- und Rockfestival in MÃ¼nchen 2019",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "tickets_available": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "0",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "50000",
            "70000",
            "70000",
            "50000",
            "50000",
            "60000",
            "60000",
            "40000",
            "70000",
            "50000",
            "360",
            "70000",
            "2500"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ticket_price": {
          "TYPE": "Float",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "0",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            380,
            1200,
            985,
            785,
            980,
            995,
            695,
            780,
            885,
            850,
            850,
            850,
            460
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "event_type": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Concert",
            "Concert",
            "Concert",
            "Festival",
            "Concert",
            "Concert",
            "Concert",
            "Concert",
            "Festival",
            "Concert",
            "Festival",
            "Festival",
            "Festival"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "organizer_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            56,
            57
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-04-29 02:40:07",
            "2019-05-05 17:50:19",
            "2019-05-14 14:31:34",
            "2019-05-14 15:14:11"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "updated_by": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            1,
            1,
            56,
            57
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "event_performers": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            114
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "event_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            26,
            26,
            30,
            30,
            30,
            30,
            31,
            31,
            31,
            31,
            34,
            34,
            34,
            34,
            34,
            37,
            37,
            37,
            37
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "band_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            11,
            5,
            11,
            5,
            12,
            5,
            10,
            12,
            5,
            6,
            1,
            3,
            5,
            7,
            10,
            4,
            8,
            9,
            12
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "genre": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Metal",
            "Pop",
            "Techno",
            "Country Music",
            "Electro Dance",
            "Dubstep",
            "Rock",
            "Rhythm and Blues",
            "Jazz",
            "Electro",
            "Indie Rock"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "notification": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "details": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Unfortunately we had to cancel 11 Event, no worries. We will refund you the whole ammount of 0.0 GBP It may take a few days for the refund to appear on your statement.",
            "Unfortunately we had to cancel 11 Event, no worries. We will refund you the whole ammount of 0.0 GBP It may take a few days for the refund to appear on your statement."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-04-30 14:17:18",
            "2019-04-30 14:17:18"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "user_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "user",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "payment": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ammount": {
          "TYPE": "Float",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1700,
            12160,
            31360,
            15920,
            1700,
            2780
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "card_no": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "5673231267533212",
            "7854386421974362",
            "8462361382513492",
            null,
            "2743925138423815",
            "3572351286321531"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "expire_date": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "08/21",
            "07/21",
            "05/21",
            null,
            "02/21",
            "02/21"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "card_holder_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Music Fiesta Lmited",
            "Light House Media",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cvs": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "731",
            "472",
            "563",
            null,
            "732",
            "831"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            40,
            47,
            50,
            51,
            54,
            55
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2x The Lake District Music Festival 2019 Concert tickets",
            "40x Spanish Fiesta Mallorca Concert tickets",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "20x Canadian Country Music Fiesta  Concert tickets",
            "2x The Lake District Music Festival 2019 Festival tickets",
            "4x Playa Festival Mexico Concert tickets"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_created": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-05-12 22:09:57",
            "2019-05-13 15:05:20",
            "2019-05-14 10:45:55",
            "2019-05-14 11:33:01",
            "2019-05-14 12:51:08",
            "2019-05-14 13:04:39"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "discounted": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "user_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "user",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "user": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "title": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Mr.",
            "Ms",
            "Mr",
            "Ms",
            "Mrs.",
            "Mr",
            "Miss",
            "Ms",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Miss",
            "Mr.",
            "Ms",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Miss",
            "Mr.",
            "Mrs.",
            "Miss",
            "Mr.",
            "Mrs.",
            "Mr.",
            "Ms",
            "Mrs.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mrs.",
            "Mr.",
            "Mrs.",
            "Mrs."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "first_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kate",
            "Bob",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kate",
            "Mike",
            "Sam",
            "Maria",
            "Gary",
            "Harry",
            "Mike",
            "Katie",
            "Jane",
            "Mike",
            "Kate",
            "Tom",
            "Mike ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Belen",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kate",
            "Avril",
            "Alex",
            "Kate",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mel",
            "Alice",
            "Harry",
            "Bob ",
            "Bob",
            "Kate",
            "Dolf",
            "Avril",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "last_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Terchila",
            "White",
            "Stone",
            "Large",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brown",
            "Gray",
            "Cat",
            "White",
            "Smith",
            "Black",
            "Brown",
            "Smart",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Oax",
            "Smith",
            "Rock",
            "Great",
            "Silver",
            "Long",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Jones",
            "Smith",
            "Smith",
            "White",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jones",
            "Great",
            "Ford",
            "Ford ",
            "Broad",
            "<PERSON>",
            "House",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "gender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Female"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address_line": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Vikings Global House",
            "5 Oaks",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "78 Forest Hill Way",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Forest House",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " MECF House",
            "Power House",
            "894 Light House",
            "782 Power House",
            "4 Forest Close",
            "4 Forest Close",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address_line2": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Aldgate",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "",
            null,
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Flat A",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Flat B",
            "Flat C",
            "Flat F",
            "Flat A",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "town": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luton",
            "Luton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Uxbridge",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luton",
            "Luton",
            "Luton",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luton ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "county": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "postcode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "SW7 2NX",
            "BN1 ",
            "E1 7AX",
            "LU13 FX",
            "LU8",
            "SW5",
            "NW12",
            "LU9",
            "SE5",
            "UB7",
            "NW7",
            "SE7",
            "SW6",
            "NW9",
            "NE8",
            "LU3",
            "LU3 3HJ",
            "LU4 5TE",
            "LU6 6OD",
            "W1 7FR",
            "W11 8ED",
            "W14 9SW",
            "W1U 6YW",
            "SW1P 6DX",
            "B4 1AA",
            "LU1",
            "BR1 4SK",
            "LU1 5RU",
            "SW5 2PH",
            "SW5 2PH",
            "LU1 8FS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "SW5 7SQ",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dob": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-05-17",
            "1999-04-07",
            "1998-03-23",
            "1985-01-25",
            "2019-04-28",
            "20/04/1989",
            "1988-04-14",
            "1988-09-06",
            "1990-12-09",
            "1987-04-17",
            "1989-04-08",
            "1987-04-25",
            "1986-04-02",
            "1984-04-01",
            "1994-04-25",
            "1986-03-17",
            "1997-05-17",
            "1965-02-13",
            "1985-03-14",
            "1999-05-27",
            "1998-09-20",
            "1982-05-10",
            "1991-09-05",
            "1995-05-20",
            "1993-02-01",
            "1995-11-15",
            "1996-06-20",
            "1992-02-10",
            "1997-05-17",
            "1996-05-20",
            "1997-09-11",
            "1991-07-05",
            "1988-01-02",
            "2019-05-09"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "",
            null,
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact_phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "corporate_organisation_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            "Music Stars Limited",
            "Country Buzz Limited",
            "Festival Fiesta Limited",
            "Music Festival Inc",
            "Test Corporate",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "Music Fiesta Limited",
            "Events Music Limited",
            "Hopkins Studios Limited",
            "Lighthouse Media Limited",
            "Power House Media Limited",
            null,
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email_address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mobile_no": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "web_address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "www.vikings.com",
            "music-stars.com",
            "www.cbl.com",
            "www.festival-fiesta.co.uk",
            "www.mf.com",
            null,
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "www.music-fiesta.com",
            "www.events.com",
            "www.hopkins-studios.com",
            "www.lighthouse-media.com",
            "www.powerhouse-media.com",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "www.musikkonzerte.com",
            "www.power-entertainment.com",
            "test"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "$2a$08$0239z2O/uUWKIf.QHZ0d6.AAq.jGM0WXuHyGT06yalHlbNJxhzMiC",
            "$2a$08$JCsnAzpEFbG8GR1Ki0SBVu0c66EFREYNNSLN9QLUUOfsgVnnko3YC",
            "$2a$08$G0dJ7Nrsn.OOdK1fzb./r.WwcXEmv.MiksPXIi6ypUI1ryEhwQ/ZS",
            "$2a$08$2SteSn3yHH3Yb5AIYkScwOLRgbztreqlaf.ekEmUawp7vo6U1nkS6",
            "$2a$08$WlYBfNHZbmxY8nVL8gPr4.ltG6mdaVeJg8wjioVw5jJZ7mdMD4Awm",
            "$2a$08$0239z2O/uUWKIf.QHZ0d6.AAq.jGM0WXuHyGT06yalHlbNJxhzMiC",
            "$2a$08$Ya6UUbaa2pCoPksBl5vptOlIvxOO87G3psNGUOusbHaYMXCuugUEy",
            "$2a$08$rBZbHZkzjQ1DqPsQHY.c2.pdBvq.DPle69r3BKD9XjIrnzHjx0XCe",
            "$2a$08$vtFW5Y2AA4Hz.1owHGTRReJRyZ5DvhK8LCUSl.j/B5/LrZyriY1H.",
            "$2a$08$sJpxYHxeXOF3wVnWyHaiMOK25TUAPHfw7U12qxghnTqqm1.C3jhpC",
            "$2a$08$7XzSUFNzjuYZORzvptB/P.gWsIwJRKHGOquickndLNqkvNrAIVQOa",
            "$2a$08$1VLeTA0vu5zINjhVQorU9OT0wJ8n48zz50RB/.YP3r1mYyDydvtLG",
            "$2a$08$4GW5SHyhIPnzEgCflSx4B.IF0nxfpEzOlauafynC0ykIhg5Z79wMu",
            "$2a$08$l8.pgscUl3BYpi4VS2W41OL8aVQX7X0ZLZknWY6AQ9FUb8pRhGHpG",
            "$2a$08$o5KBVEtxab4tWlCUaQSCFuuHkx5NgKpNb1B4NYMkp2ymHQLkifKb2",
            "$2a$08$mzTk3b9cn4S3h73bcPbOQ.y8WLzsrCvarnHc2ILndTExk/Yh0vVwy",
            "$2a$08$0239z2O/uUWKIf.QHZ0d6.AAq.jGM0WXuHyGT06yalHlbNJxhzMiC",
            "$2a$08$0239z2O/uUWKIf.QHZ0d6.AAq.jGM0WXuHyGT06yalHlbNJxhzMiC",
            "$2a$08$0239z2O/uUWKIf.QHZ0d6.AAq.jGM0WXuHyGT06yalHlbNJxhzMiC",
            "$2a$08$.0HWmqIvzppyI6D/obhUI.Payw/Yo4c3eJ9CJInyEE83Yh851JexC",
            "$2a$08$PsF5VyxlXzYwNkdkGYyiuOZpVOz631bz/mPQyBVZ8fCkFZU3XWwue",
            "$2a$08$cpRR0P1J8/DZb2iQ2U9CjOxdKXGqec0PJp5DtpGyMbrEAeBS29Whi",
            "$2a$08$xCqTvyjIWhImkWDF./T4yuIx4qZGe1qYOTXwWLCXEAsokCOYOU.G.",
            "$2a$08$66B3XRwGR3gLsdmbna2P..z4lymmYPx5odfTkscETNhE8dQisIZhK",
            "$2a$08$eOO8GAMhLLECvz6WcAXT/uI33nPGJquywp52oTt0wUDNmquz205r.",
            "$2a$08$G92DS7vLdfma10FKahjykOAmhb/1Ose3peKbdNZ68D1usDWQFVyZ6",
            "$2a$08$5ULjzv7ZQGj7.4xsDpotg.kNtp96mGcyo12jMUWLpPKr9bCF8vBW6",
            "$2a$08$yYSHkKXKo85XIILhTGV9aO8Ve4z8a/T9QfykC7.War8q4TbC2fDSS",
            "$2a$08$N/Kw/2Q.8KtMS7RUqhe05.VXwlIxb8f0FQ3.NioeHLuSN6J8d4NAK",
            "$2a$08$.XLczuAaTsraLNGlIE1IBOl/CysuCkspToci1dCFAB98m008qak0i",
            "$2a$08$j8Ge9twsFulvi2elrtuFwezWd6xleHgS2WSecgzpKDlzl2yq31yem",
            "$2a$08$TLEPi/k1q9uTpRgwDPePlePNmd7leNzSoy3ckq6pQwkdpi9/oJ1wS",
            "$2a$08$tAJJnkM.WFPmHf8IyeTiBeqIa5eIc2GwtuTOskfmaQRAGm8UCjSmy",
            "$2a$08$alS7HxIcRQuMvUctXjOBdufsUzK2LwyIl1KekPOKvrkYcxq87cks."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "events_organiser_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            "",
            "Null",
            "1",
            "1",
            null,
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "Organiser Test",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "null",
            "1",
            "1",
            "null"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_admin": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_agent": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            0,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_created": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-04-23 14:56:24",
            "2019-04-23 14:56:24",
            "2019-04-23 14:56:24",
            "2019-04-23 14:56:24",
            "2019-04-28 17:49:24",
            "2019-04-28 20:51:18",
            "2019-04-28 21:00:07",
            "2019-04-28 21:04:30",
            "2019-04-28 21:06:39",
            "2019-04-28 21:28:17",
            "2019-04-28 21:31:04",
            "2019-04-28 21:34:26",
            "2019-04-28 21:37:03",
            "2019-04-28 21:40:43",
            "2019-04-28 21:44:34",
            "2019-04-28 21:48:43",
            "2019-05-12 21:49:40",
            "2019-05-13 13:15:21",
            "2019-05-13 13:18:43",
            "2019-05-13 13:24:29",
            "2019-05-13 13:28:00",
            "2019-05-13 13:30:59",
            "2019-05-13 13:34:08",
            "2019-05-13 15:00:54",
            "2019-05-13 15:55:30",
            "2019-05-14 09:53:44",
            "2019-05-14 10:14:30",
            "2019-05-14 11:27:07",
            "2019-05-14 12:13:21",
            "2019-05-14 12:39:48",
            "2019-05-14 13:03:25",
            "2019-05-14 13:55:16",
            "2019-05-14 15:01:18",
            "2019-05-15 11:22:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}