{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/adilKhan72/rizqdoor/blob/521ecc3819df0f7c1d8a9e6a5b26b40b23bf7837/rizqdoor.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "admin": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "admin"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "ast_2016"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "appliedjobseeker": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            11,
            13,
            17,
            23,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "postjobid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            57,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            79,
            54,
            74,
            83,
            79,
            79,
            49,
            82,
            79,
            58,
            57
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "adil",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "JAVED ASHRAF",
            "Asif",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "sfad"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "imranmurtaza07@gmail",
            "adilkhanengineer72@g",
            "kumail.mughal123@gma",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "12341"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "coverletter": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "LZXJAD SFKLAJD",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "I have got the experience of banking as Manager operation in Bank and Branch Manager for 25 years",
            "I have got the experience of banking as Manager operation in Bank and Branch Manager since 1991",
            "With reference to your job ad i m applying for teaching vaccancies in your org.i m experienced and qualified candidate.",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "qewr"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cv": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "./user_cv_uploads/imranmurtazagmailcom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/adilkhanengineergmailcom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/kumailmughalgmailcom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/adilkhanengineerswatiigmailcom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/muhammadbgmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/javedashrafkhawajagmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/javedashrafkhawajagmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/fairyasifgmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/umerahmedbuttyahoocom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/hassaanniazihngmailcom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/sajidshaheengmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/sajidshaheengmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/shanwaziryahoocom.pdf",
            "./user_cv_uploads/majokahotmailcom.docx",
            "./user_cv_uploads/adfgmailcom.pdf"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_applied": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "postjobid"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "post-job",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "NoAction",
          "ON_UPDATE": "NoAction"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "blog": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            3,
            5,
            8,
            9
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "title": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "5 Resume Hacks to Get More Interviews",
            "10 New Year’s Resolutions and How to Achieve Them",
            "Tips for Staying Sane During Your Job Search",
            "Words of Wisdom: Inspiration for Your 2017 Job Search"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "paragraph": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "With 2018 just a few short days away, many of us are not only reflecting on the year that passed but looking forward to the new one ahead. When it comes to resolving to be better at something, or a better someone for that matter, we should own up to the fact that the journey to self-improvement is a process. We should view the road to success as a marathon rather than a sprint. For if we did, we’d have a much greater chance of sticking with it when the going gets tough",
            "You’ve updated and posted your resume, signed up for job alerts, and have consistently applied to jobs. Yet, you still haven’t landed your #NewJob2017. Don’t dismay. Our internet sources tell us that it takes roughly one month to find a job for every $10,000 of the paycheck you would like to earn. For example, if you were looking for a job that pays $50,000 a year your job search could take 5 months.\r\n\r\nBelow are some ways to help take away some of your job search pain and put your mind at ease:\r\n\r\n1.  Take a Break\r\n\r\nYou don’t want to run the risk of job search burnout. Taking some time away from your job search to focus on things like your family, friends and health will help you appreciate all that’s good in your life in order to help lift your spirits.",
            "Judging from all the headlines, Facebook posts and tweets 2016 has been a pretty rough year.  But rather than reflect on all the gory details, let’s look onward to 2017\r\nwith the promise and hope that we’ll be able to turn things around in a new year. That said, hope alone cannot change things. It can’t change who we are and it can’t change how we are. If we want to change we must take action. And in order to take action we need to be inspired.\r\n\r\nWhile inspiration comes from many places, today we turn to the Holstee Manifesto. Much\r\ngreater than a mission statement, the Manifesto was created by three founders of a t-shirt company who not only wanted to put their definition of success and happiness in print, but wanted to share their positive intentions with the world.\r\n\r\nIt’s a highly relevant piece of work that can be applied to almost anything in your life, especially to your pursuit for a new job. It begins like this:\r\n\r\nThis is your life. Do what you love, and do it often. If you don’t like something, change it. If you don’t like your job, quit.  If you don’t have enough time, stop watching TV."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "blogtype": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Market-Insights",
            "Our-News",
            "Our-News",
            "Finding-a-Job"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "blog-type": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "admin-id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "types": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_creation": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "admin-id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "admin",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "NoAction",
          "ON_UPDATE": "NoAction"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "city": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "countryid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            13,
            7,
            7,
            7,
            14,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            7,
            11,
            17,
            9
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cityname": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Rawalpindi",
            "Delhi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kukes",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Entre Rios",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "countryid"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "jobcountry",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "NoAction",
          "ON_UPDATE": "NoAction"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "company": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "employerid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            21,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "companybranchname": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Azam Systems and Technologies Pvt Limited",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "adsf",
            "StackWiser",
            "Silkbank",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Blackstone",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "IT Services"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "compinfo": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Established in 2014, Azam Systems &amp; Technologies (Pvt.) Limited is a leading software company providing affordable, reliable and user-friendly software solutions. Our approach is customer-centric and user experience is number one for us. We go to extraordinary lengths to satisfy, delight and nourish our customers.",
            "It company",
            "Established in 2014.Its  is a leading software company providing affordable, reliable and user-friendly software solutions. Our approach is customer-centric and user experience is number one for us. We go to extraordinary lengths to satisfy, delight and nourish our customers.",
            "Established in 1999, Nesis Holding PrivateLimited is a leading software company providing affordable, reliable and user-friendly software solutions. Our approach is customer-centric and user experience is number one for us. We go to extraordinary lengths to satisfy, delight and nourish our customers.",
            "do nothing man",
            "<PERSON>",
            "jhdfg jadhsg jhfgajhk",
            "it&nbsp;",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "",
            "Infomatrix is an international computer project competition, born from a desire to bring the world’s best IT students together. The competition is not just about promoting professional excellence; it also serves to promote intercultural dialogue and cooperation, through the involvement of students and teachers from all around the world.",
            "We provide design, development, application, implementation, support and management of computer and non-computer based technologies for the express purpose of communicating product design intent and constructability. Design technology can be applied to the problems encountered in construction, operation and maintenance of a product.",
            "We are a Research & Development organization with experienced professionals ready and committed to provide you with Innovatively Creative solutions. We design, manufacture and market a range of innovative products developed within the organization with a commitment to technology, design, user affability and environmental consciousness. We conceive, plan and deploy customized solutions according to the needs of our clients. We provide complete solutions of hardware design and firmware applications. Apart from core competencies in Software and Algorithms development, we have the ability to move a project from concept to product form by delivering our customized technologies.\r\n\r\nWe believe to conduct our interaction in a manner that promotes long-term partnerships based on mutual trust and respect. Our endeavor would be to assume responsibility for every task undertaken by us for high quality product delivery as per the expectations of our clients. We will foster and maintain relationships among staff, management, customers and suppliers that enable us to attain our corporate and personal goals.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "howmanyemployees": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "8",
            "5",
            "20",
            "100",
            "3",
            "3",
            "32",
            "323",
            "10",
            "20",
            "11",
            "25",
            "55",
            "18",
            "30",
            "70",
            "192"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "countrycode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "213",
            "32",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92",
            "92"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "234523452352",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "25423212245",
            "2345234525413",
            "234523532",
            "2435245323452",
            "<AU_TFN>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "3161502278",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "8735203",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "7080200",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "companyfield": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Capital Markets",
            "IT",
            "Software",
            "IT",
            "IT",
            "Hardware's",
            "Building Materials",
            "Broadcast Media",
            "Banking",
            "Computer Software",
            "Events Services",
            "Telecommunications",
            "Computer Software",
            "Computer Software",
            "Computer Software",
            "Education Management",
            "Information Technology and Services"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "30 Mary Street BRISBANE QLD 4000",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Muhamad Kamal House Jansahib Muhallalah Shahi Bazar Kanju Swat Kpk",
            "Muhamad Kamal House Jansahib Muhallalah Shahi Bazar Kanju Swat Kpk",
            "Silkbank",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "I-10 Markaz Islamabad.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "House No 3 Opposite Umania Restaurant Main Muree Road Barakahu Islamabad"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_creation": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "employerid"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "employer",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "NoAction",
          "ON_UPDATE": "NoAction"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "employer": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "companyname": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Azam Systems and Technologies",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Binary Solutionz   Private Limited",
            "Nesis Holding  Private Limited",
            "Do nothing",
            "youlung",
            "StackWiser",
            "Invix",
            "Silkbank",
            "Azam System and Technologies Private Limited",
            "teest",
            "Blackstone",
            "Axcess International Education",
            "SBM Communication",
            "Informatrix",
            "Dera IT Solutions",
            "TeReSol",
            "Leo Solution Academy",
            "Stepnex Services Private Limited",
            "SOFTWARE WALK INC"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Konar",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Kukes",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Berat",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "Berat",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "country": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "China",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "12345678_aA",
            "pakistan_1@1",
            "ahsan1971",
            "Pakistan_11",
            "test1234",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cecos.123",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pakistan_11",
            "Pakistan_11",
            "Pakistan_11",
            "Pakistan_11",
            "Wajid@786",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "login_session": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "0",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_creation": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_updated_last": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "jobcareerlevel": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "careerlevel": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "jobcountry": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "countryname": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "India",
            "USA",
            "United Arab Emirates",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "China",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "jobfield": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "job-field": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Marketing",
            "Software &amp; Web Development",
            "Architects &amp; Construction",
            "Accounts, Finance &amp; Financial Services",
            "Computer Networking",
            "Hotel/Restaurant Management",
            "Telemarketing",
            "Sales &amp; Business Development",
            "Project Management",
            "Operations",
            "Monitoring &amp; Evaluation",
            "Quality Assurance (QA)",
            "Writer",
            "Health &amp; Medicine",
            "Client Services &amp; Customer Support",
            "Hardware",
            "Administration",
            "Teachers/Education, Training &amp; Development",
            "Management Consulting"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "logeduserappliedforjobmanytomany": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "userjobseekerid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            3,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "postjobid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            57,
            48,
            85,
            73,
            83,
            83,
            84,
            84
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "applieddate": {
          "TYPE": "Timestamp",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-03-13 06:00:00",
            "2019-03-06 07:00:00",
            "2019-03-06 07:00:00",
            "2019-03-07 07:00:00",
            "2019-03-14 12:16:27",
            "2019-03-14 12:16:35",
            "2019-04-09 07:18:09",
            "2019-04-09 07:18:14"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "userjobseekerid"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "userjobseeker",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "post-job": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            47,
            48,
            49,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            73,
            74,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "employerid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            8,
            8,
            8,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            11,
            11,
            18,
            19,
            21,
            21,
            23,
            19,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            23,
            29
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "jobtitle": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Junior Product Manager Software Developer",
            "Accountant",
            "NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR",
            "sales and marketing",
            "Deputy Director Special Project Marketing",
            "Operational Manager",
            "Coordinator",
            "Call Center Officer Required",
            "Web Developer",
            "Quality Assurance Analyst",
            "Android Developer",
            "Unity developer",
            "Content Writer Required",
            "BSO",
            "Assistant  Manager",
            "Female Marketer",
            "Marketing Team",
            "Customer Service Representatives",
            "Web Developer Internee",
            "Business Analyst",
            "Software Engineer",
            "Accounts Assistant",
            "Urgent Required Male and Female Teachers",
            "Customer Service Representatives",
            "Big data Developer"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "discription": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "we make safe, simple. We help first responders in public safety and public service, the federal government, and industrial organizations keep communities and our country safe by providing the most reliable radios and P25 communication solutions. We are a qualified and intensely committed team whose number one goal is to be an agile partner our customers can trust, in every situation.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "The City of Hinesville is accepting applications for a Network Administrator. This position oversees data security and maintains production level servers, patches and updates and participates in the support and maintenance of all components of the network according to established specifications. The position also provides direct support to the Information Technology Director.",
            "1) Out door marketing !\r\n2) Bachelors Must !\r\n3) Good communication Skills",
            "Master is must for candidate .Must having 5 year experience of project management.",
            "It wil play a leading role in managing both raw materials and personnel. Oversight of inventory, purchasing and supplies is central to the job. Human resources tasks include determining needs, hiring employees, overseeing assignment of employees and planning staff development.",
            "Following Duties :-\r\n1)Office workflow procedures to ensure maximum efficiency. 2)Maintaining files and records with effective filing systems. 3)Supporting other teams with various administrative tasks.",
            "1)Honest and hardworking .\r\n2) Fluent in English .\r\n3) Capable to work in night shift .",
            "Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, MIS, or other related field preferred\r\nExperience with OOP in PHP, Doctrine, AJAX, JS, jQuery, JSON, Web Services.\r\nWorking knowledge of XML in a PHP programming environments\r\nFamiliarity in ReactJS, bootstrap, symphony framework, micro services.\r\nExperience with Symfony, Doctrine Unit Testing, Agile software development, SVN and GIT a plus.\r\nPHP certifications a plus",
            "Minimum of Bachelor's degree in computer science, engineering, and technology.\r\nThree to Five (3-5) years experience in the quality assurance software testing field.\r\nExperience in quality assurance process and procedure, test plans and test scripts.\r\nSome development experience.\r\nPC proficiency in Microsoft Office applications.\r\nMust be a quick learner.\r\nStrong oral and written communications skills.\r\nAbility to create and maintain professional relationships within all levels of the organization (peers, work groups, customers, supervisors).\r\nAbility to be self-motivated and work independently and as a member of a team.\r\nFlexibility to operate and self-driven to excel in a fast-paced environment.\r\nCapable of multi-tasking, highly organized, with excellent time management skills.\r\nDetail oriented with excellent follow-up practices\r\nKnowledge of Quality Center, Functional Tester, Automation, Performance Test, Security Test.\r\nStrong Project Management Skills.",
            "Understanding of new technologies and the mobile hardware industry\r\nStrong attention to detail and understanding of a startup environment\r\nExperience working with large organizations\r\nProficient understanding of code versioning tools, such as Git\r\nUnderstanding of Google’s Android design principles and interface guidelines",
            "BA/BS in Digital Media, Game Art & Design, Software Development, Computer Science, or related field. May accept additional experience in lieu of a degree.\r\nExperience is desired the following areas: game programming and scripting (AI, weapons, items, objects, particles, vehicles, scenario).\r\nSkilled with Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and other standard graphics applications. Web and multimedia development\r\nExperience using Dreamweaver, HTML, CSS, Flash, and Captivate is a major plus.\r\nFlexibility and ability to adapt to quickly changing circumstances and work priorities in a timely manner.\r\nStrong analytical and problem-solving skills.\r\nUnity game engine experience is highly desired.\r\nFamiliarity with Visual Studio experience is desired.\r\nExperience with immersive virtual reality such as Oculus or GearVR preferred.\r\nPost-production, including non-linear, professional editing with Adobe Premier and After Effects, motion graphics creation, color correction, audio mixing, and video compression preferred.\r\nExperience implementing software and web sites that are compliant with Section 508 Accessibility requirements preferred.\r\nSoftware development including but not limited to, Java, JavaScript, ASP.NET C#, Flex/ActionScript 3, PHP, SQL, neo4j, MongoDB preferred.",
            "Having Good Thinking and Writing Skills!",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "We are seeking a highly-motivated candidate to support our vision. In this role, the Assistant Manager motivates, instills accountability and achieves results to drive success in the position. This role provides overall leadership, supervision, and direction on strategic initiatives and operating standards to positively impact business results.",
            "Female need for marketing work totally indoor office work fixed salary",
            "Marketing team is required for the different event promotion in outside market",
            "...",
            "Looking for an passionate fresh BS IT. graduate with or without experience for internship. Apply only if you're looking to build your career in right direction and planning long term success, we're offering almost all of web product = domain, hosting, ssl ... & services = web application design / development, graphic design, seo .... & SAAS Tools to our clients; that will return same benefits to you as of learning opportunities. Also you will be able to increase your communication skill due to provide technical & sale support to our client through email tickets / chat or phone.\r\n\r\nInternee will work under team leader so they will learn from the team leader in every direction of web development.",
            "Our company is looking for a Business Analyst. The prospective candidate should be well versed in the techniques and methodologies for conducting business analysis, requirements gathering and performing system analysis and design for new and existing applications, processes and systems. The ideal candidate should possess good written and verbal communication skills. Should have worked in the area of Business Analysis for MIS applications.. Should have written Requirement specification and Functional Specificaitons. Should pocess good knowledge of Use Case Analysis, Data Flow Diagrams and different SDLC methodolgoies such a Agile, Scrum , PMI etc.",
            "1)In depth knowledge of .NET Platform\r\n2)Practical experience on C# and ASP.NET\r\n3)Database Programming with MS SQL Server\r\n4)Strong Object Oriented Analytical skills\r\n5)Good knowledge on HTML, XHTML, AJAX, JavaScript and JQuery\r\n6)Assist and coordinate with project managers to perform project analysis, determining functional and technical business requirements, application development.\r\n7)Must have experience of working in crystal reports and other reporting softwares",
            "Experience: 2-3 Years\r\n\r\n(Experience of Audit Firm is must)\r\n\r\nACCA Affiliates / CA Inter\r\n\r\nSound Knowledge of MS Office and Quick Books is must.\r\n\r\nTASKS:-\r\n\r\nPreparing Invoices as per operations\r\nReporting Biweekly of Receivables\r\nContacting Clients for Payments and CPR\r\nRecording Invoices, Payments and discounts in Quick Books\r\nDrafting GST / PST Returns\r\nAssisting Accounts Team",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "...Good English Communication, Good listening, Competent, Good team player",
            "Job Description:-\r\n\r\n• 5+ years of experience owning and building data pipelines.\r\n• Extensive knowledge of data engineering tools, technologies and approaches\r\n• Ability to absorb business problems and understand how to service required data needs\r\n• Design and operation of robust distributed systems\r\n• Proven experience building data platforms from scratch for data consumption across a wide variety of use cases (e.g data science, ML, scalability etc)\r\n• Demonstrated ability to build complex, scalable systems with high quality Experience with specific AWS technologies (such as S3, Redshift, EMR, and Kinesis)\r\n• Experience with multiple data technologies and concepts such as Airflow, Kafka, Hadoop, Hive, Spark, MapReduce, SQL, NoSQL, and Columnar databases. a plus\r\n• Experience in one or more of Java, Scala, python and bash.\r\n\r\n\r\nExpected Outcomes:\r\n\r\n• Design and implement data infrastructure and processing workflows required to build a data lake in AWS to support data science, machine learning, BI and reporting also in AWS Build robust, efficient and reliable data pipelines consisting of diverse data sources\r\n• Design and develop real time streaming and batch processing pipeline solutions\r\n• Own the data expertise and data quality for the pipelines\r\n• Drive the collection of new data and refinement of existing data sources\r\n• Identify shared data needs across Advanced Auto Parts, understand their specific requirements, and build efficient and scalable pipelines to meet various needs\r\n• Build data stores for feature variables required for machine learning"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "skills": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "campaigning,marketing",
            "accounting",
            "networking",
            "Marketing",
            "Marketing",
            "Managing",
            "Managing",
            "English",
            "php",
            "Analysis",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Unity",
            "Writing",
            "S",
            "Management",
            "English",
            "English",
            "CSR",
            "Html,Php,JavaScript,Css",
            "Marketing,Management",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Managing",
            "Teaching",
            "CSR",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "noposition": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            5,
            8,
            5,
            3,
            3,
            5,
            1,
            10,
            2,
            1,
            4,
            12,
            5,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            20,
            10,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "jobfield": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Architects &amp; Construction",
            "Accounts, Finance &amp; Financial Services",
            "Computer Networking",
            "Sales &amp; Business Development",
            "Project Management",
            "Operations",
            "Monitoring &amp; Evaluation",
            "Telemarketing",
            "Software &amp; Web Development",
            "Quality Assurance (QA)",
            "Software &amp; Web Development",
            "Software &amp; Web Development",
            "Writer",
            "Sales &amp; Business Development",
            "Operations",
            "Marketing",
            "Marketing",
            "Telemarketing",
            "Software &amp; Web Development",
            "Marketing",
            "Software &amp; Web Development",
            "Accounts, Finance &amp; Financial Services",
            "Teachers/Education, Training &amp; Development",
            "Telemarketing",
            "Management Consulting"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "country": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "United Arab Emirates",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "China",
            "China",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "exp": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            2,
            1,
            5,
            3,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            1,
            3,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            50000,
            1,
            0,
            2,
            5,
            2,
            2,
            1,
            5
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "currencytype": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "BRR",
            "",
            "DZD",
            "BRR",
            "PKR",
            "DZD",
            "BRR",
            "BRR",
            "DZD",
            "BRR",
            "DZD",
            "BRR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "PKR",
            "USD"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "salary": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            90,
            20,
            30,
            10000,
            30000,
            20000,
            15000,
            3000,
            25000,
            100000,
            10000,
            82000,
            2000,
            16000,
            35000,
            15000,
            25000,
            35000,
            18500,
            0,
            0,
            30000,
            25000,
            1,
            70
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dayofduaration": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "default",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "",
            "0",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "7",
            "",
            "15",
            "10",
            "6",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "1",
            "12"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "gender": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "female",
            "female",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "",
            "both",
            "female",
            "both",
            "",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "both",
            "male",
            "both"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "posteddate": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Wednesday 2 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 2 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 2 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Wednesday 9 January 2019",
            "Saturday 9 February 2019",
            "Monday 11 February 2019",
            "Tuesday 12 February 2019",
            "Wednesday 13 February 2019",
            "Wednesday 13 February 2019",
            "Thursday 14 February 2019",
            "Thursday 14 February 2019",
            "Thursday 14 February 2019",
            "Thursday 14 February 2019",
            "Friday 15 February 2019",
            "Friday 15 February 2019",
            "Friday 22 February 2019"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "1",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "jobcityid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            10,
            11,
            12,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            19,
            22,
            23,
            19,
            9,
            19,
            19,
            9,
            9,
            19,
            19,
            19,
            9,
            9,
            29
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "jobfieldid": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            14,
            15,
            16,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            18,
            13,
            23,
            13,
            13,
            24,
            19,
            21,
            12,
            12,
            18,
            13,
            12,
            13,
            15,
            29,
            18,
            30
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "qualification": {
          "TYPE": "Varbinary",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "496e7465726d656469617465",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "496e7465726d656469617465",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "4d6173746572",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "42616368656c6f72",
            "496e7465726d656469617465",
            "4d6173746572"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_updated_last": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "jobfieldid"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "jobfield",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "employerid"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "employer",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "subscription": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rawalpindi"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "jobtitle": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "sales and marketing",
            "Assistant  Manager",
            "Accounts Assistant",
            "Web Developer Internee"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_creation": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "userjobseeker": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "profilepic": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            "adilkhanengineergmailcom.jpg",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "contact",
            "qase",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dateofbirth": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-02-06",
            "2019-02-06",
            "2019-02-14",
            "2019-02-02",
            "2019-02-28",
            "2019-01-07",
            "1982-10-20"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "gender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "transgender",
            "transgender",
            "male",
            "male",
            "male",
            "male",
            "male"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "country": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "nationality": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "landlinenumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "23141",
            "3444141",
            "3444141",
            "8552883",
            "3333",
            "4",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "countrycode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1246",
            "376",
            "92",
            "244",
            "501",
            "244",
            "92"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mobilenumber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "29",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "8",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "experience": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "15",
            "15",
            "12",
            "5",
            "1",
            "16",
            "5"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "industory": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Chemicals",
            "Broadcast Media",
            "Architecture & Planning",
            "Alternative Medicine",
            "Civil Engineering",
            "Apparel & Fashion",
            "Information Technology and Services"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "currencytype": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "CLP",
            "GBP",
            "PKR",
            "GBP",
            "CYP",
            "DZD",
            "PKR"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "currentsalery": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "12",
            "12",
            "22",
            "5",
            "222",
            "-4",
            "60000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "desiredsalary": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "12",
            "12",
            "22",
            "7",
            "333",
            "-5",
            "80000"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "resume": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "infomalenydanceacademycom.pdf",
            "infoasdfgcom.pdf",
            "adilkhanengineergmailcom.pdf",
            "ceoazamstcom.pdf",
            "capritechhotmailcom.pdf",
            "adfgmailcom.doc",
            "majokahotmailcom.docx"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "13131313",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "12345678",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "Lmkr@ffc12"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "login_session": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_creation": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-03-12 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-13 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-12 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-12 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-12 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-12 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-12 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_updated_last": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}