{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/MrSynnek/DatabaseProject/blob/53c5a83f74d230ff6bbc5ae7780e1074a493a0fc/football_management%20.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "club": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "AFC Wimbledon",
            "Arsenal",
            "Aston villa",
            "Athletic Bilbao",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Blackburn Rovers",
            "Blackpool",
            "Bolton Wanderers",
            "Bournemouth",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Brentford",
            "Brighton & Hove Albion",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bristol Rovers",
            "<PERSON>",
            "BurnleyCardiff City",
            "Burton Albion",
            "Cambridge United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Carlisle United",
            "Charlton Athletic",
            "Chelsea",
            "Cheltenham Town",
            "Chesterfield",
            "Colchester United",
            "Coventry City",
            "Crawley Town",
            "Crewe Alexandra",
            "Crystal Palace",
            "Derby County",
            "Doncaster Rovers",
            "Everton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Forest Green Rovers",
            "Fulham",
            "Gillingham",
            "Grimsby Town",
            "Huddersfield Town",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Ipswich Town F.C.",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "Leeds United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Leyton Orient",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Liverpool FC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Maidenhead United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Manchester United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Middlesbrough",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Milton Keynes Dons",
            "Morecambe",
            "Newcastle United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Northampton Town",
            "Norwich City FC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Oldham Athletic",
            "Oxford United",
            "Peterborough United",
            "Plymouth Argyle",
            "Port Vale",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Preston North End",
            "Queens Park Rangers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Real Madrid CF",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rotherham United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Scunthorpe United",
            "Sheffield United",
            "Sheffield Wednesday",
            "Shrewsbury Town",
            "Southampton FC",
            "Southend United",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Sunderland",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Swindon Town",
            "Torquay United",
            "Tottenham Hotspur FC",
            "Tranmere Rovers",
            "Walsall",
            "Watford",
            "West Bromwich Albion",
            "West Ham United",
            "Wigan Athletic",
            "Woking",
            "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
            "Wrexham",
            "Wycombe Wanderers"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Alias": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Kingsmeadow",
            "The Gunners",
            "Villans",
            "The Lions",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Blues",
            "The Riversiders",
            "The Seasiders",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Cherries",
            "The Bantams",
            "The Bees",
            "Seagulls",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Pirates",
            "<PERSON>",
            "WalesOnline",
            "Burton Albion",
            "United",
            "The Bluebirds",
            "Cumbrians",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Blues",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Spireites",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Reds",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Eagles",
            "The Rams",
            "Donny",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Grecians",
            "Barça",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Rovers",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "the Mariners",
            "The Terriers",
            "The Tigers",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Juve",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Foxes",
            "The Os",
            "The Imps",
            "The Reds",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Magpies",
            "<PERSON>",
            "the Red Devils",
            "The Stags",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Dockers",
            "The Dons",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Magpies",
            "<PERSON>",
            "the Cobblers",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Latics",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Valiants",
            "Pompey boys",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Superhoops",
            "The Royals",
            "The Whites",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Millers",
            "The Ammies",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Blades",
            "The Owls",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Black Cats",
            "The Swans",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Super White Army",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Hornets",
            "the Baggies",
            "The Hammers",
            "The Latics",
            "The Cardinals",
            "Wolves",
            "Red Dragons",
            "The Chairboys"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Location": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bilbao ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Blackburn",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bournemouth",
            "Bradford",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bristol",
            "Bristol",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Burnley",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Chesterfield",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Coventry",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Crewe",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Derby",
            "Doncaster",
            "Liverpool",
            "Exeter",
            "Barcelona",
            "Fleetwood",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Fulham",
            "Gillingham",
            "Grimsby",
            "Huddersfield",
            "Hull",
            "Ipswich",
            "Turin",
            "Leeds",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Leyton",
            "Lincoln",
            "Liverpool",
            "Luton",
            "Macclesfield",
            "Maidenhead",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Middlesbrough",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Morecambe",
            "Newcastle",
            "Newport",
            "Northampton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Oldham",
            "Oxford",
            "Peterborough",
            "Plymouth",
            "Port",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Preston North",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Rotherham",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sheffield",
            "Sheffield",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Southampton",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Stoke",
            "Sunderland",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Swindon",
            "Torquay",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Tranmere",
            "Walsall",
            "Watford",
            "West Bromwich",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Wigan",
            "Woking",
            "Wolverhampton",
            "Wrexham",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "League": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "EFL League One",
            "Premier League",
            "Premier League",
            "La Liga",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League One",
            "National League",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League Two",
            "La Liga",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "Serie A",
            "EFL Championship",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL League One",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "National League",
            "Premier League",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL League Two",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "La Liga",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL League Two",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL Championship",
            "National League",
            "Premier League",
            "EFL League One",
            "EFL League Two",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "EFL Championship",
            "National League",
            "EFL League One",
            "National League",
            "EFL League One"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "In_sponser": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1400000,
            "<PERSON>",
            6000000,
            5000000,
            10007550,
            10000000,
            15000000,
            1500000,
            4300000,
            3500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1500055,
            1500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1400000,
            14253725,
            1700000,
            1500055,
            200000,
            "<PERSON>",
            52225,
            1500000,
            12500000,
            8000,
            11007550,
            52225,
            10000621,
            52225,
            52225,
            12000000,
            15000000,
            1230000,
            8000000,
            980000,
            20000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            52225,
            7690005,
            1500000,
            52225,
            6510000,
            12560000,
            "<PERSON>",
            15000000,
            24651200,
            6000000,
            400000,
            "<PERSON>",
            13000000,
            170000,
            52225,
            12456575,
            20000000,
            15000000,
            7541239,
            12000000,
            1240000,
            1500000,
            8521476,
            6500000,
            7412358,
            10245782,
            5000000,
            9654000,
            6458000,
            59000000,
            6800000,
            12035478,
            17425368,
            25000000,
            1500000,
            21650000,
            11695220,
            20000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            20123478,
            15247536,
            5500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            7500000,
            6000000,
            6410000,
            12453457,
            1025482,
            1740000,
            "<PERSON>",
            3550000,
            8245637,
            10000000,
            5800000,
            17423574,
            2500000,
            1750000,
            1700000,
            1750000,
            12425371,
            "<PERSON>",
            21035478,
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "In_ticket": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            52900,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            150000,
            75373,
            1455000,
            980000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            200000,
            400000,
            780000,
            66000,
            55500,
            60000,
            750040,
            85247,
            750040,
            66000,
            "<PERSON>",
            51400,
            54000,
            410555,
            300000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1455000,
            54000,
            65000,
            75000,
            56000,
            100000,
            12000000,
            23500,
            250000,
            98000,
            400000,
            54610,
            56000,
            965000,
            410555,
            95000,
            "<PERSON>",
            250000,
            62417,
            "<PERSON>",
            894562,
            200000,
            56000,
            320000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            42400,
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            62410,
            85000,
            "<PERSON>",
            12000,
            74124,
            250000,
            85241,
            75415,
            150000,
            945600,
            56000,
            50000,
            57000,
            72537,
            102457,
            946523,
            54000,
            756200,
            1790000,
            150000,
            78000,
            50000,
            142374,
            95201,
            150000,
            42400,
            50000,
            175000,
            78000,
            84207,
            754015,
            124000,
            52400,
            "<PERSON>",
            142357,
            250000,
            56000,
            72419,
            40000,
            92400,
            12400,
            52000,
            75320,
            52400,
            75869,
            23600
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "In_copyr": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            480500,
            3900000,
            9000000,
            5000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            4000000,
            4200000,
            544523,
            200000,
            250000,
            569000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            480000,
            "<PERSON>",
            321457,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            23000,
            480000,
            56000,
            "<PERSON>",
            3700000,
            70000,
            "<PERSON>",
            95000,
            950000,
            70000,
            54000,
            125000,
            1250000,
            140555,
            3000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            400000,
            555400,
            95000,
            25000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            56000,
            1900000,
            15000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            5000000,
            1984600,
            2700000,
            "<PERSON>",
            125000,
            4000000,
            480000,
            "<PERSON>",
            521476,
            4000000,
            3450000,
            301247,
            756100,
            "<PERSON>",
            550000,
            "<PERSON>",
            2200000,
            521478,
            1457235,
            1500000,
            35642000,
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            480000,
            852475,
            852471,
            "<PERSON>",
            548600,
            964852,
            2100000,
            400000,
            "<PERSON>",
            250000,
            "<PERSON>",
            301247,
            2000000,
            301447,
            "<PERSON>",
            2200000,
            231200,
            520147,
            1454035,
            "<PERSON>",
            480000,
            250000,
            752413,
            3400000,
            "<PERSON>",
            602475,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            780000,
            421357,
            480000,
            952413,
            55500
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "In_award": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            15000000,
            200000,
            55500,
            500000,
            3000000,
            154235,
            550000,
            3500000,
            55500,
            1000555,
            "<PERSON>",
            200050,
            2200000,
            19632547,
            "<PERSON>",
            1200555,
            50500,
            201000,
            95000,
            7000000,
            34600000,
            52225,
            54500,
            70000,
            12000,
            555,
            50225,
            450000000,
            35600000,
            234555,
            25000000,
            98000,
            50000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            36000000,
            7000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            75000000,
            1123475,
            200000,
            38945650,
            "<PERSON>",
            940000,
            97500,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            14235768,
            7500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1023475,
            13652000,
            "<PERSON>",
            120000000,
            2014357,
            "<PERSON>",
            2541376,
            3214569,
            "<PERSON>",
            79582000,
            "<PERSON>",
            554000,
            1750000,
            4752138,
            5231479,
            48562000,
            550005,
            348600,
            34960000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1400000,
            1420000,
            6321487,
            7589631,
            3800000,
            1023475,
            1145000,
            1900000,
            1450000,
            8532147,
            3214569,
            250000,
            200000,
            3500000,
            11369547,
            32600000,
            1580000,
            10235478,
            1245000,
            200000,
            250000,
            250000,
            14235870,
            200000,
            12458789,
            1540000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "In_playerout": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            5550450,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            2000000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            9500000,
            4010000,
            15000000,
            2245550,
            "<PERSON>",
            15000000,
            4000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            5550540,
            "<PERSON>",
            10000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            980000,
            75000,
            5550000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            45000000,
            54000,
            7500000,
            5000,
            "<PERSON>",
            56000,
            "<PERSON>",
            15000000,
            "<AU_TFN>",
            1400000,
            "<PERSON>",
            70000,
            60000000,
            555000,
            70000,
            90000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            65000,
            75000000,
            12367000,
            2000000,
            55000000,
            78956420,
            35000000,
            98400,
            455000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            5550000,
            56000,
            27000000,
            65000000,
            32000000,
            22000000,
            65000450,
            5450000,
            1890000,
            35000000,
            24000000,
            15000000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            20000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            78650000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1470000,
            25000000,
            15000000,
            69750000,
            1500555,
            55684320,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            2400000,
            1890000,
            60000000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            10000000,
            2250000,
            "<PERSON>",
            15000000,
            1230000,
            15000000,
            45000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            5550000,
            14000000,
            35000000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            1230000,
            28000000,
            1400000,
            5550000,
            4550000,
            5550000,
            15000000,
            5550000,
            45000000,
            505000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Ex_player": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            3500555,
            6500000,
            750000,
            2300000,
            46000000,
            34000000,
            20000000,
            13000000,
            20000000,
            9000000,
            2500000,
            9500000,
            4000000,
            8500555,
            "<PERSON>",
            20000000,
            3400000,
            9500000,
            782000,
            8500555,
            95000,
            500000,
            7000000,
            70000,
            2600000,
            55500,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PERSON>",
            95000,
            2000000,
            42000000,
            1240000,
            6500000,
            54000,
            10000000,
            10000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            32000000,
            500000,
            56000,
            1052500,
            45000000,
            2400000,
            80000000,
            31200000,
            6250000,
            9480,
            99000,
            7000000,
            8500555,
            9000,
            3000000,
            1400000,
            5500000,
            2000000,
            286000542,
            8500455,
            "<PERSON>",
            3000000,
            2200000,
            4000000,
            5000000,
            2000000,
            12650000,
            36480000,
            1580000,
            1750000,
            10000000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PERSON>",
            5550000,
            1265000,
            19400000,
            10000000,
            1320000,
            1120000,
            15000000,
            10000000,
            1500000,
            2210000,
            1148500,
            1750000,
            1140000,
            5000000,
            5200000,
            8550455,
            8500555,
            9500000,
            2500000,
            6500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            8000000,
            1748500,
            8500555,
            8500555,
            1500555,
            15000000,
            8500555,
            14000000,
            1500000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Ex_staff": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            5700000,
            1500000,
            750000,
            1500000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            25500000,
            15000055,
            13000000,
            15000000,
            8000000,
            2400000,
            4500065,
            3500000,
            5600000,
            3450000,
            2000000,
            3400000,
            4500065,
            56231,
            5600000,
            56000,
            200000,
            1750000,
            56000,
            4500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            4203000,
            555,
            58000,
            2640000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1500000,
            1450000,
            56000,
            2000000,
            9500010,
            56000,
            "<PERSON>",
            200000,
            70000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            1500000,
            3400000,
            1985600,
            1700000,
            9478,
            200000,
            1500000,
            5600000,
            84000,
            "<PERSON>",
            2000000,
            1250000,
            1500000,
            50000000,
            5700000,
            "<PERSON>",
            2500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            3500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            750000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            1264800,
            1230000,
            6500000,
            2500000,
            5000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            4300000,
            1400000,
            26840000,
            20000000,
            1410000,
            222100,
            1500000,
            2000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1500000,
            142500,
            650000,
            79000,
            2500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            4700000,
            5600000,
            "<PERSON>",
            5000000,
            1700000,
            1140000,
            4500000,
            142500,
            5600000,
            5600000,
            1604000,
            1500000,
            6600000,
            2000000,
            1230400
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Ex_state": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            3000000,
            2500000,
            175000,
            80000,
            55500,
            54005,
            550004,
            300000,
            50000,
            45000,
            60000,
            40000,
            5500,
            64400,
            100000,
            54400,
            60000,
            32188,
            5500,
            56000,
            160000,
            3200000,
            95000,
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            2000000,
            95000,
            75000,
            7500000,
            120000,
            50000,
            2500000,
            52225,
            33000,
            70000,
            75000,
            120000,
            160000,
            54000,
            165000,
            130000,
            140000,
            4000000,
            75000,
            3000000,
            47000,
            "<PERSON>",
            2700000,
            5500,
            4890,
            75000,
            4500000,
            2500000,
            100000,
            500000,
            5500,
            79000,
            200000,
            2000000,
            70000,
            82000,
            1750000,
            50000,
            "<PERSON>",
            68000,
            75000,
            300000,
            70000,
            "<PERSON>",
            55000,
            96400,
            "<PERSON>",
            175000,
            "<PERSON>",
            189000,
            75000,
            80000,
            1500000,
            100000,
            5980,
            1500000,
            69000,
            40000,
            82000,
            "<PERSON>",
            5500,
            "<PERSON>",
            40000,
            2000000,
            58900,
            60000,
            600100,
            5500,
            581200,
            "<PERSON>",
            120000,
            75000,
            35000,
            65400
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Ex_playerin": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            180000,
            "<PERSON>",
            25000000,
            3555,
            6400000,
            9000000,
            12000000,
            2500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            2350000,
            400000,
            980000,
            180000,
            1205000,
            25000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            400000,
            33154,
            180000,
            80000,
            2000000,
            100000000,
            9000,
            6400000,
            56000,
            16000000,
            56000,
            50000,
            190000000,
            78500000,
            "<PERSON>",
            75000000,
            54000,
            "<PERSON>",
            572000,
            56000,
            100000000,
            2000000,
            80000,
            54692000,
            75060000,
            2000000,
            1500000,
            55640000,
            25000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            160000,
            50000000,
            180000,
            70000,
            15000000,
            157000000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            20000000,
            75000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            2000000,
            12500000,
            7500000,
            5000000,
            20000000,
            1325000,
            89450000,
            1320000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            20000000,
            54680000,
            590000,
            46500000,
            15096000,
            "<PERSON>",
            2450000,
            198000,
            10000000,
            25000000,
            17000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1840000,
            15000000,
            1560000,
            15000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            550000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1220000,
            3500000,
            50000000,
            1470000,
            1500000,
            1840000,
            180000,
            180000,
            180000,
            2500000,
            180000,
            20000000,
            4200000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Ex_misscell": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1200,
            2000000,
            500000,
            23000,
            20000,
            55000,
            38500,
            24500,
            31500,
            20000,
            14555,
            25400,
            54005,
            100,
            68500,
            75000,
            65500,
            25400,
            731311,
            4003,
            98000,
            5555,
            2500000,
            100000,
            20000,
            58000,
            4500000,
            98000,
            55500,
            150000,
            480000,
            8400,
            750000,
            80000,
            64000,
            4200,
            95000,
            "<PERSON>",
            5555,
            75000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            12000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            75000,
            250000,
            95000,
            "<PERSON>",
            300000,
            1070,
            9000,
            25000,
            16000000,
            "<PERSON>",
            20000,
            "<PERSON>",
            9070,
            50000,
            35000,
            850000,
            50000,
            100000,
            2000000,
            10000,
            75600,
            78000,
            741000,
            75000,
            75000,
            136500,
            60000,
            256100,
            125600,
            20000,
            57000,
            48500,
            50000,
            100000,
            2000000,
            22000,
            14000,
            2000000,
            76200,
            45000,
            "<PERSON>",
            4171,
            8970,
            20000,
            75000,
            5000000,
            23000,
            65000,
            16000,
            1720,
            3540,
            4070,
            91000,
            1100,
            150000,
            5000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "contact": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Brentford Football Club Griffin Park Braemar Road Brentford TW8 0NT",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Kiyan Prince Foundation Stadium South Africa RoadLondonW12 7PJ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Lincoln City Football Club LNER Stadium Lincoln Lincolnshire LN5 8LD",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Newcastle upon Tyne NE1 4ST",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Portsmouth Football Club Fratton Park Frogmore Road Portsmouth PO4 8RA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Stevenage Football Club The Lamex Stadium Broadhall Way StevenageHerts SG2 8RH",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Clubname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Carlisle United",
            "Huddersfield Town",
            "Plymouth Argyle",
            "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
            "West Bromwich Albion",
            "Peterborough United",
            "Cambridge United",
            "Wycombe Wanderers",
            "West Ham United",
            "AFC Wimbledon",
            "Brighton & Hove Albion",
            "Liverpool FC",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Real Madrid CF",
            "Walsall",
            "Wigan Athletic",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Blackpool",
            "Grimsby Town",
            "Oldham Athletic",
            "Brentford",
            "Leyton Orient",
            "Bolton Wanderers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Norwich City FC",
            "Chelsea",
            "Cheltenham Town",
            "Chesterfield",
            "Morecambe",
            "Swindon Town",
            "Fulham",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Preston North End",
            "Leeds United",
            "Everton",
            "Blackburn Rovers",
            "Bristol Rovers",
            "Chelsea",
            "Scunthorpe United",
            "Oxford United",
            "Crewe Alexandra",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Arsenal",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Sheffield Wednesday",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "Colchester United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Doncaster Rovers",
            "Queens Park Rangers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Tottenham Hotspur FC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Torquay United",
            "Shrewsbury Town",
            "Newcastle United",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Burton Albion",
            "Ipswich Town F.C.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Tranmere Rovers",
            "Northampton Town",
            "Wrexham",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Gillingham",
            "Middlesbrough",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Southend United",
            "Derby County",
            "Crystal Palace",
            "Sheffield United",
            "Coventry City",
            "Southampton FC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Sunderland",
            "Milton Keynes Dons",
            "<PERSON>",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Rotherham United",
            "Woking",
            "Forest Green Rovers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Crawley Town",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Charlton Athletic",
            "Port Vale",
            "Watford",
            "Aston villa",
            "Bournemouth",
            "Maidenhead United",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Clubname"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "club",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "contract": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Number": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Player_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            15,
            24,
            16,
            6,
            20,
            23,
            5,
            8,
            14,
            4,
            7,
            17,
            10,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            2,
            1,
            18,
            9,
            19,
            3,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            22,
            21,
            30,
            28,
            29,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            65,
            64,
            63,
            62,
            61,
            60,
            59,
            58,
            57,
            56,
            55,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            75,
            74,
            73,
            72,
            71,
            70,
            69,
            68,
            67,
            66,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            94,
            93,
            92,
            91,
            90,
            89,
            88,
            87,
            86,
            85,
            84,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Clubname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Start_date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2017-04-08",
            "2019-06-04",
            "2019-04-10",
            "2019-04-10",
            "2019-07-14",
            "2018-04-26",
            "2016-05-27",
            "2015-04-15",
            "2019-04-24",
            "2019-04-24",
            "2019-04-27",
            "2017-05-18",
            "2019-05-14",
            "2019-04-10",
            "2016-03-18",
            "2018-06-19",
            "2017-04-03",
            "2016-04-01",
            "2019-04-23",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2019-04-09",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2018-06-30",
            "2019-08-15",
            "2020-04-26",
            "2020-03-15",
            "2020-04-15",
            "2020-05-20",
            "2015-04-11",
            "2015-04-11",
            "2018-03-15",
            "2020-02-06",
            "2020-02-06",
            "2019-09-04",
            "2017-03-18",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2017-03-18",
            "2018-07-16",
            "2020-02-06",
            "2015-04-11",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2017-03-18",
            "2018-07-19",
            "2018-03-15",
            "2019-08-16",
            "2018-10-10",
            "2018-10-10",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2020-06-20",
            "2020-06-20",
            "2020-06-20",
            "2020-06-20",
            "2020-07-18",
            "2020-07-20",
            "2020-08-20",
            "2020-08-20",
            "2020-08-21",
            "2020-08-21",
            "2020-09-03",
            "2020-09-03",
            "2020-09-03",
            "2020-09-05",
            "2020-09-05",
            "2020-10-18",
            "2020-07-20",
            "2020-08-20",
            "2020-10-20",
            "2020-08-21",
            "2020-08-21",
            "2020-09-20",
            "2020-11-20",
            "2020-09-22",
            "2020-08-21",
            "2020-11-20",
            "2020-12-18",
            "2020-12-18",
            "2019-06-25",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-06-25",
            "2019-04-15",
            "2018-05-12",
            "2019-02-16",
            "2020-03-25",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-02-25",
            "2019-03-25",
            "2020-01-01",
            "2020-05-08",
            "2020-06-19",
            "2017-03-18",
            "2020-05-13",
            "2020-05-13"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Expire_date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2023-04-08",
            "2023-06-04",
            "2025-04-10",
            "2025-04-10",
            "2024-07-14",
            "2023-04-26",
            "2022-05-27",
            "2020-04-15",
            "2023-04-24",
            "2024-04-24",
            "2024-04-27",
            "2020-05-18",
            "2025-05-14",
            "2021-04-10",
            "2021-03-18",
            "2023-06-19",
            "2022-04-03",
            "2020-04-01",
            "2021-04-23",
            "2024-04-15",
            "2024-04-15",
            "2020-04-15",
            "2021-04-09",
            "2021-04-15",
            "2021-04-15",
            "2020-06-30",
            "2020-08-15",
            "2022-04-26",
            "2025-04-15",
            "2022-04-15",
            "2024-05-20",
            "2021-04-11",
            "2021-04-11",
            "2022-03-18",
            "2022-03-18",
            "2022-02-06",
            "2021-09-04",
            "2021-03-18",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2021-03-18",
            "2020-07-16",
            "2022-02-06",
            "2021-04-11",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2021-03-18",
            "2020-07-19",
            "2022-03-15",
            "2023-08-16",
            "2020-10-10",
            "2020-10-10",
            "2025-04-15",
            "2022-04-15",
            "2022-06-20",
            "2022-06-20",
            "2022-06-20",
            "2022-06-20",
            "2022-07-18",
            "2023-07-20",
            "2024-08-20",
            "2025-08-20",
            "2025-08-21",
            "2025-08-21",
            "2023-09-03",
            "2021-09-03",
            "2021-09-03",
            "2022-09-05",
            "2022-09-05",
            "2022-10-18",
            "2023-10-18",
            "2024-10-19",
            "2023-10-20",
            "2023-08-21",
            "2023-08-21",
            "2021-09-20",
            "2022-11-20",
            "2023-09-22",
            "2021-08-21",
            "2021-11-20",
            "2021-12-18",
            "2021-12-18",
            "2025-06-25",
            "2021-04-15",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2025-06-25",
            "2021-04-15",
            "2022-05-12",
            "2021-02-16",
            "2022-03-25",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2021-02-25",
            "2022-03-25",
            "2022-01-01",
            "2022-06-08",
            "2025-06-19",
            "2021-03-18",
            "2025-05-13",
            "2025-05-13"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Salary(Euro)": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            16683333,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            6300000,
            "<PERSON>",
            5200000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            11967000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            624000,
            160000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            163000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            17600000,
            18200000,
            "<PERSON>",
            11866666,
            "<PERSON>",
            9792000,
            "<PERSON>",
            479030,
            "<PERSON>",
            760000,
            547832,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            699000,
            195500,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            200000,
            540705,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            358600,
            16000000,
            9000000,
            7600000,
            7600000,
            7500000,
            6000000,
            5600000,
            4600000,
            5600000,
            2600000,
            3600000,
            6000000,
            4600000,
            2600000,
            2600000,
            1720000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1500000,
            1460000,
            1400000,
            760000,
            960000,
            "<PERSON>",
            650000,
            620000,
            650000,
            720000,
            760000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            2800000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1624000,
            2800000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            884000,
            1164000,
            624000,
            1624000,
            "<PERSON>",
            924000,
            1604000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1250000,
            880000,
            "<PERSON>",
            2800000,
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Clubname"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "club",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "eventdate": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Edate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-04-27",
            "2020-04-29",
            "2020-05-01",
            "2020-05-03",
            "2020-05-04",
            "2020-05-03",
            "2020-05-04",
            "2020-05-10",
            "2020-05-15",
            "2020-05-16",
            "2020-06-05",
            "2020-06-07",
            "2020-06-10",
            "2020-06-17",
            "2020-07-14",
            "2020-07-26",
            "2020-07-30",
            "2020-07-24",
            "2020-08-07",
            "2020-08-09",
            "2020-08-11",
            "2020-08-13",
            "2020-09-08",
            "2020-09-20",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-09",
            "2020-05-09",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-17",
            "2020-05-20",
            "2020-05-20",
            "2020-05-20",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-24",
            "2020-05-21",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-31",
            "2020-05-31",
            "2020-05-31",
            "2020-05-31",
            "2020-05-31",
            "2020-05-06",
            "2020-05-06",
            "2020-05-06",
            "2020-05-06",
            "2020-05-06",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-02",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-07",
            "2020-05-09",
            "2020-05-09",
            "2020-05-09",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-17",
            "2020-05-20",
            "2020-05-14",
            "2020-05-17",
            "2020-05-20",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-23",
            "2020-05-24",
            "2020-05-24",
            "2020-05-24",
            "2020-05-24",
            "2020-05-24",
            "2020-05-30",
            "2020-05-30",
            "2020-05-30",
            "2020-05-30",
            "2020-05-30",
            "2020-05-30",
            "2020-04-27",
            "2020-06-13",
            "2020-05-04"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Clubname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Liverpool FC",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Chelsea",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Manchester United",
            "Arsenal",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Tottenham Hotspur FC",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Liverpool FC",
            "Newcastle United",
            "Everton",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "Norwich City FC",
            "Aston villa",
            "Sheffield United",
            "Juventus F.C.",
            "Liverpool FC",
            "FC Barcelona",
            "Bournemouth",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Preston North End",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bristol Rovers",
            "Burton Albion",
            "Doncaster Rovers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Gillingham",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Blackburn Rovers",
            "Blackpool",
            "Bolton Wanderers",
            "Bournemouth",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Brighton & Hove Albion",
            "BurnleyCardiff City",
            "Brentford",
            "Charlton Athletic",
            "Coventry City",
            "Crystal Palace",
            "Derby County",
            "Fulham",
            "Crystal Palace",
            "Derby County",
            "Fulham",
            "Oldham Athletic",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Queens Park Rangers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Sheffield Wednesday",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Sunderland",
            "Chesterfield",
            "Swindon Town",
            "Watford",
            "West Bromwich Albion",
            "West Ham United",
            "Wigan Athletic",
            "AFC Wimbledon",
            "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
            "Aston villa",
            "Blackburn Rovers",
            "Cheltenham Town"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "vita": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "All players practice in the prepared stadium",
            "UEFA CHAMPION LEAGUE\r\nA.C. MILAN VS MANCHESTER CITY\r\nAT 9.00 P.M.",
            "All players take the long vacation",
            "vs Realmadrid",
            "vs Spurs",
            "Friendly Match vs Buriram United",
            "vs Dundee United FC",
            "Meet and greet fanclub",
            "Friendly Match Muangthong United",
            "vs Manchester United",
            "vs Torquay United",
            "Meet and greet fanclub",
            "vs West Ham",
            "vs Arsenal",
            "New kit lauch",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "meet and greet fanclub",
            "Friendly Match vs FC seoul",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Dundee United FC",
            "Friendly Match Eagle Friend Police",
            "Meet and greet fanclub",
            "vs Liverpool FC ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "vs Espanyol",
            "vs Celta Vigo",
            "vs Crystal Palace",
            "vs AFC Bournemouth",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Atlético Madrid ",
            "vs Real Madrid",
            "vs Arsenal",
            "Manchester United",
            "<PERSON>",
            "vs Athletic Bilbao",
            "vs West Ham United",
            "vs Burnley",
            "vs Real Sociedad",
            "<PERSON>",
            "vs Everton",
            "vs Newcastle United",
            "vs AC Milan",
            "VS Aston Villa",
            "vs Norwich City FC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Parma",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Real Betis",
            "vs Liverpool Fc",
            "vs Fulham",
            "vs Plymouth Argyle",
            "vs Northampton Town",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Morecambe",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Macclesfield Town",
            "vs Leyton Orient",
            "vs Grimsby Town",
            "vs Forest Green Rovers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Crewe Alexandra",
            "vs Crawley Town",
            "vs Derby County",
            "vs Crystal Palace",
            "vs Crystal Palace",
            "vs Coventry City",
            "vs Brentford",
            "vs BurnleyCardiff City",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Atlético Madrid",
            "vs Bournemouth",
            "vs Bolton Wanderers",
            "vs Blackpool",
            "vs Blackburn Rovers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Barnsley",
            "vs Blackburn Rovers",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Barnsley",
            "<PERSON>",
            "vs Parma",
            "vs Manchester United",
            "vs Real Betis",
            "vs Woking",
            "<PERSON>",
            "vs Maidenhead United",
            "vs Wrexham",
            "vs Torquay United",
            "vs Walsall",
            "vs Swindon Town",
            "vs Stevenage",
            "vs Scunthorpe United",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "vs Port Vale",
            "vs Espanyol",
            "vs Real Madrid",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Clubname"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "club",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Clubname"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "formation": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Clubname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Formation": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "4-3-3",
            "4-5-1",
            "4-4-2",
            "3-4-3",
            "4-2-3-1",
            "3-5-2",
            "4-1-4-1",
            "5-4-1",
            "4-1-2-1-2",
            "4-2-4",
            "4-3-2-1",
            "3-3-1-3",
            "3-3-3-1",
            "3-6-1",
            "1-6-3",
            "3-4-1-2",
            "2-3-5",
            "2-3-2-3",
            "2-5-3",
            "1-4-3-2",
            "4-2-2-2",
            "1-4-2-3",
            "4-3-1-2",
            "4-6-0",
            "4-4-1-1",
            "3-4-2-1",
            "5-3-2",
            "3-3-4"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Clubname"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "club",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Clubname"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "player": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Aymeric Laporte",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dele Alli",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jamaal Lascelles",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Bdate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1983-04-14",
            "1993-08-17",
            "1985-09-03",
            "1990-05-28",
            "1994-05-28",
            "1994-05-27",
            "1994-07-17",
            "1988-02-12",
            "1996-12-15",
            "1994-05-27",
            "2001-01-09",
            "2001-01-09",
            "2001-10-10",
            "1990-10-24",
            "1991-06-28",
            "1994-08-10",
            "1986-01-08",
            "1985-05-04",
            "2000-05-28",
            "1996-06-22",
            "2001-05-26",
            "2001-10-17",
            "1991-02-21",
            "1994-12-08",
            "1998-06-02",
            "1996-01-11",
            "1997-04-03",
            "1987-06-24",
            "1993-11-15",
            "1985-05-02",
            "1992-06-15",
            "1998-10-07",
            "1991-07-08",
            "1987-02-22",
            "1989-09-22",
            "1997-09-10",
            "1993-07-28",
            "1992-07-08",
            "1989-03-02",
            "1992-12-24",
            "1996-04-11",
            "1994-06-22",
            "1987-09-07",
            "1999-01-14",
            "1987-05-08",
            "1997-01-09",
            "1989-10-23",
            "1996-02-22",
            "1993-04-15",
            "1993-02-15",
            "1987-01-11",
            "1996-11-23",
            "1997-12-09",
            "1997-05-07",
            "1996-10-03",
            "1986-11-05",
            "1988-01-03",
            "1993-10-06",
            "1996-05-23",
            "1984-10-02",
            "1993-06-22",
            "1986-04-07",
            "1966-12-21",
            "1984-01-21",
            "1990-03-06",
            "1998-02-23",
            "1994-12-21",
            "1992-06-23",
            "1996-12-16",
            "1997-10-01",
            "1991-07-22",
            "1994-05-14",
            "1989-11-18",
            "1996-06-08",
            "1989-03-03",
            "1997-03-04",
            "1999-11-04",
            "1992-10-15",
            "1988-11-11",
            "1995-09-23",
            "1989-01-15",
            "1990-10-08",
            "1986-01-30",
            "1990-07-02",
            "1994-03-30",
            "1991-09-26",
            "1991-05-20",
            "1991-12-20",
            "1989-09-26",
            "1993-11-11",
            "1989-02-21",
            "1993-07-09",
            "1994-08-02",
            "1994-05-05",
            "1989-10-24",
            "2000-03-21",
            "1995-03-22",
            "1997-10-30",
            "1992-02-27",
            "1989-09-10"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "National": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Chilean",
            "Brazilian",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "French",
            "French",
            "Argentine",
            "Ukrainian",
            " Portuguese",
            "Spanish",
            "English",
            "Senegalese",
            "German",
            "Belgian",
            "Portuguese",
            "Spanish",
            "Brazilian",
            "English",
            "Spanish",
            "Spanish",
            "English",
            "Algerian",
            "English",
            "Argentine",
            "German",
            "Brazilian",
            "Argentine",
            "Argentine",
            "Portuguese",
            "Egyptian",
            "English",
            "Dutch",
            "Argentine",
            "English",
            "Welsh",
            "English",
            "South Korean",
            "Belgian",
            "<PERSON>",
            "English",
            "French",
            "Scottish",
            "English",
            "English",
            "French",
            "Ukrainian",
            "Spanish",
            "Brazilian",
            "Argentine",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "Belgian",
            "Nigerian",
            "Danish",
            "Irish",
            "Portuguese",
            "Turkish",
            "Swiss",
            "Welsh",
            "English",
            "English",
            "Nigerain",
            "English",
            "English",
            " A Ghanaian",
            "French",
            "Nigerian",
            "English",
            "English",
            "Belgian",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "Belgian",
            "English",
            "Welsh",
            "Slovak",
            "English",
            "Irish",
            "English",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Welsh",
            "French",
            "Swiss",
            "Irish",
            "English",
            "Argentine",
            "American",
            "Swedish",
            "Spainisn",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "English",
            "Scots"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "SN": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            31,
            33,
            2,
            5,
            14,
            22,
            30,
            11,
            27,
            50,
            72,
            88,
            8,
            17,
            20,
            21,
            25,
            47,
            16,
            66,
            69,
            26,
            7,
            10,
            19,
            9,
            99,
            98,
            97,
            18,
            65,
            4,
            23,
            6,
            38,
            32,
            3,
            12,
            24,
            13,
            15,
            28,
            34,
            37,
            35,
            41,
            76,
            54,
            68,
            92,
            29,
            36,
            39,
            40,
            49,
            55,
            43,
            77,
            41,
            96,
            46,
            59,
            67,
            79,
            89,
            95,
            42,
            44,
            45,
            51,
            60,
            70,
            80,
            90,
            58,
            64,
            78,
            87,
            94,
            52,
            53,
            56,
            57,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            71,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            86,
            84,
            85,
            93,
            91,
            11
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Position": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "GK",
            "GK",
            "GK",
            "RB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "LB",
            "RB",
            "RB",
            "LB",
            "CB",
            "CM",
            "CAM",
            "RM",
            "CM",
            "CDM",
            "RM",
            "CM",
            "CM",
            "CM",
            "RW",
            "LW",
            "ST",
            "RW",
            "LW",
            "RW",
            "CAM",
            "LW",
            "RW",
            "RB",
            "CB\t",
            "GK",
            "CB",
            "RW",
            "ST",
            "LW",
            "CB",
            "RB",
            "CAM",
            "ST",
            "RW",
            "CB",
            "CM",
            "CB",
            "ST",
            "CF",
            "LW",
            "CM",
            "ST",
            "CM",
            "LM",
            "CM",
            "ST",
            "GK",
            "CB",
            "RB",
            "CB",
            "GK",
            "GK",
            "LB",
            "LB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "RB",
            "CAM",
            "CAM",
            "CAM",
            "CAM",
            "CM",
            "CM",
            "RM",
            "LW",
            "GK",
            "GK",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "RB",
            "RB",
            "GK",
            "GK",
            "GK",
            "LB",
            "LB",
            "LB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "CB",
            "RB",
            "RB",
            "RB",
            "CAM",
            "CAM",
            "CAM",
            "CM",
            "CM",
            "RM"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "IsCaptian": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N",
            "N"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Clubname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Liverpool FC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "substitute": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "N",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "N",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y",
            "Y"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "vita": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "The 29-year-old has made the right-back slot his own and won six trophies in his first two seasons.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "He made 16 appearances in total and registered five assists as City lifted the Premier League, FA Cup, Carabao Cup and Community shield.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "A left-sided attacking midfielder, he was immediately sent on loan to PSV Eindhoven, where, by his own admission, he didn’t play as much as he would have liked.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Always cool, calm and collected, he has so far passed every test with flying colours - as he proved in his senior debut where he again looked mature beyond his years.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "An all-action full-back, Alpha made the move to City from Real Mallorca in 2017 and has gone from strength to strength ever since.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "A Belgian professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Premier League club Manchester City and the Belgian national team. Recognised for his passing, dribbling, tackling and shooting ability, lead him to one of the best in the world.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "A Spanish football midfielder who currently plays for Manchester City.",
            "An English professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Manchester City.",
            "A professional footballer who plays as a winger for Premier League club Manchester City and captains the Algerian national team.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "An Argentine professional footballer who plays as a striker for English Premier League club Manchester City and the Argentine national team. He is widely considered as one of the best players of his generation.",
            "He made his professional debut for Schalke 04 in 2014 and transferred to Manchester City in 2016 for an initial £37 million fee. He was voted PFA Young Player of the Year in 2017–18 after helping City win the Premier League and EFL Cup.",
            "He was voted the best newcomer of the 2015 Campeonato Brasileiro Série A, a year in which he also helped his team win the Copa do Brasil. The following year he was named the player of the season as Palmeiras won their ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "A Portuguese professional footballer who plays as a forward for Serie A club Juventus Often considered the best player in the world and widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "An English footballer who played as a central midfielder and is captain of West Ham United. He has played almost all his youth and first team football for West Ham apart from two short loan spells",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "A Spanish professional footballer who played for English club West Ham United mainly as an attacking midfielder.He amassed La Liga totals of 129 matches and 12 goals during four seasons, with Malaga and Villarreal. In 2019, he signed with West Ham United.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "He began his career at Anderlecht, where he made 185 official appearances and scored 35 goals across four seasons. He won the league title twice and in 2017 was chosen as the Belgian Professional Footballer of the Year.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " First senior professional team was the Turkish second division Altinordu.",
            "He started his professional career at Grasshopper Club Zurich in 2004, then moved to FC Thun a year later.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "He began his senior career as a teenager at Wiener Neustadt before signing his first professional contract at 17 with SV Mattersburg.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "He was a youth product of Ipswich Town but was not offered a professional contract and thus signed for Grimsby Town in 2006. ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "an English professional footballer who plays for Leicester City. His regular position is in midfield, but he can play in defence when required. ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "an English professional footballer who plays as a winger for Premier League club Leicester City.He joined Aston Villa at the age of eight.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "an English professional footballer who plays as a goalkeeper for Swansea City, on loan from Newcastle United.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "A Dutch professional footballer who plays as a centre back for Championship club Swansea City. .",
            "An English professional footballer who plays as a right back for Championship club Swansea City..",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "A Dutch professional footballer who plays as a left wing-back or left-back for Premier League club Newcastle United, on loan from Eintracht Frankfurt.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            " an English professional footballer who plays as a centre-back for Premier League club Newcastle United, where he is captain.",
            "He began his career at Estudiantes de La Plata, where he reached the final of the Copa Sudamericana and won the Copa Libertadores, before moving to Napoli in 2011 .",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "He began his career at Charlton Athletic, becoming their youngest-ever player at 16 years and 59 days old.In 2010, he moved to Liverpool for an initial ?1.7 million, spending a brief loan at Blackpool.",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Clubname"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "club",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "result": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Player_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
