{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/Nu-shrat/Smart__Medicare/blob/7e133269c0f7ee12fba4251159ea821899d259a7/resources/smart_medicare.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "address": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "+88082923211",
            "+880621011",
            "+880685447",
            "<AU_ACN>",
            "+880313582",
            "+880650554",
            "+880686527",
            "+880764459",
            "+880921790",
            "+880652867"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mobile_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "latitude": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "53.85689",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "75.34928",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "64.59571",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "73.36258",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "longitude": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "20.36600",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "83.35069",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "117.47151"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "registration_no"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "amenity": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "atm": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "baby_corner": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cafeteria": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "gift_shop": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "locker": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "parking": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "pharmacy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "prayer_area": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "wheelchair": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "wifi": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "registration_no"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "blood_analytical_service": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "antibody_analysis": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cbc": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "creatinine_analysis": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "crp": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "esr": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "fobt": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "hematocrit": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "kidney_function_analysis": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "lipid_profile": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "liver_function_analysis": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "rf": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "serum_analysis": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "sr": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "registration_no"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "booking": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "06fhm22ue8",
            "0kt66bxim1",
            "0x1pvj475y",
            "2662b2tphq",
            "27e39k7e6w",
            "286x6m73u1",
            "2e66se97zx",
            "2rh1o2y7nq",
            "3360ao2h0y",
            "35f29ttm51",
            "37010mjsq3",
            "37q37v5t21",
            "3865ru5g84",
            "40th24fpwd",
            "56lx6183um",
            "5wur4m4420",
            "627gndp34v",
            "652i2441d6",
            "65ye9uvyo6",
            "6sgqd1113p",
            "73uhj9ap25",
            "7p82ol1lbj",
            "7s2278v76i",
            "7sy7s29w8a",
            "8388ro4d22",
            "bp2jq3j76y",
            "cp8c776bv3",
            "d218274k38",
            "em76j1fo7a",
            "fxhq31msoo",
            "g84i52yil1",
            "h63i565e3f",
            "i551t23j62",
            "i8toe9i2mf",
            "irc326675x",
            "j225o7gym4",
            "jvvab6pbk8",
            "oa6e6b7m26",
            "q5b53u7bgb",
            "qml2w3hg47",
            "r53r4d7u6s",
            "r8zoaksz52",
            "riyik7b48g",
            "sfcfp342qq",
            "tnb32c4gyr",
            "<MEDICAL_LICENSE>",
            "v30f74i036",
            "v5idu26zbe",
            "w8k36lpm2s",
            "x5c7b429n2"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "booked_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2017-08-12 13:22:04",
            "2015-03-28 20:38:01",
            "2018-03-16 16:59:34",
            "2015-01-12 19:55:51",
            "2016-01-12 13:40:01",
            "2020-08-10 13:37:27",
            "2015-12-02 17:44:44",
            "2015-02-26 01:07:31",
            "2015-08-30 06:53:59",
            "2015-01-15 10:56:09",
            "2019-05-03 16:00:07",
            "2018-05-02 08:04:44",
            "2020-09-08 22:03:16",
            "2021-01-05 21:59:58",
            "2015-04-12 10:26:37",
            "2019-11-24 06:55:42",
            "2019-05-06 03:10:07",
            "2018-08-24 17:45:11",
            "2017-04-15 04:24:00",
            "2017-06-27 22:44:37",
            "2016-01-18 19:15:16",
            "2017-06-05 19:58:13",
            "2021-05-15 05:38:36",
            "2021-03-26 19:21:19",
            "2021-03-02 11:53:21",
            "2020-12-29 16:11:49",
            "2017-12-18 01:48:04",
            "2016-12-07 15:54:51",
            "2015-10-06 12:50:03",
            "2017-03-10 14:26:27",
            "2018-06-11 08:48:18",
            "2020-01-05 19:34:44",
            "2016-01-02 22:16:01",
            "2019-09-05 08:50:07",
            "2017-09-06 05:38:41",
            "2018-11-03 03:10:56",
            "2021-05-05 11:54:43",
            "2020-01-27 02:50:13",
            "2021-03-09 04:28:14",
            "2019-07-29 09:43:00",
            "2020-10-14 11:57:24",
            "2017-09-12 14:01:14",
            "2016-01-19 09:00:49",
            "2019-02-08 18:43:12",
            "2016-05-14 02:18:48",
            "2018-07-20 03:07:21",
            "2015-01-12 09:58:18",
            "2019-10-23 18:44:52",
            "2020-04-19 12:25:13",
            "2019-08-22 14:15:06"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mobile_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "sex": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "T",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "T",
            "T",
            "S",
            "M",
            "M",
            "S",
            "F",
            "M",
            "T",
            "F",
            "S",
            "M",
            "S",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "S",
            "M",
            "M",
            "S",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "S",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "S",
            "T",
            "M",
            "S",
            "S",
            "S",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "bed_type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "HDU",
            "<PERSON>",
            "ICU",
            "Cabin",
            "Ward",
            "HFNCU",
            "HFNCU",
            "Ward",
            "Emergency",
            "Ward",
            "Extra",
            "HDU",
            "HDU",
            "Emergency",
            "Ward",
            "COVID",
            "Extra",
            "HDU",
            "Extra",
            "HFNCU",
            "ICU",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "HFNCU",
            "Ward",
            "ICU",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cabin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "ICU",
            "Cabin",
            "Emergency",
            "ICU",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Emergency",
            "Ward",
            "ICU",
            "HFNCU",
            "Ward",
            "ICU",
            "Ward",
            "Emergency",
            "HFNCU",
            "Cabin",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "ICU",
            "ICU",
            "ICU",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "booked_for": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Brother",
            null,
            "Sister",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brother",
            "Relative",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Father",
            "Relative",
            "Relative",
            "Brother",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Relative",
            "Relative",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "Brother",
            "Father",
            null,
            "Brother",
            "Brother",
            "Sister",
            "Brother",
            "Father",
            "Relative",
            "Father",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Relative",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Relative",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Relative",
            "Brother",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brother",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "Relative",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brother",
            null,
            "Relative",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brother",
            "Father",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cancelled_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "2018-12-06 19:14:20",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "2015-09-20 12:39:44",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "2015-10-17 23:59:04",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "2017-11-26 10:29:31",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Served",
            "Served",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Served",
            "Booked",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Booked",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "Served",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Booked",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Booked",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "Booked",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Served",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "remarks": {
          "TYPE": "tinytext",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "last_updated": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2015-10-13 19:09:35",
            "2017-05-25 02:42:09",
            "2017-02-14 04:07:12",
            "2018-05-07 06:56:42",
            "2017-01-28 22:46:42",
            "2015-06-25 08:06:28",
            "2016-12-03 05:01:28",
            "2019-06-18 23:39:06",
            "2019-04-16 07:10:29",
            "2015-04-06 02:58:07",
            "2020-06-17 12:54:29",
            "2017-06-08 14:33:43",
            "2015-04-04 19:58:43",
            "2018-02-13 20:41:51",
            "2019-09-03 20:33:47",
            "2016-10-28 08:33:30",
            "2020-12-14 21:10:10",
            "2020-11-21 09:26:13",
            "2018-12-15 19:28:25",
            "2016-02-05 02:10:09",
            "2020-06-12 00:55:49",
            "2017-02-10 06:24:13",
            "2016-02-19 01:56:40",
            "2017-02-17 12:00:17",
            "2020-06-22 00:41:48",
            "2016-06-05 19:14:26",
            "2015-02-18 05:46:36",
            "2016-01-27 15:44:54",
            "2018-03-10 10:15:52",
            "2015-02-27 14:42:19",
            "2016-07-30 07:40:46",
            "2018-09-12 15:59:58",
            "2018-04-25 19:43:32",
            "2016-09-18 14:17:21",
            "2016-04-13 20:29:39",
            "2019-03-27 19:36:34",
            "2017-08-10 19:52:55",
            "2018-08-22 22:06:44",
            "2019-01-08 09:48:25",
            "2020-07-10 01:05:51",
            "2016-10-07 15:08:32",
            "2017-07-25 11:52:52",
            "2017-08-19 16:03:50",
            "2016-09-01 15:55:39",
            "2018-10-11 14:42:13",
            "2019-04-26 19:47:52",
            "2019-12-20 11:56:31",
            "2019-05-20 15:45:48",
            "2019-04-13 01:53:08",
            "2020-02-24 23:45:10"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "capacity": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "total_capacity": {
          "TYPE": "MediumInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            125860,
            31711,
            200,
            13438,
            5136,
            31579,
            31911,
            30798,
            23949,
            6806
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ward": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            26111,
            30249,
            7476,
            null,
            5020,
            null,
            13720,
            24352,
            9613,
            28006
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "special_ward": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            30351,
            2179,
            26580,
            2199,
            17556,
            28340,
            8038,
            29828,
            18429,
            18846
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cabin": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            53,
            102,
            19,
            118,
            44,
            54,
            110,
            0,
            116,
            36
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "vip_cabin": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            44,
            28,
            63,
            45,
            94,
            49,
            28,
            23,
            106
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "icu": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            18,
            90,
            2,
            100,
            56,
            102,
            97,
            72,
            47,
            26
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ccu": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            88,
            122,
            109,
            null,
            76,
            null,
            108,
            119,
            82,
            63
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "hdu": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            23796,
            14808,
            null,
            null,
            22411,
            14826,
            12698,
            20481,
            32234,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "hfncu": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            25234,
            3379,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            8281,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "emergency": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            8524,
            29239,
            9413,
            1940,
            21551,
            1397,
            29632,
            14438,
            14603,
            12064
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "covid": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            9655,
            null,
            14247,
            20627,
            null,
            32165,
            23477,
            29887,
            23418,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "extra": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            27265,
            5621,
            22785,
            15761,
            15613,
            29796,
            1329,
            24653,
            1960,
            20294
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "registration_no"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "diagnostic_imaging_service": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "angiocardiography": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "angiography": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cta": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ct": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "coloscopy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cystoscopy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "echocardiography": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "endoscopy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "fluoroscopy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mra": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mri": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mrs": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mammography": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "pet": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            null,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "pet_ct": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "spect": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ultrasound": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "x_ray": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "registration_no"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "doctor": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "1218274338",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2662027526",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2868647371",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "3880066048",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "5061607426",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Clarissa Mills",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "designation": {
          "TYPE": "tinytext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "MBBS  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Gastrology, ",
            "Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, MSc.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Pediatrics, Phd.  Medicine, ",
            "Phd.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Anesthesiology, MBBS  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Neurology, Phd.  Gastrology, ",
            "MBBS  Dermatology, Phd.  Neurology, ",
            "Phd.  Dermatology, MBBS  Dermatology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Immunology, ",
            "MSc.  Neurology, MSc.  Gastrology, MSc.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Neurology, Phd.  Immunology, ",
            "MBBS  Immunology, Phd.  Medicine, Phd.  Gastrology, ",
            "Phd.  Medicine, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Immunology, MSc.  Immunology, ",
            "Phd.  Gastrology, MSc.  Gastrology, Phd.  Pediatrics, ",
            "MSc.  Gastrology, MBBS  Gastrology, ",
            "Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Medicine, ",
            "MBBS  Gastrology, MSc.  Immunology, Phd.  Pediatrics, MSc.  Gastrology, Phd.  Psychology, ",
            "Phd.  Dermatology, MBBS  Dermatology, MBBS  Immunology, ",
            "Phd.  Medicine, MBBS  Immunology, MSc.  Anesthesiology, ",
            "Phd.  Immunology, MSc.  Dermatology, ",
            "MSc.  Immunology, MBBS  Dermatology, Phd.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Immunology, ",
            "MBBS  Medicine, MBBS  Gastrology, ",
            "MBBS  Anesthesiology, MSc.  Psychology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Dermatology, ",
            "MBBS  Nuclear Medicine, MBBS  Immunology, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Gastrology, ",
            "MSc.  Medicine, MSc.  Medicine, Phd.  Pediatrics, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Immunology, ",
            "Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, ",
            "MBBS  Medicine, MSc.  Dermatology, ",
            "Phd.  Medicine, MSc.  Neurology, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Dermatology, ",
            "MSc.  Gastrology, MSc.  Immunology, Phd.  Pathology, MBBS  Neurology, Phd.  Medicine, ",
            "MBBS  Neurology, MSc.  Neurology, Phd.  Psychology, ",
            "MBBS  Medicine, Phd.  Anesthesiology, MSc.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Gastrology, MSc.  Immunology, ",
            "Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Medicine, Phd.  Pediatrics, ",
            "Phd.  Medicine, MBBS  Gastrology, Phd.  Pediatrics, ",
            "MSc.  Dermatology, Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Pediatrics, MBBS  Gastrology, Phd.  Gastrology, ",
            "MSc.  Neurology, Phd.  Medicine, Phd.  Anesthesiology, ",
            "MSc.  Gastrology, MSc.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Neurology, Phd.  Medicine, ",
            "Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, ",
            "Phd.  Dermatology, MBBS  Pathology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Dermatology, ",
            "MBBS  Immunology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Dermatology, ",
            "Phd.  Anesthesiology, MBBS  Nuclear Medicine, ",
            "MSc.  Gastrology, MBBS  Neurology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, MBBS  Dermatology, Phd.  Pediatrics, ",
            "MBBS  Dermatology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Pediatrics, Phd.  Pediatrics, MSc.  Gastrology, ",
            "Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, MBBS  Dermatology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Psychology, Phd.  Medicine, ",
            "MSc.  Immunology, MBBS  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Gastrology, ",
            "MBBS  Anesthesiology, MSc.  Neurology, Phd.  Dermatology, ",
            "MBBS  Gastrology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Neurology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Pediatrics, ",
            "MBBS  Neurology, MSc.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Anesthesiology, Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Nuclear Medicine, ",
            "Phd.  Dermatology, MSc.  Gastrology, Phd.  Gastrology, Phd.  Pediatrics, ",
            "MBBS  Gastrology, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Anesthesiology, ",
            "MSc.  Immunology, Phd.  Gastrology, MSc.  Immunology, ",
            "Phd.  Immunology, MBBS  Anesthesiology, ",
            "Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Immunology, Phd.  Dermatology, ",
            "MBBS  Medicine, MSc.  Gastrology, Phd.  Pediatrics, MBBS  Medicine, MSc.  Immunology, ",
            "MSc.  Nuclear Medicine, Phd.  Dermatology, Phd.  Psychology, ",
            "MSc.  Gastrology, MBBS  Gastrology, MSc.  Pathology, MBBS  Gastrology, MSc.  Gastrology, "
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "chamber": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "N10",
            null,
            "LK 813",
            null,
            null,
            "F85",
            "L775",
            "S15",
            "T27",
            "U526",
            null,
            null,
            "L33",
            null,
            "N 10",
            null,
            "T38",
            null,
            null,
            "Q 26",
            null,
            "J12",
            null,
            "R20",
            null,
            "H03",
            "P988",
            "X 91",
            null,
            "A 16",
            "Y 384",
            "J987",
            "N47",
            "Q26",
            "MC 548",
            null,
            "Y11",
            "O91",
            "S 30",
            "Z72",
            null,
            "C444",
            "HO 239",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "K99",
            "QU 741",
            "H587",
            "R65"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "bio": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "joined_on": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2018-07-19 01:04:13",
            "2012-06-22 01:15:23",
            "2010-04-22 04:25:24",
            "2015-07-16 01:34:29",
            "2018-07-08 03:00:13",
            "2011-08-23 15:38:53",
            "2010-06-30 04:49:01",
            "2014-01-30 19:22:14",
            "2016-08-19 00:00:33",
            "2013-05-05 20:25:13",
            "2012-04-14 20:48:07",
            "2015-08-14 23:23:06",
            "2019-11-10 04:08:39",
            "2011-07-14 04:25:59",
            "2012-05-20 03:00:05",
            "2015-03-22 14:38:39",
            "2012-12-07 03:51:51",
            "2019-11-15 19:27:29",
            "2014-07-12 13:55:42",
            "2010-01-15 22:16:11",
            "2010-05-02 07:23:29",
            "2010-07-26 23:46:24",
            "2012-10-01 21:42:46",
            "2019-03-26 00:01:35",
            "2012-04-12 23:34:56",
            "2011-02-09 16:35:58",
            "2013-07-10 16:10:04",
            "2016-09-27 09:21:57",
            "2019-08-21 23:51:42",
            "2017-12-19 19:05:46",
            "2019-12-08 16:38:59",
            "2015-03-14 14:40:26",
            "2015-10-28 05:00:30",
            "2010-09-30 21:31:42",
            "2018-05-27 13:49:57",
            "2011-09-19 07:33:13",
            "2016-11-30 16:12:22",
            "2014-10-05 01:05:36",
            "2019-01-05 20:04:59",
            "2017-11-07 11:26:01",
            "2014-12-20 03:30:15",
            "2017-04-23 21:34:03",
            "2013-10-10 10:47:47",
            "2017-06-06 18:17:06",
            "2018-07-27 23:12:33",
            "2019-06-29 01:33:11",
            "2015-12-07 14:15:47",
            "2019-06-30 15:04:20",
            "2016-04-13 16:00:06",
            "2018-07-06 11:44:45"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "general_service": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "autopsy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "biopsy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "blood_bank": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "bronchoscopy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ecg": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "echocardiography": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "emg": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "laparoscopy": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phonocardiography": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "urinalysis": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            null,
            1,
            0,
            null,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "registration_no"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "hospital": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "hospital_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Zeerobedor Hospital",
            "Parvenepicator Matrimonial Hospital",
            "Klibanollover Hospital",
            "Unkiledax Kidney Hospital",
            "Endglibamentor Hospital",
            "Luke Hospital ",
            "Klierplar Neurology Hospital",
            "Frozapanor Hospital of Neuroscience",
            "Rapzapin Pediatric Hospital",
            "Inhupimentor Baby-Care Hospital"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "description": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "hospital_type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Private",
            "Private",
            "Public",
            "Public",
            "Private",
            "Public",
            "Private",
            "Private",
            "Public",
            "Private"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "bed_type": {
          "TYPE": "Set",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "VIP Cabin,ICU,CCU,Emergency,COVID,Extra",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "image_source": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "tmtdt.asm",
            "oqu.xls",
            "sii.asm",
            "vmsmdp.xls",
            "rlk.bmp",
            "cmlmsho.xls",
            "frc.asm",
            "zjy.pdf",
            "epyvl.bmp",
            "lnvd.doc"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "website": {
          "TYPE": "tinytext",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            "https://kzckv.netx/qpnol/vbx.htm",
            "https://xyv.local6/bccfs/kkd.aspx",
            "https://ezqdl.locall/btkki/wdujd/grs.htm",
            "https://shjba.netf39/csjkv/dqrfq.htm",
            "https://ykbf.localo9/vvhsr/ixdq.htm",
            "https://oaq.local/sjqzy/gvb.php",
            "https://cjr.net/olisy/jtr.aspx",
            "https://uun.net57/gufes/kdlgj/ciip.aspx",
            "https://yghrz.net/cdinc/dohn.php"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "joined_on": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2015-05-26 00:01:10",
            "2019-11-15 00:13:30",
            "2017-01-09 09:27:49",
            "2010-02-08 10:32:20",
            "2018-03-03 11:17:21",
            "2016-04-05 14:14:01",
            "2018-03-29 21:55:25",
            "2013-10-31 06:12:04",
            "2018-01-14 16:45:51",
            "2017-10-16 04:56:15"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "private",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "public",
            "private",
            "public",
            "public",
            "public",
            "public",
            "public",
            "deleted",
            "public",
            "public"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "log": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "logged_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "task": {
          "TYPE": "tinytext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mobile_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "role": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "schedule": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "day": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "start_time": {
          "TYPE": "Time",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "end_time": {
          "TYPE": "Time",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "last_updated": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id",
        "day"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "doctor",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "staff": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "mobile_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "4GA1NXH512T780774",
            "3GANSIF717L856815",
            "WGXNRJ4B15M504766",
            "WJXT0M4I16J448238",
            "WWA2P77314L625434",
            "WFA43LN513H888817",
            "WKSBFDTW11J799073",
            "WNSV721V10J130412",
            "WRSC0K4B15Y325207",
            "WDX6J9S515K965371",
            "4XS33C4718T829554",
            "2TAY35X514S154978",
            "3JXSD24U12I315991",
            "2NS185I716X208245",
            "WVAU6Y1515S619418",
            "2RXYJSW314K095542",
            "WUAO8JC418S501454",
            "4RSY3E6511M733827",
            "4CA01Q6214A354802",
            "WQS5555018T046953",
            "WCSBL5C219X531750",
            "3UA1D88A13Z737756",
            "5KXUG11815A710454",
            "2OXLOTGF10X356946",
            "1FAH744714U952777",
            "WFSH41P513K211467",
            "WVA26U3615B410574",
            "5TSW4L4C17W792979",
            "WJAXWR3D14O451581",
            "1KSP3S9T14K823810",
            "5GS0KP3612H133913",
            "12345",
            "3PA7612712J387117",
            "WES48B6513K748621",
            "0842e8cde6cc91d2f8ef",
            "WNS068TF10A732797",
            "WASEUCJB12L129752",
            "1KSK458518M213335",
            "5IS31K6U19H532695",
            "3SS665O314M881437",
            "WKAJ34A117X106451",
            "3UX8R32P14I868224",
            "1PSO3FWI10P285281",
            "WBS173BQ19L832433",
            "1SA78RZ911L920228",
            "2XS9XNBY14V372002",
            "5FSH8C6N14O730722",
            "4KS871DI13J114342"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "role": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Moderator",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Admin",
            "Admin",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "Moderator",
            "Admin",
            "DB Manager",
            "Admin",
            "Moderator",
            "DB Manager",
            "Admin",
            "DB Manager",
            "Moderator",
            "Admin"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "registration_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "joined_on": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-01-05 12:50:49",
            "2011-04-28 16:24:24",
            "2019-11-22 13:31:01",
            "2018-01-07 06:37:40",
            "2016-07-10 19:49:48",
            "2020-07-15 20:17:00",
            "2017-08-25 12:22:50",
            "2014-07-16 01:41:33",
            "2017-04-11 23:22:10",
            "2019-04-23 17:37:06",
            "2012-03-04 07:25:45",
            "2014-12-29 20:40:28",
            "2020-01-03 19:17:43",
            "2018-04-26 23:57:03",
            "2013-11-29 12:42:33",
            "2016-11-10 00:22:29",
            "2018-09-26 15:11:24",
            "2018-11-12 01:18:24",
            "2015-10-17 00:55:42",
            "2013-06-02 13:46:56",
            "2011-05-09 09:32:46",
            "2012-08-14 19:31:08",
            "2012-10-24 20:36:22",
            "2016-07-02 08:39:50",
            "2021-03-14 07:25:54",
            "2021-06-07 03:56:41",
            "2018-02-17 23:07:33",
            "2020-01-26 12:49:40",
            "2013-05-31 13:55:30",
            "2020-10-07 15:02:14",
            "2011-01-16 19:30:55",
            "2021-01-17 21:20:32",
            "2020-01-17 02:12:02",
            "2014-09-23 17:34:46",
            "2021-08-29 23:47:42",
            "2017-02-28 05:35:07",
            "2011-07-10 17:24:30",
            "2016-01-14 10:19:20",
            "2019-06-07 12:31:05",
            "2011-08-08 01:51:52",
            "2012-09-26 15:22:45",
            "2021-01-16 05:38:17",
            "2013-07-09 21:20:10",
            "2015-04-27 18:31:26",
            "2021-06-13 03:09:00",
            "2016-12-11 16:02:47",
            "2021-07-07 08:22:20",
            "2014-02-07 15:36:19"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "last_updated": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2014-05-15 16:06:23",
            "2013-08-11 06:00:54",
            "2016-09-16 14:56:03",
            "2013-01-13 10:11:33",
            "2018-07-02 15:19:30",
            "2017-03-01 19:43:41",
            "2016-09-07 12:49:03",
            "2011-12-14 02:34:53",
            "2020-12-19 22:59:17",
            "2018-03-21 15:31:48",
            "2012-04-01 20:28:46",
            "2011-03-01 08:27:44",
            "2011-04-28 10:31:31",
            "2020-01-25 22:21:52",
            "2020-05-11 01:51:29",
            "2017-11-13 06:31:41",
            "2018-07-17 23:41:47",
            "2015-05-16 19:00:09",
            "2015-09-03 20:49:37",
            "2019-06-08 10:45:17",
            "2015-09-01 17:41:26",
            "2011-07-19 18:46:51",
            "2013-01-13 20:33:36",
            "2021-03-06 13:36:02",
            "2013-05-20 13:03:34",
            "2019-05-09 21:21:01",
            "2016-11-13 14:04:53",
            "2021-08-30 13:17:31",
            "2011-02-19 23:37:15",
            "2013-03-22 14:29:32",
            "2011-02-26 17:30:10",
            "2021-09-08 01:35:07",
            "2012-04-22 03:27:26",
            "2015-04-07 13:01:30",
            "2021-09-07 10:41:12",
            "2017-06-14 01:55:45",
            "2018-01-24 03:54:48",
            "2012-07-19 20:40:44",
            "2020-03-01 11:57:09",
            "2020-03-08 17:01:20",
            "2019-02-06 04:19:49",
            "2013-07-30 03:01:10",
            "2020-10-29 10:17:48",
            "2012-01-15 03:45:50",
            "2018-05-26 18:14:19",
            "2020-01-26 06:09:54",
            "2016-08-28 05:57:06",
            "2021-02-28 05:53:05"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "hospital",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "registration_no"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "user": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "mobile_no": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "WMS8ET5T13R424293",
            "4BAO0JC218G648511",
            "3DX2849512D295923",
            "2UA3S8BD19Y372468",
            "WJX2317U15L323016",
            "WKA6S1EO14X138550",
            "WNAQ7HEJ18C538586",
            "3KSB654M14L735543",
            "WPX6OOFZ18V728725",
            "WKS41YRW15Q301955",
            "WJSG0VN618U843315",
            "2BSOXSQA18T358224",
            "WBS64E4Z11X481243",
            "3BXH7N4814C516870",
            "5HSFQHJH11O403271",
            "3ZX8754714Q235159",
            "WBX5YN6S11P352363",
            "WNS46E6X11L363837",
            "1LSYJB7O17I766280",
            "4QALA8BS11P922064"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "sex": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "S",
            "F",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "T",
            "F",
            "M",
            "S",
            "S",
            "S",
            "T",
            "T",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "F"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dob": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2001-01-21",
            "1980-05-02",
            "2005-06-12",
            "1992-03-02",
            "1986-03-22",
            "1998-03-10",
            "1975-11-02",
            "2002-11-24",
            "1980-12-22",
            "2000-11-01",
            "1996-03-21",
            "1973-01-09",
            "1996-12-23",
            "1989-03-24",
            "2001-04-12",
            "2005-09-03",
            "1978-05-28",
            "2005-06-11",
            "1970-12-16",
            "2005-01-06"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
