{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/abterphp/qb/blob/09adeaafc58996b6e726b3de8848baea503eb33d/docker/postgres/init/init.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "offices": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "officeCode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "7"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "NYC",
            "Paris",
            "Tokyo",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "addressLine1": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "4-1 Kioicho",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "addressLine2": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "Floor #2",
            "Level 7"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "state": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "CA",
            "MA",
            "NY",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "country": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Japan",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "UK"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "postalCode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "94080",
            "02107",
            "10022",
            "75017",
            "102-8578",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "EC2N 1HN"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "territory": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "NA",
            "NA",
            "NA",
            "EMEA",
            "Japan",
            "APAC",
            "EMEA"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "officeCode"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "employees": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "employeeNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1002,
            1056,
            1076,
            1088,
            1102,
            1143,
            1165,
            1166,
            1188,
            1216,
            1286,
            1323,
            1337,
            1370,
            1401,
            1501,
            1504,
            1611,
            1612,
            1619,
            1621,
            1625,
            1702
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "lastName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bow",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tseng",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bott",
            "Jones",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Marsh",
            "King",
            "Nishi",
            "Kato",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "firstName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Diane",
            "Mary",
            "Jeff",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Julie",
            "Steve",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Loui",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Larry",
            "Barry",
            "Andy",
            "Peter",
            "Tom",
            "Mami",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "extension": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "x5800",
            "x4611",
            "x9273",
            "x4871",
            "x5408",
            "x5428",
            "x3291",
            "x4065",
            "x2173",
            "x4334",
            "x2248",
            "x4102",
            "x6493",
            "x2028",
            "x2759",
            "x2311",
            "x102",
            "x101",
            "x102",
            "x103",
            "x101",
            "x102",
            "x2312"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "officeCode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "6",
            "4",
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "2",
            "2",
            "3",
            "3",
            "4",
            "4",
            "4",
            "7",
            "7",
            "6",
            "6",
            "6",
            "5",
            "5",
            "4"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "reportsTo": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            1002,
            1002,
            1056,
            1056,
            1056,
            1143,
            1143,
            1143,
            1143,
            1143,
            1143,
            1102,
            1102,
            1102,
            1102,
            1102,
            1088,
            1088,
            1088,
            1056,
            1621,
            1102
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "jobTitle": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "President",
            "VP Sales",
            "VP Marketing",
            "Sales Manager (APAC)",
            "Sale Manager (EMEA)",
            "Sales Manager (NA)",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep",
            "Sales Rep"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "employeeNumber"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "reportsTo"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "employees",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "employeeNumber"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "officeCode"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "offices",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "officeCode"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "productlines": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "productLine": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Classic Cars",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Planes",
            "Ships",
            "Trains",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Vintage Cars"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "textDescription": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Attention car enthusiasts: Make your wildest car ownership dreams come true. Whether you are looking for classic muscle cars, dream sports cars or movie-inspired miniatures, you will find great choices in this category. These replicas feature superb attention to detail and craftsmanship and offer features such as working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare wheel, 4-wheel independent spring suspension, and so on. The models range in size from 1:10 to 1:24 scale and include numerous limited edition and several out-of-production vehicles. All models include a certificate of authenticity from their manufacturers and come fully assembled and ready for display in the home or office.",
            "Our motorcycles are state of the art replicas of classic as well as contemporary motorcycle legends such as Harley Davidson, Ducati and Vespa. Models contain stunning details such as official logos, rotating wheels, working kickstand, front suspension, gear-shift lever, footbrake lever, and drive chain. Materials used include diecast and plastic. The models range in size from 1:10 to 1:50 scale and include numerous limited edition and several out-of-production vehicles. All models come fully assembled and ready for display in the home or office. Most include a certificate of authenticity.",
            "Unique, diecast airplane and helicopter replicas suitable for collections, as well as home, office or classroom decorations. Models contain stunning details such as official logos and insignias, rotating jet engines and propellers, retractable wheels, and so on. Most come fully assembled and with a certificate of authenticity from their manufacturers.",
            "The perfect holiday or anniversary gift for executives, clients, friends, and family. These handcrafted model ships are unique, stunning works of art that will be treasured for generations! They come fully assembled and ready for display in the home or office. We guarantee the highest quality, and best value.",
            "Model trains are a rewarding hobby for enthusiasts of all ages. Whether you're looking for collectible wooden trains, electric streetcars or locomotives, you'll find a number of great choices for any budget within this category. The interactive aspect of trains makes toy trains perfect for young children. The wooden train sets are ideal for children under the age of 5.",
            "The Truck and Bus models are realistic replicas of buses and specialized trucks produced from the early 1920s to present. The models range in size from 1:12 to 1:50 scale and include numerous limited edition and several out-of-production vehicles. Materials used include tin, diecast and plastic. All models include a certificate of authenticity from their manufacturers and are a perfect ornament for the home and office.",
            "Our Vintage Car models realistically portray automobiles produced from the early 1900s through the 1940s. Materials used include Bakelite, diecast, plastic and wood. Most of the replicas are in the 1:18 and 1:24 scale sizes, which provide the optimum in detail and accuracy. Prices range from $30.00 up to $180.00 for some special limited edition replicas. All models include a certificate of authenticity from their manufacturers and come fully assembled and ready for display in the home or office."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "htmlDescription": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "image": {
          "TYPE": "Bytea",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "productLine"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "products": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "productCode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "S10_1678",
            "S10_1949",
            "S10_2016",
            "S10_4698",
            "S10_4757",
            "S10_4962",
            "S12_1099",
            "S12_1108",
            "S12_1666",
            "S12_2823",
            "S12_3148",
            "S12_3380",
            "S12_3891",
            "S12_3990",
            "S12_4473",
            "S12_4675",
            "S18_1097",
            "S18_1129",
            "S18_1342",
            "S18_1367",
            "S18_1589",
            "S18_1662",
            "S18_1749",
            "S18_1889",
            "S18_1984",
            "S18_2238",
            "S18_2248",
            "S18_2319",
            "S18_2325",
            "S18_2432",
            "S18_2581",
            "S18_2625",
            "S18_2795",
            "S18_2870",
            "S18_2949",
            "S18_2957",
            "S18_3029",
            "S18_3136",
            "S18_3140",
            "S18_3232",
            "S18_3233",
            "S18_3259",
            "S18_3278",
            "S18_3320",
            "S18_3482",
            "S18_3685",
            "S18_3782",
            "S18_3856",
            "S18_4027",
            "S18_4409",
            "S18_4522",
            "S18_4600",
            "S18_4668",
            "S18_4721",
            "S18_4933",
            "S24_1046",
            "S24_1444",
            "S24_1578",
            "S24_1628",
            "S24_1785",
            "S24_1937",
            "S24_2000",
            "S24_2011",
            "S24_2022",
            "S24_2300",
            "S24_2360",
            "S24_2766",
            "S24_2840",
            "S24_2841",
            "S24_2887",
            "S24_2972",
            "S24_3151",
            "S24_3191",
            "S24_3371",
            "S24_3420",
            "S24_3432",
            "S24_3816",
            "S24_3856",
            "S24_3949",
            "S24_3969",
            "S24_4048",
            "S24_4258",
            "S24_4278",
            "S24_4620",
            "S32_1268",
            "S32_1374",
            "S32_2206",
            "S32_2509",
            "S32_3207",
            "S32_3522",
            "S32_4289",
            "S32_4485",
            "S50_1341",
            "S50_1392",
            "S50_1514",
            "S50_4713",
            "S700_1138",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "S700_1938",
            "S700_2047",
            "S700_2466",
            "S700_2610",
            "S700_2824",
            "S700_2834",
            "S700_3167",
            "S700_3505",
            "S700_3962",
            "S700_4002",
            "S72_1253",
            "S72_3212"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "productName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1969 Harley Davidson Ultimate Chopper",
            "1952 Alpine Renault 1300",
            "<PERSON>",
            "2003 Harley-Davidson Eagle Drag Bike",
            "1972 Alfa Romeo GTA",
            "1962 LanciaA Delta 16V",
            "1968 Ford Mustang",
            "2001 Ferrari Enzo",
            "1958 Setra Bus",
            "2002 Suzuki XREO",
            "1969 Corvair Monza",
            "1968 Dodge Charger",
            "1969 Ford Falcon",
            "1970 Plymouth Hemi Cuda",
            "1957 Chevy Pickup",
            "1969 Dodge Charger",
            "1940 Ford Pickup Truck",
            "1993 Mazda RX-7",
            "1937 Lincoln Berline",
            "1936 Mercedes-Benz 500K Special Roadster",
            "1965 Aston Martin DB5",
            "1980s Black Hawk Helicopter",
            "1917 Grand Touring Sedan",
            "1948 Porsche 356-A Roadster",
            "1995 Honda Civic",
            "1998 Chrysler Plymouth Prowler",
            "1911 Ford Town Car",
            "1964 Mercedes Tour Bus",
            "1932 Model A Ford J-Coupe",
            "1926 Ford Fire Engine",
            "P-51-D Mustang",
            "1936 Harley Davidson El Knucklehead",
            "1928 Mercedes-Benz SSK",
            "1999 Indy 500 Monte Carlo SS",
            "1913 Ford Model T Speedster",
            "1934 Ford V8 Coupe",
            "1999 Yamaha Speed Boat",
            "18th Century Vintage Horse Carriage",
            "1903 Ford Model A",
            "1992 Ferrari 360 Spider red",
            "1985 Toyota Supra",
            "Collectable Wooden Train",
            "1969 Dodge Super Bee",
            "1917 Maxwell Touring Car",
            "1976 Ford Gran Torino",
            "1948 Porsche Type 356 Roadster",
            "1957 Vespa GS150",
            "1941 Chevrolet Special Deluxe Cabriolet",
            "1970 Triumph Spitfire",
            "1932 Alfa Romeo 8C2300 Spider Sport",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "1940s Ford truck",
            "1939 Cadillac Limousine",
            "1957 Corvette Convertible",
            "1957 Ford Thunderbird",
            "1970 Chevy Chevelle SS 454",
            "1970 Dodge Coronet",
            "1997 BMW R 1100 S",
            "1966 Shelby Cobra 427 S/C",
            "1928 British Royal Navy Airplane",
            "1939 Chevrolet Deluxe Coupe",
            "1960 BSA Gold Star DBD34",
            "18th century schooner",
            "1938 Cadillac V-16 Presidential Limousine",
            "1962 Volkswagen Microbus",
            "1982 Ducati 900 Monster",
            "1949 Jaguar XK 120",
            "1958 Chevy Corvette Limited Edition",
            "1900s Vintage Bi-Plane",
            "1952 Citroen-15CV",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1912 Ford Model T Delivery Wagon",
            "1969 Chevrolet Camaro Z28",
            "1971 Alpine Renault 1600s",
            "1937 Horch 930V Limousine",
            "2002 Chevy Corvette",
            "1940 Ford Delivery Sedan",
            "1956 Porsche 356A Coupe",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1936 Mercedes Benz 500k Roadster",
            "1992 Porsche Cayenne Turbo Silver",
            "1936 Chrysler Airflow",
            "1900s Vintage Tri-Plane",
            "1961 Chevrolet Impala",
            "1980’s GM Manhattan Express",
            "1997 BMW F650 ST",
            "1982 Ducati 996 R",
            "1954 Greyhound Scenicruiser",
            "1950's Chicago Surface Lines Streetcar",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1928 Ford Phaeton Deluxe",
            "1974 Ducati 350 Mk3 Desmo",
            "1930 Buick Marquette Phaeton",
            "Diamond T620 Semi-Skirted Tanker",
            "1962 City of Detroit Streetcar",
            "2002 Yamaha YZR M1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "American Airlines: B767-300",
            "<PERSON>",
            "HMS Bounty",
            "America West Airlines B757-200",
            "The USS Constitution Ship",
            "1982 Camaro Z28",
            "ATA: B757-300",
            "F/A 18 Hornet 1/72",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "American Airlines: MD-11S",
            "Boeing X-32A JSF",
            "Pont Yacht"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "productLine": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Motorcycles",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Planes",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Planes",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Ships",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Trains",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Planes",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Ships",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Planes",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Planes",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Planes",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Trains",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Vintage Cars",
            "Trucks and Buses",
            "Trains",
            "Motorcycles",
            "Ships",
            "Planes",
            "Ships",
            "Ships",
            "Planes",
            "Ships",
            "Classic Cars",
            "Planes",
            "Planes",
            "Ships",
            "Ships",
            "Planes",
            "Planes",
            "Ships"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "productScale": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1:10",
            "1:10",
            "1:10",
            "1:10",
            "1:10",
            "1:10",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:18",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:12",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:72",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:18",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:18",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:24",
            "1:18",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:32",
            "1:50",
            "1:50",
            "1:50",
            "1:50",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:18",
            "1:700",
            "1:72",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:700",
            "1:72",
            "1:72"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "productVendor": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Exoto Designs",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Gearbox Collectibles",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Classic Metal Creations",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "Autoart Studio Design",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Studio M Art Models",
            "Unimax Art Galleries",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Red Start Diecast",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Highway 66 Mini Classics",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Carousel DieCast Legends",
            "Welly Diecast Productions",
            "Second Gear Diecast",
            "Motor City Art Classics",
            "Unimax Art Galleries"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "productDescription": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "This replica features working kickstand, front suspension, gear-shift lever, footbrake lever, drive chain, wheels and steering. All parts are particularly delicate due to their precise scale and require special care and attention.",
            "Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Model features, official Harley Davidson logos and insignias, detachable rear wheelie bar, heavy diecast metal with resin parts, authentic multi-color tampo-printed graphics, separate engine drive belts, free-turning front fork, rotating tires and rear racing slick, certificate of authenticity, detailed engine, display stand\\r\\n, precision diecast replica, baked enamel finish, 1:10 scale model, removable fender, seat and tank cover piece for displaying the superior detail of the v-twin engine",
            "Features include: Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "Features include: Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "Hood, doors and trunk all open to reveal highly detailed interior features. Steering wheel actually turns the front wheels. Color dark green.",
            "Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "Model features 30 windows, skylights & glare resistant glass, working steering system, original logos",
            "Official logos and insignias, saddle bags located on side of motorcycle, detailed engine, working steering, working suspension, two leather seats, luggage rack, dual exhaust pipes, small saddle bag located on handle bars, two-tone paint with chrome accents, superior die-cast detail , rotating wheels , working kick stand, diecast metal with plastic parts and baked enamel finish.",
            "1:18 scale die-cast about 10\\\" long doors open, hood opens, trunk opens and wheels roll",
            "1:12 scale model of a 1968 Dodge Charger. Hood, doors and trunk all open to reveal highly detailed interior features. Steering wheel actually turns the front wheels. Color black",
            "Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "Very detailed 1970 Plymouth Cuda model in 1:12 scale. The Cuda is generally accepted as one of the fastest original muscle cars from the 1970s. This model is a reproduction of one of the orginal 652 cars built in 1970. Red color.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Detailed model of the 1969 Dodge Charger. This model includes finely detailed interior and exterior features. Painted in red and white.",
            "This model features soft rubber tires, working steering, rubber mud guards, authentic Ford logos, detailed undercarriage, opening doors and hood,  removable split rear gate, full size spare mounted in bed, detailed interior with opening glove box",
            "This model features, opening hood, opening doors, detailed engine, rear spoiler, opening trunk, working steering, tinted windows, baked enamel finish. Color red.",
            "Features opening engine cover, doors, trunk, and fuel filler cap. Color black",
            "This 1:18 scale replica is constructed of heavy die-cast metal and has all the features of the original: working doors and rumble seat, independent spring suspension, detailed interior, working steering system, and a bifold hood that reveals an engine so accurate that it even includes the wiring. All this is topped off with a baked enamel finish. Color white.",
            "Die-cast model of the silver 1965 Aston Martin DB5 in silver. This model includes full wire wheels and doors that open with fully detailed passenger compartment. In 1:18 scale, this model measures approximately 10 inches/20 cm long.",
            "1:18 scale replica of actual Army's UH-60L BLACK HAWK Helicopter. 100% hand-assembled. Features rotating rotor blades, propeller blades and rubber wheels.",
            "This 1:18 scale replica of the 1917 Grand Touring car has all the features you would expect from museum quality reproductions: all four doors and bi-fold hood opening, detailed engine and instrument panel, chrome-look trim, and tufted upholstery, all topped off with a factory baked-enamel finish.",
            "This precision die-cast replica features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "This model features, opening hood, opening doors, detailed engine, rear spoiler, opening trunk, working steering, tinted windows, baked enamel finish. Color yellow.",
            "Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "Features opening hood, opening doors, opening trunk, wide white wall tires, front door arm rests, working steering system.",
            "Exact replica. 100+ parts. working steering system, original logos",
            "This model features grille-mounted chrome horn, lift-up louvered hood, fold-down rumble seat, working steering system, chrome-covered spare, opening doors, detailed and wired engine",
            "Gleaming red handsome appearance. Everything is here the fire hoses, ladder, axes, bells, lanterns, ready to fight any inferno.",
            "Has retractable wheels and comes with a stand",
            "Intricately detailed with chrome accents and trim, official die-struck logos and baked enamel finish.",
            "This 1:18 replica features grille-mounted chrome horn, lift-up louvered hood, fold-down rumble seat, working steering system, chrome-covered spare, opening doors, detailed and wired engine. Color black.",
            "Features include opening and closing doors. Color: Red",
            "This 250 part reproduction includes moving handbrakes, clutch, throttle and foot pedals, squeezable horn, detailed wired engine, removable water, gas, and oil cans, pivoting monocle windshield, all topped with a baked enamel red finish. Each replica comes with an Owners Title and Certificate of Authenticity. Color red.",
            "Chrome Trim, Chrome Grille, Opening Hood, Opening Doors, Opening Trunk, Detailed Engine, Working Steering System",
            "Exact replica. Wood and Metal. Many extras including rigging, long boats, pilot house, anchors, etc. Comes with three masts, all square-rigged.",
            "Hand crafted diecast-like metal horse carriage is re-created in about 1:18 scale of antique horse carriage. This antique style metal Stagecoach is all hand-assembled with many different parts.\\r\\n\\r\\nThis collectible metal horse carriage is painted in classic Red, and features turning steering wheel and is entirely hand-finished.",
            "Features opening trunk,  working steering system",
            "his replica features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "This model features soft rubber tires, working steering, rubber mud guards, authentic Ford logos, detailed undercarriage, opening doors and hood, removable split rear gate, full size spare mounted in bed, detailed interior with opening glove box",
            "Hand crafted wooden toy train set is in about 1:18 scale, 25 inches in total length including 2 additional carts, of actual vintage train. This antique style wooden toy train model set is all hand-assembled with 100% wood.",
            "This replica features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "Features Gold Trim, Full Size Spare Tire, Chrome Trim, Chrome Grille, Opening Hood, Opening Doors, Opening Trunk, Detailed Engine, Working Steering System",
            "Highly detailed 1976 Ford Gran Torino \\\"Starsky and Hutch\\\" diecast model. Very well constructed and painted in red and white patterns.",
            "This model features working front and rear suspension on accurately replicated and actuating shock absorbers as well as opening engine cover, rear stabilizer flap,  and 4 opening doors.",
            "Features rotating wheels , working kick stand. Comes with stand.",
            "Features opening hood, opening doors, opening trunk, wide white wall tires, front door arm rests, working steering system, leather upholstery. Color black.",
            "Features include opening and closing doors. Color: White.",
            "This 1:18 scale precision die cast replica features the 6 front headlights of the original, plus a detailed version of the 142 horsepower straight 8 engine, dual spares and their famous comprehensive dashboard. Color black.",
            "Features opening trunk,  working steering system",
            "This 1940s Ford Pick-Up truck is re-created in 1:18 scale of original 1940s Ford truck. This antique style metal 1940s Ford Flatbed truck is all hand-assembled. This collectible 1940's Pick-Up truck is painted in classic dark green color, and features rotating wheels.",
            "Features completely detailed interior including Velvet flocked drapes,deluxe wood grain floor, and a wood grain casket with seperate chrome handles",
            "1957 die cast Corvette Convertible in Roman Red with white sides and whitewall tires. 1:18 scale quality die-cast with detailed engine and underbvody. Now you can own The Classic Corvette.",
            "This 1:18 scale precision die-cast replica, with its optional porthole hardtop and factory baked-enamel Thunderbird Bronze finish, is a 100% accurate rendition of this American classic.",
            "This model features rotating wheels, working streering system and opening doors. All parts are particularly delicate due to their precise scale and require special care and attention. It should not be picked up by the doors, roof, hood or trunk.",
            "1:24 scale die-cast about 18\\\" long doors open, hood opens and rubber wheels",
            "Detailed scale replica with working suspension and constructed from over 70 parts",
            "This diecast model of the 1966 Shelby Cobra 427 S/C includes many authentic details and operating parts. The 1:24 scale model of this iconic lighweight sports car from the 1960s comes in silver and it's own display case.",
            "Official logos and insignias",
            "This 1:24 scale die-cast replica of the 1939 Chevrolet Deluxe Coupe has the same classy look as the original. Features opening trunk, hood and doors and a showroom quality baked enamel finish.",
            "Detailed scale replica with working suspension and constructed from over 70 parts",
            "All wood with canvas sails. Many extras including rigging, long boats, pilot house, anchors, etc. Comes with 4 masts, all square-rigged.",
            "This 1:24 scale precision die cast replica of the 1938 Cadillac V-16 Presidential Limousine has all the details of the original, from the flags on the front to an opening back seat compartment complete with telephone and rifle. Features factory baked-enamel black finish, hood goddess ornament, working jump seats.",
            "This 1:18 scale die cast replica of the 1962 Microbus is loaded with features: A working steering system, opening front doors and tailgate, and famous two-tone factory baked enamel finish, are all topped of by the sliding, real fabric, sunroof.",
            "Features two-tone paint with chrome accents, superior die-cast detail , rotating wheels , working kick stand",
            "Precision-engineered from original Jaguar specification in perfect scale ratio. Features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "The operating parts of this 1958 Chevy Corvette Limited Edition are particularly delicate due to their precise scale and require special care and attention. Features rotating wheels, working streering, opening doors and trunk. Color dark green.",
            "Hand crafted diecast-like metal bi-plane is re-created in about 1:24 scale of antique pioneer airplane. All hand-assembled with many different parts. Hand-painted in classic yellow and features correct markings of original airplane.",
            "Precision crafted hand-assembled 1:18 scale reproduction of the 1952 15CV, with its independent spring suspension, working steering system, opening doors and hood, detailed engine and instrument panel, all topped of with a factory fresh baked enamel finish.",
            "This replica features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "This model features chrome trim and grille, opening hood, opening doors, opening trunk, detailed engine, working steering system. Color white.",
            "1969 Z/28 Chevy Camaro 1:24 scale replica. The operating parts of this limited edition 1:24 scale diecast model car 1969 Chevy Camaro Z28- hood, trunk, wheels, streering, suspension and doors- are particularly delicate due to their precise scale and require special care and attention.",
            "This 1971 Alpine Renault 1600s replica Features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "Features opening hood, opening doors, opening trunk, wide white wall tires, front door arm rests, working steering system",
            "The operating parts of this limited edition Diecast 2002 Chevy Corvette 50th Anniversary Pace car Limited Edition are particularly delicate due to their precise scale and require special care and attention. Features rotating wheels, poseable streering, opening doors and trunk.",
            "Chrome Trim, Chrome Grille, Opening Hood, Opening Doors, Opening Trunk, Detailed Engine, Working Steering System. Color black.",
            "Features include: Turnable front wheels; steering function; detailed interior; detailed engine; opening hood; opening trunk; opening doors; and detailed chassis.",
            "Has retractable wheels and comes with a stand. Official logos and insignias.",
            "This model features grille-mounted chrome horn, lift-up louvered hood, fold-down rumble seat, working steering system and rubber wheels. Color black.",
            "This replica features opening doors, superb detail and craftsmanship, working steering system, opening forward compartment, opening rear trunk with removable spare, 4 wheel independent spring suspension as well as factory baked enamel finish.",
            "Features opening trunk,  working steering system. Color dark green.",
            "Hand crafted diecast-like metal Triplane is Re-created in about 1:24 scale of antique pioneer airplane. This antique style metal triplane is all hand-assembled with many different parts.",
            "This 1:18 scale precision die-cast reproduction of the 1961 Chevrolet Impala has all the features-doors, hood and trunk that open; detailed 409 cubic-inch engine; chrome dashboard and stick shift, two-tone interior; working steering system; all topped of with a factory baked-enamel finish.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Features official die-struck logos and baked enamel finish. Comes with stand.",
            "Features rotating wheels , working kick stand. Comes with stand.",
            "Model features bi-level seating, 50 windows, skylights & glare resistant glass, working steering system, original logos",
            "<PERSON>",
            "This model features, opening doors, detailed engine, working steering, tinted windows, detailed interior, die-struck logos, removable stakes operating outriggers, detachable second trailer, functioning 360-degree self loader, precision molded resin trailer and trim, baked enamel finish on cab",
            "This model features grille-mounted chrome horn, lift-up louvered hood, fold-down rumble seat, working steering system",
            "This model features two-tone paint with chrome accents, superior die-cast detail , rotating wheels , working kick stand",
            "Features opening trunk,  working steering system",
            "This limited edition model is licensed and perfectly scaled for Lionel Trains. The Diamond T620 has been produced in solid precision diecast and painted with a fire baked enamel finish. It comes with a removable tanker and is a perfect model to add authenticity to your static train or car layout or to just have on display.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Features rotating wheels , working kick stand. Comes with stand.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Exact replia with official logos and insignias and retractable wheels",
            "Measures 31 1/2 inches Long x 25 1/2 inches High x 10 5/8 inches Wide\\r\\nAll wood with canvas sail. Extras include long boats, rigging, ladders, railing, anchors, side cannons, hand painted, etc.",
            "Measures 30 inches Long x 27 1/2 inches High x 4 3/4 inches Wide. \\r\\nMany extras including rigging, long boats, pilot house, anchors, etc. Comes with three masts, all square-rigged.",
            "Official logos and insignias. Working steering system. Rotating jet engines",
            "All wood with canvas sails. Measures 31 1/2\\\" Length x 22 3/8\\\" High x 8 1/4\\\" Width. Extras include 4 boats on deck, sea sprite on bow, anchors, copper railing, pilot houses, etc.",
            "Features include opening and closing doors. Color: White. \\r\\nMeasures approximately 9 1/2\\\" Long.",
            "Exact replia with official logos and insignias and retractable wheels",
            "10\\\" Wingspan with retractable landing gears.Comes with pilot",
            "Completed model measures 19 1/2 inches long, 9 inches high, 3inches wide and is in barn red/black. All wood and metal.",
            "Exact replica. Wood and Metal. Many extras including rigging, long boats, pilot house, anchors, etc. Comes with three masts, all square-rigged.",
            "Polished finish. Exact replia with official logos and insignias and retractable wheels",
            "10\\\" Wingspan with retractable landing gears.Comes with pilot",
            "Measures 38 inches Long x 33 3/4 inches High. Includes a stand.\\r\\nMany extras including rigging, long boats, pilot house, anchors, etc. Comes with 2 masts, all square-rigged"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "quantityInStock": {
          "TYPE": "SmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            7933,
            7305,
            6625,
            5582,
            3252,
            6791,
            68,
            3619,
            1579,
            9997,
            6906,
            9123,
            1049,
            5663,
            6125,
            7323,
            2613,
            3975,
            8693,
            8635,
            9042,
            5330,
            2724,
            8826,
            9772,
            4724,
            540,
            8258,
            9354,
            2018,
            992,
            4357,
            548,
            8164,
            4189,
            5649,
            4259,
            5992,
            3913,
            8347,
            7733,
            6450,
            1917,
            7913,
            9127,
            8990,
            7689,
            2378,
            5545,
            6553,
            8290,
            3128,
            6645,
            1249,
            3209,
            1005,
            4074,
            7003,
            8197,
            3627,
            7332,
            15,
            1898,
            2847,
            2327,
            6840,
            2350,
            2542,
            5942,
            1452,
            7723,
            9173,
            4695,
            7995,
            2902,
            9446,
            6621,
            6600,
            6812,
            2081,
            6582,
            4710,
            2756,
            7869,
            5099,
            178,
            9241,
            2874,
            8601,
            814,
            136,
            3341,
            7062,
            1016,
            1645,
            600,
            1897,
            5841,
            737,
            3501,
            9653,
            7083,
            6934,
            7106,
            551,
            1956,
            5088,
            8820,
            4857,
            414
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "buyPrice": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "48.81",
            "98.58",
            "68.99",
            "91.02",
            "85.68",
            "103.42",
            "95.34",
            "95.59",
            "77.90",
            "66.27",
            "89.14",
            "75.16",
            "83.05",
            "31.92",
            "55.70",
            "58.73",
            "58.33",
            "83.51",
            "60.62",
            "24.26",
            "65.96",
            "77.27",
            "86.70",
            "53.90",
            "93.89",
            "101.51",
            "33.30",
            "74.86",
            "58.48",
            "24.92",
            "49.00",
            "24.23",
            "72.56",
            "56.76",
            "60.78",
            "34.35",
            "51.61",
            "60.74",
            "68.30",
            "77.90",
            "57.01",
            "67.56",
            "49.05",
            "57.54",
            "73.49",
            "62.16",
            "32.95",
            "64.58",
            "91.92",
            "43.26",
            "52.66",
            "84.76",
            "23.14",
            "69.93",
            "34.21",
            "49.24",
            "32.37",
            "60.86",
            "29.18",
            "66.74",
            "22.57",
            "37.32",
            "82.34",
            "20.61",
            "61.34",
            "47.10",
            "47.25",
            "15.91",
            "34.25",
            "72.82",
            "16.24",
            "46.91",
            "50.51",
            "38.58",
            "26.30",
            "62.11",
            "48.64",
            "98.30",
            "29.34",
            "21.75",
            "69.78",
            "57.46",
            "36.23",
            "32.33",
            "53.93",
            "66.92",
            "24.14",
            "25.98",
            "26.72",
            "33.61",
            "33.02",
            "56.13",
            "27.06",
            "68.29",
            "37.49",
            "34.17",
            "34.00",
            "51.15",
            "43.30",
            "39.83",
            "68.80",
            "33.97",
            "46.53",
            "59.33",
            "54.40",
            "51.09",
            "53.63",
            "36.27",
            "32.77",
            "33.30"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "MSRP": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "95.70",
            "214.30",
            "118.94",
            "193.66",
            "136.00",
            "147.74",
            "194.57",
            "207.80",
            "136.67",
            "150.62",
            "151.08",
            "117.44",
            "173.02",
            "79.80",
            "118.50",
            "115.16",
            "116.67",
            "141.54",
            "102.74",
            "53.91",
            "124.44",
            "157.69",
            "170.00",
            "77.00",
            "142.25",
            "163.73",
            "60.54",
            "122.73",
            "127.13",
            "60.77",
            "84.48",
            "60.57",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "132.00",
            "101.31",
            "62.46",
            "86.02",
            "104.72",
            "136.59",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "107.57",
            "100.84",
            "80.41",
            "99.21",
            "146.99",
            "141.28",
            "62.17",
            "105.87",
            "143.62",
            "92.03",
            "87.77",
            "121.08",
            "50.31",
            "148.80",
            "71.27",
            "73.49",
            "57.80",
            "112.70",
            "50.31",
            "109.42",
            "33.19",
            "76.17",
            "122.89",
            "44.80",
            "127.79",
            "69.26",
            "90.87",
            "35.36",
            "68.51",
            "117.44",
            "37.76",
            "88.51",
            "85.61",
            "61.23",
            "65.75",
            "107.08",
            "83.86",
            "140.43",
            "68.24",
            "41.03",
            "118.28",
            "97.39",
            "72.45",
            "80.84",
            "96.31",
            "99.89",
            "40.23",
            "54.11",
            "62.14",
            "64.64",
            "68.79",
            "102.05",
            "43.64",
            "115.75",
            "58.58",
            "81.36",
            "66.67",
            "91.34",
            "86.61",
            "90.52",
            "99.72",
            "72.28",
            "101.15",
            "118.65",
            "80.00",
            "100.17",
            "99.31",
            "74.03",
            "49.66",
            "54.60"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "productCode"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "productLine"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "productlines",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "productLine"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "customers": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "customerNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            103,
            112,
            114,
            119,
            121,
            124,
            125,
            128,
            129,
            131,
            141,
            144,
            145,
            146,
            148,
            151,
            157,
            161,
            166,
            167,
            168,
            169,
            171,
            172,
            173,
            175,
            177,
            181,
            186,
            187,
            189,
            198,
            201,
            202,
            204,
            205,
            206,
            209,
            211,
            216,
            219,
            223,
            227,
            233,
            237,
            239,
            240,
            242,
            247,
            249,
            250,
            256,
            259,
            260,
            273,
            276,
            278,
            282,
            286,
            293,
            298,
            299,
            303,
            307,
            311,
            314,
            319,
            320,
            321,
            323,
            324,
            328,
            333,
            334,
            335,
            339,
            344,
            347,
            348,
            350,
            353,
            356,
            357,
            361,
            362,
            363,
            369,
            376,
            379,
            381,
            382,
            385,
            386,
            398,
            406,
            409,
            412,
            415,
            424,
            443,
            447,
            448,
            450,
            452,
            455,
            456,
            458,
            459,
            462,
            465,
            471,
            473,
            475,
            477,
            480,
            481,
            484,
            486,
            487,
            489,
            495,
            496
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "customerName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Atelier graphique",
            "Signal Gift Stores",
            "Australian Collectors, Co.",
            "La Rochelle Gifts",
            "Baane Mini Imports",
            "Mini Gifts Distributors Ltd.",
            "Havel & Zbyszek Co",
            "Blauer See Auto, Co.",
            "Mini Wheels Co.",
            "Land of Toys Inc.",
            "Euro+ Shopping Channel",
            "Volvo Model Replicas, Co",
            "Danish Wholesale Imports",
            "Saveley & Henriot, Co.",
            "Dragon Souveniers, Ltd.",
            "Muscle Machine Inc",
            "Diecast Classics Inc.",
            "Technics Stores Inc.",
            "Handji Gifts& Co",
            "Herkku Gifts",
            "American Souvenirs Inc",
            "Porto Imports Co.",
            "Daedalus Designs Imports",
            "La Corne D'abondance, Co.",
            "Cambridge Collectables Co.",
            "Gift Depot Inc.",
            "Osaka Souveniers Co.",
            "Vitachrome Inc.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "AV Stores, Co.",
            "Clover Collections, Co.",
            "Auto-Moto Classics Inc.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Canadian Gift Exchange Network",
            "Online Mini Collectables",
            "Toys4GrownUps.com",
            "Asian Shopping Network, Co",
            "Mini Caravy",
            "King Kong Collectables, Co.",
            "Enaco Distributors",
            "Boards & Toys Co.",
            "Natürlich Autos",
            "Heintze Collectables",
            "Québec Home Shopping Network",
            "ANG Resellers",
            "Collectable Mini Designs Co.",
            "giftsbymail.co.uk",
            "Alpha Cognac",
            "Messner Shopping Network",
            "Amica Models & Co.",
            "Lyon Souveniers",
            "Auto Associés & Cie.",
            "Toms Spezialitäten, Ltd",
            "Royal Canadian Collectables, Ltd.",
            "Franken Gifts, Co",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Rovelli Gifts",
            "Souveniers And Things Co.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "BG&E Collectables",
            "Vida Sport, Ltd",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Der Hund Imports",
            "Oulu Toy Supplies, Inc.",
            "Petit Auto",
            "Mini Classics",
            "Mini Creations Ltd.",
            "Corporate Gift Ideas Co.",
            "Down Under Souveniers, Inc",
            "Stylish Desk Decors, Co.",
            "Tekni Collectables Inc.",
            "Australian Gift Network, Co",
            "Suominen Souveniers",
            "Cramer Spezialitäten, Ltd",
            "Classic Gift Ideas, Inc",
            "CAF Imports",
            "Men 'R' US Retailers, Ltd.",
            "Asian Treasures, Inc.",
            "Marseille Mini Autos",
            "Reims Collectables",
            "SAR Distributors, Co",
            "GiftsForHim.com",
            "Kommission Auto",
            "Gifts4AllAges.com",
            "Online Diecast Creations Co.",
            "Lisboa Souveniers, Inc",
            "Precious Collectables",
            "Collectables For Less Inc.",
            "Royale Belge",
            "Salzburg Collectables",
            "Cruz & Sons Co.",
            "L'ordine Souveniers",
            "Tokyo Collectables, Ltd",
            "Auto Canal+ Petit",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Extreme Desk Decorations, Ltd",
            "Bavarian Collectables Imports, Co.",
            "Classic Legends Inc.",
            "Feuer Online Stores, Inc",
            "Gift Ideas Corp.",
            "Scandinavian Gift Ideas",
            "The Sharp Gifts Warehouse",
            "Mini Auto Werke",
            "Super Scale Inc.",
            "Microscale Inc.",
            "Corrida Auto Replicas, Ltd",
            "Warburg Exchange",
            "FunGiftIdeas.com",
            "Anton Designs, Ltd.",
            "Australian Collectables, Ltd",
            "Frau da Collezione",
            "West Coast Collectables Co.",
            "Mit Vergnügen & Co.",
            "Kremlin Collectables, Co.",
            "Raanan Stores, Inc",
            "Iberia Gift Imports, Corp.",
            "Motor Mint Distributors Inc.",
            "Signal Collectibles Ltd.",
            "Double Decker Gift Stores, Ltd",
            "Diecast Collectables",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contactLastName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "King",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lee",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Natividad",
            "Young",
            "Leong",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Rancé",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tseng",
            "King",
            "Kentary",
            "Frick",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Devon",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Young",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gao",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Young",
            "Kloss",
            "Ibsen",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Lincoln",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Holz",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Koskitalo",
            "Dewey",
            "Frick",
            "Huang",
            "Brown",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brown",
            "Brown",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Suominen",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cervantes",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kuger",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Young",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Urs",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cartrain",
            "Pipps",
            "Cruz",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "McRoy",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Feuer",
            "Lewis",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Frick",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Choi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Anton",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ricotti",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Moos",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Roel",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Smith",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contactFirstName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jean",
            "Peter",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Susan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Julie",
            "Kwai",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jytte ",
            "Mary ",
            "Eric",
            "Jeff",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Juri",
            "Wendy",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Keith",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Marie",
            "Jerry",
            "Julie",
            "Mory",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Matti",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dean",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Julie",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mike",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mary",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Palle",
            "Jean ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Renate ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Anna",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Marta",
            "Ed",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mel",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Steve",
            "Wing",
            "Julie",
            "Mike",
            "Ann ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ben",
            "Kalle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jesus",
            "Brian",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Paul ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Wales",
            "Karin",
            "Juri",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lino ",
            "Braun",
            "Allen",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Akiko",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Rita ",
            "Sarah",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Maria",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sue",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Yu",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sven ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sean",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Steve",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Rosa",
            "Sue",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tony"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "40.32.2555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "40.67.8555",
            "07-98 9555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(26) 642-7555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(91) 555 94 44",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "31 12 3555",
            "78.32.5555",
            "+65 221 7555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "+65 224 1555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(1) 356-5555",
            "20.16.1555",
            "(1) 42.34.2555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "90-224 8555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_MEDICARE>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "88.60.1555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(93) 203 4555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "86 21 3555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(91) 745 6555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "61.77.6555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "011-4988555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "30.59.8555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "981-443655",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "61-7-3844-6555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "2967 555",
            "91.24.4555",
            "26.47.1555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(1) 354-2555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "6562-9555",
            "+63 2 555 3587",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(1) 47.55.6555",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "7675-3555",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(91) 555 22 82",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_ACN>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "(95) 555 82 82",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "addressLine1": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "8489 Strong St.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Erling Skakkes gate 78",
            "5677 Strong St.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lyonerstr. 34",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Berguvsvägen  8",
            "Vinbæltet 34",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bronz Sok.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "7586 Pompton St.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brehmen St. 121",
            "149 Spinnaker Dr.",
            "Estrada da saúde n. 58",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "4658 Baden Av.",
            "25593 South Bay Ln.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Keskuskatu 45",
            "Fauntleroy Circus",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "16780 Pompton St.",
            "12, Berkeley Gardens Blvd",
            "1900 Oak St.",
            "7635 Spinnaker Dr.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Suntec Tower Three",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bank of China Tower",
            "Rambla de Cataluña, 23",
            "4097 Douglas Av.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Smagsloget 45",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Gran Vía, 1",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Magazinweg 7",
            "Via Monte Bianco 34",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Mehrheimerstr. 369",
            "23 Tsawassen Blvd.",
            "Berliner Platz 43",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Via Ludovico il Moro 22",
            "Monitor Money Building",
            "39323 Spinnaker Dr.",
            "Rte des Arsenaux 41 ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Drammensveien 126A",
            "Kingsfordweg 151",
            "Obere Str. 57",
            "Torikatu 38",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "7734 Strong St.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Software Engineering Center",
            "Maubelstr. 90",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Merchants House",
            "6047 Douglas Av.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luisenstr. 48",
            "8616 Spinnaker Dr.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Hauptstr. 29",
            "7825 Douglas Av.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Geislweg 14",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Strada Provinciale 124",
            "2-2-8 Roppongi",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Hansastr. 15",
            "5905 Pompton St.",
            "Heerstr. 22",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Åkergatan 24",
            "3086 Ingle Ln.",
            "Kirchgasse 6",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Walserweg 21",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "20093 Cologno Monzese",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Forsterstr. 57",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "3 Hagalim Blv.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "11328 Douglas Av.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "120 Hanover Sq.",
            "6251 Ingle Ln.",
            "Arenales 1938 3'A'"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "addressLine2": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            "Level 3",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Bronz Apt. 3/6 Tesvikiye",
            "Suite 400",
            null,
            null,
            "2nd Floor",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Suite 101",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Suite 101",
            null,
            null,
            "Floor No. 4",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "8 Temasek",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Crowther Way 23",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Level 15",
            null,
            "815 Pacific Hwy",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "PB 211 Sentrum",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Level 2",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "SEC Oy",
            null,
            null,
            "27-30 Merchant's Quay",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "NatWest Center #13-03",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Level 11",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Suite 200",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Alessandro Volta 16",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Nantes",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Nantes",
            "<PERSON>",
            "San Rafael",
            "Warszawa",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "NYC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Luleå",
            "Kobenhavn",
            "Lyon",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "NYC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Lisboa",
            "Lille",
            "Paris",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "NYC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Liverpool",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Barcelona",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Århus",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Cowes",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Torino",
            "Paris",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Köln",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Bergamo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Fribourg",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Oslo",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Oulu",
            "Bruxelles",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Espoo",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Cork",
            "Marseille",
            "Reims",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lisboa",
            "Bern",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Paris",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "NYC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Graz",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "NYC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Milan",
            "Burbank",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "state": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            "NV",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "CA",
            null,
            null,
            "CA",
            "NY",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "NY",
            "PA",
            "CA",
            null,
            null,
            "CT",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "MA",
            "CT",
            "Osaka",
            "NY",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "MA",
            null,
            "BC",
            "MA",
            "CA",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "CA",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "CA",
            "Isle of Wight",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "BC",
            null,
            "NSW",
            null,
            "NSW",
            "MA",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "NY",
            "MA",
            "CA",
            null,
            null,
            "NJ",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "PA",
            null,
            "CA",
            "Co. Cork",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "MA",
            "NH",
            null,
            null,
            "MA",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Tokyo",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "NY",
            null,
            "CT",
            null,
            "CA",
            null,
            "CT",
            "NY",
            null,
            null,
            "MA",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "CA",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "PA",
            "CA",
            null,
            "MA",
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "postalCode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "44000",
            "83030",
            "3004",
            "44000",
            "4110",
            "97562",
            "01-012",
            "60528",
            "94217",
            "10022",
            "28034",
            "S-958 22",
            "1734",
            "69004",
            "079903",
            "10022",
            "70267",
            "94217",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "N 5804",
            "97823",
            "1756",
            "59000",
            "75012",
            "51247",
            "97562",
            " 530-0003",
            "10022",
            "21240",
            "EC2 5NT",
            "2",
            "58339",
            "WX1 6LT",
            "V3F 2K1",
            "58339",
            "90003",
            "038988",
            "67000",
            null,
            "08022",
            "92561",
            "01307",
            "8200",
            "H1J 1C3",
            "28001",
            "91217",
            "PO31 7PJ",
            "31000",
            "60528",
            "10100",
            "75508",
            "78000",
            "50739",
            "T2F 8M4",
            "80805",
            "2060",
            "24100",
            "2067",
            "51247",
            "1700",
            "1203",
            "N 0106",
            "1043 GR",
            "12209",
            "90110",
            "B-1180",
            "24067",
            "50553",
            "94217",
            null,
            "WX3 6FW",
            "94019",
            "4101",
            "FIN-02271",
            "14776",
            "71270",
            "28023",
            "91003",
            null,
            "13008",
            "51100",
            "0028",
            null,
            "44087",
            "51003",
            "62005",
            "1675",
            "3012",
            "58339",
            "B-6000",
            "5020",
            "1227 MM",
            "42100",
            "106-0032",
            "75016",
            "70563",
            null,
            "80686",
            "10022",
            "04179",
            "97561",
            "S-844 67",
            "94217",
            "8010",
            "97823",
            "10022",
            "28023",
            "52066",
            "50553",
            "28023",
            "3150",
            null,
            "94019",
            "68306",
            "196143",
            "47625",
            "41101",
            "71270",
            "94217",
            "WA1 1DP",
            "51003",
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "country": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "Spain",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "Japan",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "UK",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "UK",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Spain",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Spain",
            "USA",
            "UK",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Italy",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Italy",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "UK",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "Spain",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Italy",
            "Japan",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "Spain",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "USA",
            "Spain",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Italy",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Spain",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "UK",
            "USA",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "salesRepEmployeeNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1370,
            1166,
            1611,
            1370,
            1504,
            1165,
            null,
            1504,
            1165,
            1323,
            1370,
            1504,
            1401,
            1337,
            1621,
            1286,
            1216,
            1165,
            1612,
            1504,
            1286,
            null,
            1370,
            1337,
            1188,
            1323,
            1621,
            1286,
            1501,
            1501,
            1504,
            1216,
            1501,
            1323,
            1188,
            1166,
            null,
            1370,
            1621,
            1702,
            1166,
            null,
            1401,
            1286,
            null,
            1166,
            1501,
            1370,
            null,
            1401,
            1337,
            1370,
            1504,
            1323,
            null,
            1611,
            1401,
            1611,
            1216,
            null,
            1702,
            1504,
            null,
            null,
            1501,
            1401,
            1323,
            1188,
            1165,
            1612,
            1501,
            1323,
            1611,
            1501,
            null,
            1188,
            1702,
            1166,
            null,
            1337,
            1337,
            null,
            1612,
            null,
            1216,
            1216,
            null,
            1702,
            1188,
            1401,
            1401,
            1621,
            1401,
            1621,
            1337,
            null,
            1612,
            1504,
            1286,
            null,
            1323,
            1504,
            1165,
            1401,
            1286,
            1286,
            1702,
            null,
            1216,
            null,
            1611,
            1401,
            1166,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            1702,
            1323,
            1165,
            1501,
            1188,
            1612
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "creditLimit": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "21000.00",
            "71800.00",
            "117300.00",
