{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/keybrl/xdu-coursework/blob/e9fff7ed60380e63fb557f2f47a6573604de3948/projects/g2h2-db/%E7%AC%AC1%E6%AC%A1%E4%B8%8A%E6%9C%BA/%E6%BA%90%E7%A0%81/employee.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "employee": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "employee_name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Baker",
            "Cole",
            "David",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Green",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ida",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nolan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Roman",
            "Scott",
            "Tony",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Web",
            "<PERSON>",
            "York",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "street": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "A",
            "A",
            "A",
            "A",
            "A",
            "A",
            "A",
            "C",
            "B",
            "A",
            "B",
            "B",
            "B",
            "B",
            "B",
            "B",
            "B",
            "B",
            "C",
            "C",
            "C",
            "C",
            "C",
            "C",
            "C",
            "C"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "employee_name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "company": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "company_name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "HUAWEI",
            "<PERSON>",
            "NetEase",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Baidu",
            "ICBC",
            "ABC",
            "CCB",
            "BOC",
            "BOCOM",
            "First Bank Corporation",
            "Small Bank Corporation"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "company_name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "works": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "employee_name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Baker",
            "Cole",
            "David",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Green",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ida",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nolan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Roman",
            "Scott",
            "Tony",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Web",
            "<PERSON>",
            "York",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "company_name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "HUAWEI",
            "NetEase",
            "HUAWEI",
            "NetEase",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "ICBC",
            "HUAWEI",
            "<PERSON>",
            "HUAWEI",
            "ICBC",
            "<PERSON>",
            "NetEase",
            "BOC",
            "Small Bank Corporation",
            "CCB",
            "First Bank Corporation",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Small Bank Corporation",
            "BOCOM",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "First Bank Corporation",
            "First Bank Corporation"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "salary": {
          "TYPE": "Numeric",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            5456,
            1231,
            9999,
            620,
            530,
            3332,
            22222,
            54355,
            23233,
            54353,
            2332,
            23413,
            980928,
            24816,
            9876,
            12345,
            99823,
            666,
            2333,
            500,
            13500,
            600,
            550,
            540,
            1000,
            10001
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "employee_name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "employee_name"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "employee",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "employee_name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "company_name"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "company",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "company_name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "manages": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "employee_name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Baker",
            "Cole",
            "David",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Green",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ida",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nolan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Roman",
            "Scott",
            "Tony",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Web",
            "<PERSON>",
            "York",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "manager_name": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cole",
            "Cole",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cole",
            "<PERSON>",
            "David",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Green",
            "Roman",
            "Roman",
            "Roman",
            "David",
            "Ida",
            "Ida",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "employee_name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "employee_name"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "employee",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "employee_name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "manager_name"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "employee",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "employee_name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}