{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/iqbalatma/project_w_dio/blob/517cb64452de3b6c3d70bae80d951daa9bf82df8/assets/Backup%20Database/tes_sabun_cuci_mobil-v15-structure_and_data_full.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "basic_info_meta": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "fullname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sabun Aryanz - kasir cica 1",
            "Sabun Aryanz - kasir uber 1"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact_1": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact_2": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "website": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "http://sabun-aryanz.com",
            "http://sabun-aryanz.com",
            "http://sabun-aryanz.com"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "logo": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "logo.png",
            "logo.png",
            "logo.png"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-11-16 03:02:30",
            "2021-01-13 18:00:00",
            "2021-01-13 18:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "updated_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-26 18:01:18",
            "2021-01-26 18:01:46",
            "2021-01-26 19:46:48"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "updated_by": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "store_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "store",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "SetNull",
          "ON_UPDATE": "Cascade"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "customer": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "full_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Jhon",
            "Shin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gudang Pusat",
            "Cust uber 1",
            "Cust uber 2",
            "Cust uber 3",
            "tes1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "toko ujung berung"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "0888888888",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "0888888888888",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<AU_ABN>",
            "0111111111111",
            "01111111111111"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cust_type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "retail",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "retail",
            "retail",
            "reseller",
            "reseller",
            "reseller",
            "retail",
            "retail",
            "reseller",
            "retail",
            "reseller",
            "reseller"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-23 03:06:55",
            "2020-12-24 06:37:27",
            "2021-01-12 02:33:53",
            "2021-01-12 02:34:36",
            "2021-01-12 02:39:31",
            "2021-01-26 19:51:17",
            "2021-01-26 19:51:51",
            "2021-01-26 19:52:10",
            "2021-01-28 21:24:40",
            "2021-01-29 20:27:22",
            "2021-01-29 21:23:16"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_store": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "store_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "store",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "SetNull",
          "ON_UPDATE": "Cascade"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "custom_price": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "price": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            10000,
            7000,
            11500,
            4500,
            25000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "customer_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "product_code": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "PR001",
            "TYTY1",
            "TYTY1",
            "TYTY1",
            "PR002"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-24 06:38:03",
            "2021-01-12 02:34:03",
            "2021-01-12 02:34:52",
            "2021-01-12 02:39:42",
            "2021-01-26 19:51:31"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "employee": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "username": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "admins"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "$2a$08$g6axSKDVOvmKJOTOYUbK/OO1DP5vsSRPNtRBowHc.nQs2v5VGsoky",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$TewpSs2aYottWdQaZLCHjeNpMdTPBV.xizhqPrHCiuWC3aHIwfGpy",
            "$2a$08$eDBmz5BisfYClwo.rs5k.Ot8pqR.3Ub/X1.1ANTc5bbaMJyy0H9Y."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "first_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "",
            "Admin",
            "Admin",
            "Kasir Cica 1",
            "Kasir Cica 2",
            "Kasir Uber 1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "dios"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "last_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Sihir",
            "Pemilik",
            "Gudang 1",
            "Gudang 2",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "Ilham"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Headquarters",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "avatar": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "avatar-1.png",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "avatar-7.png",
            "avatar-1.png",
            "avatar-2.png",
            "avatar-2.png",
            "avatar-3.png",
            "avatar-3.png",
            "avatar-3.png",
            "avatar-3.png",
            "avatar-1.png"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "role_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            3,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-11-18 22:55:22",
            "2020-11-10 22:48:27",
            "2020-11-10 22:52:15",
            "2020-11-10 22:52:15",
            "2020-11-10 22:54:23",
            "2020-11-10 22:54:23",
            "2020-11-10 22:54:23",
            "2020-11-10 22:54:23",
            "2020-11-17 03:19:40"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "invoice": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            15,
            1,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            16,
            10,
            39,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            17,
            11,
            70,
            71,
            89,
            90,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            98,
            18,
            12,
            99,
            100,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            105,
            106,
            107,
            108,
            19,
            13,
            109,
            110,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            114,
            115,
            116,
            117,
            118,
            20,
            14,
            119,
            120,
            121,
            133,
            134,
            135,
            136,
            139,
            140,
            141,
            21,
            142,
            22,
            23
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "invoice_number": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1/KS/01/2021",
            "1/KS/12/2020",
            "10/CB/01/2021",
            "11/CB/01/2021",
            "12/KS/01/2021",
            "13/KS/01/2021",
            "14/KS/01/2021",
            "15/CB/01/2021",
            "16/CB/01/2021",
            "17/CB/01/2021",
            "18/CB/01/2021",
            "19/CB/01/2021",
            "2/AR/01/2021",
            "2/KS/12/2020",
            "20/CB/01/2021",
            "21/CB/01/2021",
            "22/CB/01/2021",
            "23/CB/01/2021",
            "24/CB/01/2021",
            "25/CB/01/2021",
            "26/CB/01/2021",
            "27/CB/01/2021",
            "28/CB/01/2021",
            "29/CB/01/2021",
            "3/AR/01/2021",
            "3/KS/12/2020",
            "30/CB/01/2021",
            "31/CB/01/2021",
            "32/CB/01/2021",
            "33/CB/01/2021",
            "34/KS/01/2021",
            "35/KS/01/2021",
            "36/KS/01/2021",
            "37/KS/01/2021",
            "38/CB/01/2021",
            "39/KS/01/2021",
            "4/AR/01/2021",
            "4/KS/12/2020",
            "40/CB/01/2021",
            "41/CB/01/2021",
            "42/CB/01/2021",
            "43/CB/01/2021",
            "44/KS/01/2021",
            "45/KS/01/2021",
            "46/KS/01/2021",
            "47/KS/01/2021",
            "48/CB/01/2021",
            "49/CB/01/2021",
            "5/KS/01/2021",
            "5/KS/12/2020",
            "50/CB/01/2021",
            "51/CB/01/2021",
            "52/CB/01/2021",
            "53/CB/01/2021",
            "54/CB/01/2021",
            "55/CB/01/2021",
            "56/KS/01/2021",
            "57/CB/01/2021",
            "58/CB/01/2021",
            "59/CB/01/2021",
            "6/KS/01/2021",
            "6/KS/12/2020",
            "60/CB/01/2021",
            "61/CB/01/2021",
            "62/CB/01/2021",
            "63/CB/01/2021",
            "64/CB/01/2021",
            "65/CB/01/2021",
            "66/CB/01/2021",
            "67/CB/01/2021",
            "68/CB/01/2021",
            "69/CB/01/2021",
            "7/KS/01/2021",
            "70/KS/01/2021",
            "8/KS/01/2021",
            "9/CB/01/2021"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "paid_amount": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            20000,
            "<PERSON>",
            13000,
            0,
            100000,
            5000,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            512000,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            80000,
            0,
            0,
            15000,
            10000,
            200000,
            15000,
            0,
            12000,
            0,
            0,
            200000,
            0,
            0,
            50000,
            12000,
            8000,
            10000,
            20500,
            0,
            25000,
            0,
            15000,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1500000,
            0,
            0,
            50000,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            222222222,
            35000,
            100000,
            15000,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "left_to_paid": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            39000,
            47000,
            0,
            8000,
            3000,
            54000,
            10000,
            0,
            840000,
            20000,
            20000,
            8008000,
            81000,
            60000,
            200000,
            "<PERSON>",
            20000,
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            100000,
            "<PERSON>",
            60000,
            "<PERSON>",
            100000,
            1000,
            "<PERSON>",
            20000,
            45000,
            10000,
            60000,
            45000,
            "<PERSON>",
            18000,
            181000,
            100000,
            7808000,
            80000,
            100000,
            50000,
            38000,
            30000,
            30000,
            9500,
            50000,
            25000,
            60000,
            45000,
            30000,
            "<PERSON>",
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            "<PERSON>",
            6152500,
            3183500,
            20000,
            3164000,
            1664000,
            1347500,
            50000,
            "<PERSON>",
            56000,
            "<PERSON>",
            228000,
            235000,
            96000,
            "<PERSON>",
            27000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            52500,
            -222169722,
            17000,
            10000,
            15000,
            60000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "paid_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-13 11:03:41",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-26 07:32:29",
            "2021-01-26 07:33:05",
            "2021-01-26 07:41:57",
            "2021-01-26 07:42:10",
            "2021-01-26 07:42:24",
            "2021-01-26 07:48:45",
            "2021-01-26 07:51:07",
            "2021-01-26 07:52:33",
            "2021-01-26 07:54:18",
            "2021-01-26 07:54:44",
            "2021-01-13 11:06:49",
            "2020-12-24 16:52:17",
            "2021-01-26 07:55:13",
            "2021-01-26 09:38:12",
            "2021-01-26 10:38:37",
            "2021-01-26 10:52:01",
            "2021-01-26 11:03:13",
            "2021-01-26 11:06:18",
            "2021-01-26 11:10:36",
            "2021-01-26 11:35:51",
            "2021-01-26 11:40:30",
            "2021-01-26 11:41:52",
            "2021-01-13 11:07:23",
            "2020-12-24 17:01:28",
            "2021-01-26 11:48:27",
            "2021-01-26 15:45:35",
            "2021-01-26 17:32:25",
            "2021-01-26 17:34:29",
            "2021-01-26 19:56:40",
            "2021-01-27 06:27:40",
            "2021-01-27 06:43:49",
            "2021-01-27 06:44:21",
            "2021-01-27 06:45:56",
            "2021-01-27 10:26:27",
            "2021-01-13 11:42:12",
            "2020-12-24 18:14:31",
            "2021-01-29 15:24:18",
            "2021-01-29 15:27:28",
            "2021-01-29 17:21:25",
            "2021-01-29 17:21:34",
            "2021-01-29 18:31:42",
            "2021-01-29 18:32:02",
            "2021-01-29 18:44:37",
            "2021-01-29 18:45:12",
            "2021-01-29 21:23:53",
            "2021-01-29 21:24:24",
            "2021-01-13 17:36:51",
            "2020-12-24 18:15:02",
            "2021-01-29 23:01:54",
            "2021-01-29 23:02:45",
            "2021-01-29 23:07:52",
            "2021-01-29 23:09:15",
            "2021-01-30 10:47:34",
            "2021-01-30 11:32:46",
            "2021-01-30 22:04:09",
            "2021-01-31 06:29:15",
            "2021-01-31 06:32:05",
            "2021-01-31 06:36:16",
            "2021-01-13 18:16:38",
            "2020-12-24 18:26:13",
            "2021-01-31 06:51:06",
            "2021-01-31 06:51:26",
            "2021-01-31 06:51:53",
            "2021-01-31 07:39:53",
            "2021-01-31 07:40:35",
            "2021-01-31 07:44:44",
            "2021-01-31 07:45:12",
            "2021-01-31 07:53:30",
            "2021-01-31 11:39:54",
            "2021-01-31 11:40:06",
            "2021-01-13 18:23:22",
            "2021-01-31 11:41:02",
            "2021-01-26 07:22:21",
            "2021-01-26 07:29:29"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "paid_type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "transfer",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "transfer",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "transfer",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "kontrabon",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash",
            "cash"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "payment_img": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "transaction_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            13,
            1,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            21,
            22,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            14,
            10,
            33,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            15,
            10,
            65,
            66,
            63,
            66,
            68,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            14,
            11,
            73,
            73,
            73,
            73,
            75,
            75,
            76,
            76,
            77,
            77,
            16,
            12,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            85,
            86,
            17,
            12,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            107,
            108,
            108,
            18,
            109,
            16,
            19
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-13 11:03:41",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-26 07:32:29",
            "2021-01-26 07:33:05",
            "2021-01-26 07:41:57",
            "2021-01-26 07:42:09",
            "2021-01-26 07:42:24",
            "2021-01-26 07:48:45",
            "2021-01-26 07:51:07",
            "2021-01-26 07:52:33",
            "2021-01-26 07:54:18",
            "2021-01-26 07:54:44",
            "2021-01-13 11:06:49",
            "2020-12-24 16:52:17",
            "2021-01-26 07:55:13",
            "2021-01-26 09:38:12",
            "2021-01-26 10:38:37",
            "2021-01-26 10:52:01",
            "2021-01-26 11:03:13",
            "2021-01-26 11:06:18",
            "2021-01-26 11:10:36",
            "2021-01-26 11:35:51",
            "2021-01-26 11:40:30",
            "2021-01-26 11:41:52",
            "2021-01-13 11:07:23",
            "2020-12-24 17:01:28",
            "2021-01-26 11:48:27",
            "2021-01-26 15:45:35",
            "2021-01-26 17:32:24",
            "2021-01-26 17:34:29",
            "2021-01-26 19:56:40",
            "2021-01-27 06:27:40",
            "2021-01-27 06:43:49",
            "2021-01-27 06:44:21",
            "2021-01-27 06:45:56",
            "2021-01-27 10:26:27",
            "2021-01-13 11:42:12",
            "2020-12-24 18:14:31",
            "2021-01-29 15:24:18",
            "2021-01-29 15:27:28",
            "2021-01-29 17:21:25",
            "2021-01-29 17:21:34",
            "2021-01-29 18:31:42",
            "2021-01-29 18:32:01",
            "2021-01-29 18:44:37",
            "2021-01-29 18:45:12",
            "2021-01-29 21:23:53",
            "2021-01-29 21:24:24",
            "2021-01-13 17:36:51",
            "2020-12-24 18:15:02",
            "2021-01-29 23:01:54",
            "2021-01-29 23:02:45",
            "2021-01-29 23:07:52",
            "2021-01-29 23:09:15",
            "2021-01-30 10:47:34",
            "2021-01-30 11:32:46",
            "2021-01-30 22:04:09",
            "2021-01-31 06:29:15",
            "2021-01-31 06:32:05",
            "2021-01-31 06:36:16",
            "2021-01-13 18:16:38",
            "2020-12-24 18:26:13",
            "2021-01-31 06:51:06",
            "2021-01-31 06:51:26",
            "2021-01-31 06:51:53",
            "2021-01-31 07:39:53",
            "2021-01-31 07:40:35",
            "2021-01-31 07:44:44",
            "2021-01-31 07:45:12",
            "2021-01-31 07:53:30",
            "2021-01-31 11:39:54",
            "2021-01-31 11:40:06",
            "2021-01-13 18:23:22",
            "2021-01-31 11:41:02",
            "2021-01-26 07:22:20",
            "2021-01-26 07:29:29"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "status": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "0",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "1",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "0",
            "1"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "transaction_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "transaction",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "NoAction",
          "ON_UPDATE": "Cascade"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "invoice_item": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            98,
            99,
            100,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            105,
            106,
            107,
            108,
            109,
            110,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            114,
            115,
            116,
            117,
            118,
            119,
            120,
            121,
            144,
            145,
            146,
            147,
            148,
            149,
            155,
            156,
            157
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "quantity": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            2,
            12,
            4,
            19,
            4,
            10,
            2,
            395,
            4,
            5,
            3,
            5,
            4,
            3,
            2,
            4,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            4,
            42,
            1,
            1,
            3,
            10,
            5,
            6,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            5,
            4,
            5,
            3,
            1,
            3,
            7,
            3,
            1,
            3,
            8,
            5,
            7,
            3,
            5,
            3,
            5,
            5,
            4,
            5,
            3,
            2,
            9,
            2,
            4,
            91,
            96,
            112,
            83,
            45,
            19,
            36,
            22,
            2,
            113,
            77,
            2,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            5,
            5,
            2,
            2,
            5,
            1,
            111,
            3,
            5
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "item_price": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            80000,
            "<PERSON>",
            80000,
            "<PERSON>",
            20000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            100000,
            30000,
            50000,
            52000,
            60000,
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            40000,
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            840000,
            20000,
            20000,
            60000,
            200000,
            "<PERSON>",
            120000,
            40000,
            40000,
            81000,
            100000,
            80000,
            "<PERSON>",
            60000,
            20000,
            81000,
            140000,
            81000,
            20000,
            60000,
            200000,
            50000,
            189000,
            30000,
            100000,
            81000,
            100000,
            100000,
            40000,
            50000,
            60000,
            40000,
            "<PERSON>",
            54000,
            "<PERSON>",
            136500,
            2880000,
            "<PERSON>",
            124500,
            1350000,
            532000,
            792000,
            "<PERSON>",
            20000,
            3164000,
            1347500,
            56000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            120000,
            100000,
            "<PERSON>",
            40000,
            56000,
            "<PERSON>",
            27000,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            52500,
            110000
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "invoice_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            10,
            10,
            12,
            13,
            15,
            16,
            16,
            17,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            23,
            25,
            26,
            28,
            34,
            35,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            57,
            58,
            58,
            59,
            67,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            69,
            70,
            70,
            71,
            92,
            92,
            94,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            96,
            98,
            99,
            103,
            105,
            107,
            109,
            110,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            113,
            113,
            114,
            114,
            114,
            114,
            114,
            115,
            116,
            118,
            119,
            120,
            121,
            121,
            133,
            133,
            134,
            134,
            135,
            136,
            139,
            140,
            142
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "product_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            3,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            16,
            1,
            7,
            16,
            7,
            2,
            2,
            6,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            7,
            2,
            2,
            7,
            16,
            8
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "kas": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            23,
            27,
            28,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "kas_code": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "D/20/12/000001",
            "D/20/12/000002",
            "D/20/12/000003",
            "D/20/12/000004",
            "D/21/01/000001",
            "D/21/01/000002",
            "D/21/01/000003",
            "K/21/01/000004",
            "K/21/01/000005",
            "K/21/01/000006",
            "D/21/01/000007",
            "D/21/01/000008",
            "D/21/01/000009",
            "D/21/01/000010",
            "D/21/01/000011",
            "D/21/01/000012",
            "D/21/01/000013",
            "D/21/01/000014",
            "D/21/01/000015",
            "D/21/01/000016",
            "D/21/01/000017",
            "D/21/01/000018",
            "D/21/01/000019",
            "D/21/01/000020",
            "D/21/01/000021",
            "D/21/01/000022",
            "D/21/01/000023",
            "D/21/01/000024",
            "D/21/01/000025",
            "D/21/01/000026",
            "D/21/01/000027",
            "D/21/01/000028",
            "K/21/01/000029",
            "K/21/01/000030",
            "D/21/01/000031",
            "K/21/01/000032",
            "D/21/01/000033",
            "K/21/01/000034",
            "D/21/01/000035",
            "K/21/01/000036",
            "K/21/01/000037",
            "K/21/01/000038",
            "K/21/01/000039",
            "K/21/01/000040",
            "K/21/01/000041",
            "K/21/01/000042"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "title": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Checkout: INV 1/KS/12/2020",
            "Checkout: INV 2/KS/12/2020",
            "Checkout: INV 4/KS/12/2020",
            "Checkout: INV 5/KS/12/2020",
            "Checkout: INV 1/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 2/AR/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 3/AR/01/2021",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pengeluaran aja lupa saya juga apa",
            "Checkout: INV 5/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 6/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 7/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 12/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 14/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout ke Cabang: <br>INV 15/CB/01/2021",
            "Checkout ke Cabang:\nINV 16/CB/01/2021",
            "Checkout ke Cabang: INV 23/CB/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 32/CB/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 33/CB/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 34/KS/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 35/KS/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 37/KS/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 41/CB/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 42/CB/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 43/CB/01/2021",
            "Checkout: INV 44/KS/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 45/KS/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 47/KS/01/2021",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 49/CB/01/2021",
            "AWALUDIN",
            "bakso goreng",
            "Energi",
            "Energize",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 58/CB/01/2021",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bayar Utang: INV 69/CB/01/2021",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Checkout: INV 70/KS/01/2021",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "description": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            "Energi drink",
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-24",
            "2020-12-24",
            "2020-12-24",
            "2020-12-24",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2020-10-02",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-13",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-26",
            "2021-01-27",
            "2021-01-27",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2021-01-29",
            "2020-12-28",
            "2020-12-28",
            "2021-01-22",
            "2020-12-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-03",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31",
            "2021-01-31"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "debet": {
          "TYPE": "UnsignedBigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            512000,
            0,
            0,
            20000,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            35000,
            100000,
            0,
            30000,
            148000,
            100000,
            15000,
            10000,
            200000,
            15000,
            12000,
            50000,
            12000,
            8000,
            10000,
            20500,
            25000,
            15000,
            "<PERSON>",
            15000,
            0,
            0,
            1500000,
            0,
            52500,
            0,
            100000,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "kredit": {
          "TYPE": "UnsignedBigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            12000,
            22000,
            42500,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            "<PERSON>",
            137500,
            0,
            "<PERSON>",
            0,
            2100,
            0,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            209999999979,
            209999999979
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "final_balance": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            837000,
            837000,
            837000,
            857000,
            857000,
            857000,
            845000,
            "<PERSON>",
            780500,
            780500,
            780500,
            815500,
            915500,
            915500,
            945500,
            1093500,
            1193500,
            1208500,
            1218500,
            1418500,
            1433500,
            1445500,
            1495500,
            1507500,
            1515500,
            1525500,
            1546000,
            1571000,
            "<PERSON>",
            1799000,
            1814000,
            1669000,
            1531500,
            3031500,
            2801500,
            2854000,
            2851900,
            2951900,
            -23330381431,
            -230737788862,
            -254071122193,
            -277404455524,
            -487404455503,
            -697404455482,
            -907404455461
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "debet",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "debet",
            "kredit",
            "debet",
            "kredit",
            "debet",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "kredit",
            "kredit"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Timestamp",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-24 08:49:15",
            "2020-12-24 09:52:17",
            "2020-12-24 11:14:31",
            "2020-12-24 11:15:03",
            "2021-01-13 04:03:42",
            "2021-01-13 04:06:50",
            "2021-01-13 04:07:23",
            "2021-01-13 04:25:53",
            "2021-01-13 04:26:07",
            "2021-01-13 04:26:30",
            "2021-01-13 10:36:51",
            "2021-01-13 11:16:38",
            "2021-01-13 11:23:22",
            "2021-01-26 00:41:57",
            "2021-01-26 00:42:25",
            "2021-01-26 00:48:45",
            "2021-01-26 00:51:08",
            "2021-01-26 03:52:02",
            "2021-01-26 10:32:25",
            "2021-01-26 10:34:29",
            "2021-01-26 12:56:40",
            "2021-01-26 23:27:40",
            "2021-01-26 23:44:21",
            "2021-01-29 08:27:28",
            "2021-01-29 10:21:25",
            "2021-01-29 10:21:34",
            "2021-01-29 11:31:42",
            "2021-01-29 11:32:02",
            "2021-01-29 11:45:12",
            "2021-01-29 14:24:24",
            "2021-01-29 15:45:06",
            "2021-01-29 15:52:21",
            "2021-01-30 00:09:03",
            "2021-01-30 00:19:59",
            "2021-01-30 23:32:05",
            "2021-01-31 02:39:19",
            "2021-01-31 04:40:06",
            "2021-01-31 04:40:20",
            "2021-01-31 04:41:02",
            "2021-01-31 04:50:34",
            "2021-01-31 04:56:12",
            "2021-01-31 04:56:39",
            "2021-01-31 04:58:18",
            "2021-01-31 04:59:09",
            "2021-01-31 05:00:30",
            "2021-01-31 05:01:12"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_by": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "material": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            11,
            7,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "material_code": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "BB001",
            "BB002",
            "BB003",
            "BB004",
            "BM001",
            "BM002",
            "BM003",
            "BM004",
            "BM005",
            "BM006",
            "DIO1",
            "QQQ1",
            "RRE1"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "full_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Detergen biru",
            "Detergen pink",
            "Detergen silver",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cup Styrofoam 200ml",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sedotan Plastik",
            "Air mineral",
            "Sedotan Stainless Steel",
            "Mentah 1",
            "QUAQ",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "unit": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "mililiter",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "pcs",
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "pcs",
            "gram",
            "gram",
            "gram"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "volume": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "category": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "bahan",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan",
            "bahan"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "image": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "default.png",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png",
            "default.png"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "price_base": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            14,
            17,
            11,
            21,
            70,
            1500,
            20,
            750,
            9,
            450,
            500,
            230,
            250
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-30 07:45:51",
            "2021-01-30 07:46:07",
            "2021-01-30 07:46:18",
            "2021-01-30 07:46:37",
            "2020-12-23 02:56:49",
            "2020-12-23 02:57:18",
            "2020-12-23 02:57:49",
            "2020-12-23 02:58:09",
            "2020-12-28 01:32:57",
            "2020-12-28 01:48:26",
            "2021-01-13 15:47:27",
            "2021-01-11 13:03:54",
            "2021-01-12 03:51:09"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "material_inventory": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "material_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            4,
            3,
            6,
            2,
            7,
            1,
            5,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "quantity": {
          "TYPE": "UnsignedBigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            9990874,
            9699109,
            109,
            10014890,
            1008,
            9473414,
            906,
            0,
            0,
            "<PERSON>",
            468071,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            33258594755
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "critical_point": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-27 14:54:12",
            "2020-12-27 14:54:18",
            "2020-12-28 01:48:26",
            "2021-01-11 12:00:55",
            "2021-01-11 13:03:54",
            "2021-01-11 13:06:55",
            "2021-01-11 13:07:15",
            "2021-01-12 03:51:09",
            "2021-01-13 15:47:27",
            "2021-01-30 07:45:51",
            "2021-01-30 07:46:07",
            "2021-01-30 07:46:18",
            "2021-01-30 07:46:37"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "updated_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 09:06:21",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 09:39:19",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:00",
            null,
            null,
            "2021-01-31 07:04:16",
            "2021-01-31 07:12:42",
            "2021-01-31 07:03:22",
            "2021-01-31 12:01:12"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_by": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "updated_by": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "material_mutation": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            11,
            2,
            12,
            3,
            13,
            4,
            14,
            5,
            15,
            6,
            16,
            7,
            17,
            8,
            18,
            67,
            9,
            68,
            10,
            69,
            70,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            105,
            106,
            107,
            108,
            109,
            110,
            111,
            112,
            113,
            114,
            115,
            116,
            117,
            118,
            119,
            120,
            121,
            122,
            123,
            124,
            125,
            126,
            127,
            128,
            129,
            130,
            131,
            132,
            133,
            134,
            135,
            136,
            137,
            138,
            139,
            140,
            141,
            142,
            143,
            144,
            145,
            146,
            147,
            148,
            149,
            150,
            151,
            169,
            170,
            171,
            172,
            173,
            174,
            175,
            176,
            177
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "material_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            4,
            2,
            3,
            1,
            2,
            5,
            1,
            6,
            4,
            2,
            3,
            7,
            2,
            7,
            1,
            6,
            6,
            4,
            7,
            3,
            3,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            5,
            4,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            15,
            14,
            13,
            13,
            12,
            15,
            14,
            13,
            12,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            12,
            14,
            15,
            13,
            14,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            13,
            14,
            12,
            12,
            13,
            13,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            6,
            7,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15,
            15
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "store_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mutation_code": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "000001/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000001/MAT/MSK/11/01/2021",
            "000002/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000002/MAT/MSK/11/01/2021",
            "000003/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000003/MAT/MSK/11/01/2021",
            "000004/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000004/MAT/MSK/11/01/2021",
            "000005/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000005/MAT/MSK/11/01/2021",
            "000006/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000006/MAT/MSK/11/01/2021",
            "000007/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000007/MAT/MSK/12/01/2021",
            "000008/MAT/KEL/24/12/2020",
            "000008/MAT/MSK/12/01/2021",
            "000009/MAT/KEL/12/01/2021",
            "000009/MAT/MSK/27/12/2020",
            "000010/MAT/KEL/12/01/2021",
            "000010/MAT/MSK/27/12/2020",
            "000011/MAT/MSK/12/01/2021",
            "000012/MAT/MSK/12/01/2021",
            "000013/MAT/KEL/12/01/2021",
            "000014/MAT/KEL/12/01/2021",
            "000015/MAT/KEL/12/01/2021",
            "000016/MAT/KEL/12/01/2021",
            "000017/MAT/KEL/26/01/2021",
            "000018/MAT/KEL/26/01/2021",
            "000019/MAT/KEL/26/01/2021",
            "000020/MAT/MSK/26/01/2021",
            "000021/MAT/MSK/26/01/2021",
            "000022/MAT/MSK/26/01/2021",
            "000023/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000024/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000025/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000026/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000027/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000028/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000029/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000030/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000031/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000032/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000033/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000034/MAT/KEL/29/01/2021",
            "000035/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000036/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000037/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000038/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000039/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000040/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000041/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000042/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000043/MAT/MSK/30/01/2021",
            "000044/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000045/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000046/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000047/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000048/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000049/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000050/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000051/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000052/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000053/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000054/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000055/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000056/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000057/MAT/KEL/30/01/2021",
            "000058/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000059/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000060/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000061/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000062/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000063/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000064/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000065/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000066/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000067/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000068/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000069/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000070/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000071/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000072/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000073/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000074/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000075/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000076/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000077/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000078/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000079/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000080/MAT/KEL/31/01/2021",
            "000081/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000082/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000083/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000084/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000085/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000086/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000087/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000088/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000089/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021",
            "000090/MAT/MSK/31/01/2021"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "quantity": {
          "TYPE": "UnsignedBigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            2,
            101,
            60,
            155,
            2,
            16,
            200,
            11,
            12,
            15,
            600,
            4,
            12,
            254,
            1440,
            123,
            15,
            100,
            30,
            100,
            10000,
            500000,
            12000,
            100,
            5000,
            100,
            10,
            10,
            20,
            1000,
            1000,
            25000,
            1000,
            10,
            300,
            10,
            300,
            3,
            90,
            3,
            1440,
            12,
            600,
            12,
            10000,
            10000,
            10000,
            10000,
            10000,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            44000,
            51000,
            "<PERSON>",
            124000,
            191250,
            68750,
            121250,
            153750,
            20000,
            20000,
            20000,
            "<PERSON>",
            125000,
            455000,
            "<PERSON>",
            125000,
            211,
            125,
            1200,
            148140,
            9872,
            96,
            9999999,
            9999999,
            9999999,
            9999999,
            "<PERSON>",
            10000,
            300000,
            10000,
            100,
            100,
            200,
            12000,
            100,
            5000,
            100,
            100,
            1000,
            100,
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>",
            "<UK_NHS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mutation_type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk",
            "masuk"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_at": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-11 12:00:55",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-11 13:06:56",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-11 13:07:15",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-11 13:07:23",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-11 13:07:31",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-11 13:07:42",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-12 01:12:25",
            "2020-12-24 15:49:14",
            "2021-01-12 02:59:49",
            "2021-01-12 03:35:56",
            "2020-12-27 14:54:12",
            "2021-01-12 03:35:56",
            "2020-12-27 14:54:18",
            "2021-01-12 03:45:06",
            "2021-01-12 03:56:31",
            "2021-01-12 03:58:47",
            "2021-01-12 03:58:47",
            "2021-01-12 03:58:47",
            "2021-01-12 03:58:47",
            "2021-01-26 11:55:34",
            "2021-01-26 11:55:34",
            "2021-01-26 11:55:34",
            "2021-01-26 12:09:48",
            "2021-01-26 12:09:58",
            "2021-01-26 12:10:09",
            "2021-01-29 14:47:56",
            "2021-01-29 14:47:56",
            "2021-01-29 14:47:56",
            "2021-01-29 14:47:56",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:45",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:45",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:45",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:45",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:56",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:56",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:56",
            "2021-01-29 15:20:56",
            "2021-01-30 09:53:25",
            "2021-01-30 09:53:31",
            "2021-01-30 09:53:39",
            "2021-01-30 09:53:50",
            "2021-01-30 09:54:14",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:15",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:22",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:28",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:38",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:46",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:46",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:46",
            "2021-01-30 09:56:46",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:02",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:02",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:02",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:02",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:13",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:13",
            "2021-01-30 09:57:13",
            "2021-01-30 11:27:46",
            "2021-01-30 11:27:46",
            "2021-01-30 11:27:54",
            "2021-01-31 06:35:36",
            "2021-01-31 06:35:36",
            "2021-01-31 07:03:22",
            "2021-01-31 07:03:22",
            "2021-01-31 07:03:57",
            "2021-01-31 07:04:16",
            "2021-01-31 07:06:30",
            "2021-01-31 07:12:42",
            "2021-01-31 07:34:50",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:02",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:11",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:22",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:46",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:46",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:46",
            "2021-01-31 07:35:46",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:00",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:00",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:00",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 07:36:08",
            "2021-01-31 09:06:22",
            "2021-01-31 09:39:19",
            "2021-01-31 11:40:19",
            "2021-01-31 11:50:34",
            "2021-01-31 11:56:12",
            "2021-01-31 11:56:39",
            "2021-01-31 11:58:18",
            "2021-01-31 11:59:09",
            "2021-01-31 12:00:30",
            "2021-01-31 12:01:12"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "created_by": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "gudang1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "is_deleted": {
          "TYPE": "TinyInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
