{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/somanyadav/NU-Connect/blob/74492b527d4c33833dd79b1b880324666e28cfa9/FoodZone/foodorder.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "contact": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "CHANDAN KUMAR",
            "CHANDAN KUMAR",
            "BIRJU KUMAR",
            "CHANDAN KUMAR"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Mobile": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Subject": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "sa",
            "sa",
            "asd",
            "asd"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Message": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "",
            "<PERSON>",
            "hfgdsfsx"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "customer": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "username": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "birju",
            "<PERSON>",
            "nidha",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "fullname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "BIRJU KUMAR",
            "CHANDAN KUMAR",
            "nidha",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "998696572",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Pondicherry University, SRK HOSTEL ROOM NUMBER-59,",
            "Pondicherry University, SRK HOSTEL ROOM NUMBER-59,",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "food": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "F_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            65,
            66,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Spring Rolls",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tea",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tea",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Puff",
            "Pizza",
            "French Fries",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pizza",
            "French Fries",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "price": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            40,
            60,
            99,
            80,
            65,
            75,
            25,
            20,
            85,
            25,
            20,
            40,
            45,
            35,
            200,
            60,
            35,
            200,
            75,
            45
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Juicy Masala Paneer Kathi Roll loaded with Masala Paneer chunks, onion & Mayo.",
            "Try Meurig - A whole Pomfret fish grilled with tangy marination & served with grilled onions and tomatoes.",
            "Lose all senses over this very delicious chocolate hazelnut truffle.",
            "Oreo Shake - a perfect party sweet treat.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "concentrated coffee made by forcing pressurized water through finely ground coffee beans.",
            "The simple elixir of tea is of our natural world.",
            "it",
            "concentrated coffee made by forcing pressurized water through finely ground coffee beans.",
            "The simple elixir of tea is of our natural world.",
            "Cocktail Crispy Samosa..",
            "it gives whole new dimension even to the most boring or dull vegetable",
            "Vegetable Puff, a snack with crisp-n-flaky outer layer and mixed vegetables stuffing",
            "Good and Tasty ",
            "Pure Veg and Tasty.",
            "Pure Vegetable and Tasty.",
            "Pure Vegetable and Tasty.",
            "Pure Veg and Tasty.",
            "TASTY"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "R_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            6,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "images_path": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "images/Masala_Paneer_Kathi_Roll.jpg",
            "images/Meurig.jpg",
            "images/Chocolate_Hazelnut_Truffle.jpg",
            "images/Happy_Happy_Choco_Chip_Shake.jpg",
            "images/Spring_Rolls.jpg",
            "images/Baahubali_Thali.jpg",
            "images/coffee.jpg",
            "images/tea.jpg",
            "images/paneer pakora.jpg",
            "images/coffee.jpg",
            "images/tea.jpg",
            "images/samosa.jpg",
            "images/paneer pakora.jpg",
            "images/puff.jpg",
            "Pizza.jpg",
            "frenchfries.jpg",
            "images/Pakora.jpg",
            "images/Pizza.jpg",
            "images/frenchfries.jpg",
            "images/Pakora.jpg"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "options": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "ENABLE",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "DISABLE",
            "DISABLE",
            "DISABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "DISABLE",
            "DISABLE",
            "DISABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE",
            "ENABLE"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "R_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "restaurants",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "R_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "manager": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "username": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "aditi068",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "fullname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "DHIRAJ kUMAR",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Goa",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Pondicherry University, SRK HOSTEL ROOM NUMBER-59,",
            "Pondicherry. Le cafe",
            "Bihar"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "aditi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "username"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "orders": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "order_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50,
            51,
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "F_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            58,
            61,
            61,
            65,
            58,
            65,
            58,
            65,
            60,
            59,
            60,
            65,
            59,
            58,
            60,
            65,
            66,
            59,
            63,
            68,
            62,
            68,
            62,
            65,
            68,
            59,
            58,
            59,
            58,
            60,
            59,
            61,
            60,
            59,
            61,
            62,
            72,
            78,
            78,
            73,
            77,
            70,
            60,
            70,
            60,
            70,
            60,
            60,
            62,
            70,
            73,
            70,
            60,
            69,
            62,
            70,
            70,
            60,
            59,
            61,
            71,
            70,
            72,
            71,
            70,
            72,
            60,
            71
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "foodname": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tea",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Spring Rolls",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Spring Rolls",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Spring Rolls",
            "<PERSON>",
            "French Fries",
            "French Fries",
            "Puff",
            "Pizza",
            "Tea",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "Tea",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "Tea",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "Spring Rolls",
            "Tea",
            "Puff",
            "Tea",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Spring Rolls",
            "Tea",
            "Tea",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tea",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tea",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chocolate Hazelnut Truffle",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "price": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            40,
            80,
            80,
            25,
            40,
            25,
            40,
            25,
            99,
            60,
            99,
            25,
            60,
            40,
            99,
            25,
            20,
            60,
            75,
            75,
            65,
            75,
            65,
            25,
            75,
            60,
            40,
            60,
            40,
            99,
            60,
            80,
            99,
            60,
            80,
            65,
            45,
            75,
            75,
            35,
            200,
            20,
            99,
            20,
            99,
            20,
            99,
            99,
            65,
            20,
            35,
            20,
            99,
            25,
            65,
            20,
            20,
            99,
            60,
            80,
            40,
            20,
            45,
            40,
            20,
            45,
            99,
            40
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "quantity": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            2,
            4,
            7,
            2,
            7,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            4,
            1,
            4,
            1,
            7,
            5,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            6,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            6,
            7,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            4,
            6,
            5,
            3,
            1,
            5,
            7,
            1,
            4,
            1,
            1,
            6,
            1,
            3,
            4,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            2,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "order_date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-03",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-05",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-15",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-16",
            "2019-03-25",
            "2019-03-25",
            "2019-03-25",
            "2019-03-25",
            "2019-03-30",
            "2019-03-30",
            "2019-03-30",
            "2019-04-01",
            "2019-04-01",
            "2019-04-01",
            "2019-04-01",
            "2019-04-02",
            "2019-04-02",
            "2019-04-17",
            "2019-04-17",
            "2019-04-17",
            "2019-04-17",
            "2019-04-17",
            "2019-04-17",
            "2019-04-18",
            "2019-04-18"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "username": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "birju",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "R_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            4,
            1,
            4,
            1,
            4,
            3,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            2,
            1,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            2,
            3,
            6,
            2,
            6,
            2,
            4,
            6,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            3,
            2,
            1,
            3,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            2,
            3,
            2,
            3,
            3,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            2
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "restaurants": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "R_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "contact": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "M_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "M_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "manager",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "username"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}