{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/ytxal23/SGS-Web-and-Dent.I.St-C-.NET-/blob/19be50b0aa613efb9333b527811f2dfa406887f0/MJCR-ODC/dbdental.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "APACHE-2.0",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "tbldiscount": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "intDiscount": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strDiscountName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "No Discount",
            "Senior Discount",
            "Student Discount",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Special Ako",
            "PWD Discount",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Discount daw",
            "Loyalty",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dblDiscountPercentage": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            34,
            20,
            50,
            20,
            50,
            12,
            2,
            12,
            12
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strDiscountDesc": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Two year consistent regular patients",
            "Senior citizens",
            "Others and others",
            "Relatives ko",
            "<PERSON>",
            "People with Disability and etc",
            "trip ko eh",
            "kjakldsjfasl",
            "123",
            "Regular patients"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strStatus": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tblemployee": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "charEmpID": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Emp001",
            "Emp002",
            "Emp003",
            "Emp004",
            "Emp005",
            "Emp006",
            "Emp007",
            "Emp008",
            "Emp009",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strEmpFirst": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Les",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kevin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Henry",
            "Fe",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Alex"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strEmpMid": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Lest",
            "Lopez",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ostia",
            "c",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Hapit",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kakaka",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strEmpLast": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "salud",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "KAte",
            "Uy"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strImage": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "C://Users//Laxteroid//Pictures//TaeTae1.jpg",
            "C://Users//Laxteroid//Pictures//Camera Roll//WIN_20170718_191613.JPG",
            "C://Users//Laxteroid//Pictures//TaeTae1.jpg",
            "C://Users//Laxteroid//Pictures//Camera Roll//WIN_20170718_191613.JPG",
            "C://Users//Laxteroid//Pictures//Camera Roll//WIN_20170718_191613.JPG",
            "C://Users//Laxteroid//Pictures//Camera Roll//WIN_20170718_191613.JPG"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dtmEmpBirthdate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1999-12-04",
            "1990-07-13",
            "1999-10-18",
            "1999-12-04",
            "1999-09-16",
            "1984-06-12",
            "1993-05-10",
            "1957-10-28",
            "1984-06-12",
            "1999-09-29"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "charContact": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "80918381023",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strEmpAddress": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Pasig",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "dsakdjalkdkl",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Pasig",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strEmpGender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Male"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "intEmpRoleID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            3,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            3,
            1,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strLicense": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "17161616166161",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strUsername": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "admin",
            "dent1",
            "sect1",
            "les02",
            "kcs",
            "cjare",
            "adm1",
            "fedcny",
            "kakaka",
            "dent2"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPassword": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "123",
            "123",
            "123",
            "123",
            "kcs",
            "3244185981728979115075721453575112",
            "123",
            "123123",
            "123",
            "123"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strEmpStatus": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tblmodule": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "intModuleID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strModuleName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Employee Module",
            "Set Schedule Module",
            "Treatment Module",
            "Category Module",
            "Specialization Module",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Request Appointment Module",
            "Approve Appointment Module",
            "Dental Treatment Module",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Reports Module",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Module Permission",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tax and Fee Module",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strModuleDesc": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by",
            "Accessed by"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "intModuleID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tblpatient": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "charPatientID": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientFirst": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Ellen",
            "kevin",
            "Wale",
            "Kris",
            "Jae",
            "James",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientMid": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "T",
            "c",
            "Dee",
            "<PERSON>",
            "T",
            "T",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientLast": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Minn",
            "salud",
            "Salud",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Minn",
            "Minn",
            "Ford"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientAddress": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Daegu",
            "asd",
            "zxZX",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pasig",
            "Daegu",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dtmpatientBirthdate": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1997-06-23",
            "1999-09-16",
            "1997-09-17",
            "2010-02-02",
            "1995-03-09",
            "1994-06-14",
            "1996-04-04"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientGender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Female",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male",
            "Male"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientContact": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strPatientEmail": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strHistory": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "charPatientID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tblreceiptheader": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "strReceiptNo": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "BIL021",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "BIL024",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strfkTransactionID": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "datDate": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2017-09-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-19 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-09-24 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-04 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-05 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-05 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-06 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-06 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-06 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-06 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-09 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-13 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-14 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-18 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-18 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-18 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-14 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-14 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-15 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-15 00:00:00",
            "2017-12-05 00:00:00",
            "2018-01-14 00:00:00",
            "2018-01-21 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "datDueDate": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2017-10-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-19 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-21 00:00:00",
            "2017-10-24 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-03 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-04 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-04 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-05 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-05 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-05 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-05 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-08 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-12 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-13 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-17 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-13 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-13 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-14 00:00:00",
            "2017-11-14 00:00:00",
            "2018-01-04 00:00:00",
            "2018-02-13 00:00:00",
            "2018-02-20 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "decAmountToPay": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "89251.96",
            "101090.00",
            "40336.80",
            "44056.80",
            "40336.80",
            "40336.80",
            "40584.80",
            "40336.80",
            "809.60",
            "1321.60",
            "1495.20",
            "11324.00",
            "11448.00",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "1424.74",
            "2442.82",
            "22400.00",
            "664.52",
            "5803.33",
            "882.52",
            "11890.20",
            "12031.53",
            "5786.40",
            "1234.33",
            "833.46",
            "833.46",
            "5686.80",
            "525.53",
            "525.53"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "intfkDiscount": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            4,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            5,
            0,
            0,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            2,
            0,
            0,
            3,
            1,
            1
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strBillStat": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tblspecialization": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "intSpecID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSpecName": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "General Dentist",
            "Orthodontist"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSpecDesc": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Regular check-ups and operations",
            "Rearrangement of teeth"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "intSpecID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tblteeth": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "strToothCode": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00020",
            "TO00021",
            "TO00022",
            "TO00023",
            "TO00024",
            "TO00025",
            "TO00026",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00028",
            "TO00029",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00031",
            "TO00032",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00037",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00041",
            "TO00042",
            "TO00043",
            "TO00044",
            "TO00045",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00050",
            "TO00051",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00053",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00055",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00060",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00064",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00070",
            "TO00071",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00076",
            "TO00077",
            "TO00078",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00080",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00087",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO001",
            "TO00100",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00125",
            "TO00126",
            "TO00127",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00132",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00135",
            "TO00136",
            "TO00137",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00146",
            "TO00147",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00155",
            "TO00156",
            "TO00157",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00172",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00175",
            "TO00176",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00181",
            "TO00182",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00184",
            "TO00185",
            "TO00186",
            "TO00187",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00191",
            "TO00192",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00194",
            "TO00195",
            "TO00196",
            "TO00197",
            "TO00198",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00201",
            "TO00202",
            "TO00203",
            "TO00204",
            "TO00205",
            "TO00206",
            "TO00207",
            "TO00208",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00211",
            "TO00212",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00214",
            "TO00215",
            "TO00216",
            "TO00217",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00245",
            "TO00246",
            "TO00247",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00252",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00255",
            "TO00256",
            "TO00257",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00261",
            "TO00262",
            "TO00263",
            "TO00264",
            "TO00265",
            "TO00266",
            "TO00267",
            "TO00288",
            "TO00289",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00291",
            "TO00292",
            "TO00293",
            "TO00294",
            "TO00295",
            "TO00296",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00334",
            "TO00335",
            "TO00336",
            "TO00337",
            "TO00338",
            "TO00339",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00341",
            "TO00342",
            "TO00343",
            "TO00344",
            "TO00345",
            "TO00346",
            "TO00347",
            "TO00348",
            "TO00349",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00355",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00357",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00361",
            "TO00362",
            "TO00363",
            "TO00364",
            "TO00365",
            "TO00366",
            "TO00367",
            "TO00368",
            "TO00369",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00371",
            "TO00372",
            "TO00373",
            "TO00374",
            "TO00375",
            "TO00376",
            "TO00377",
            "TO00378",
            "TO00379",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "TO00382",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strToothNumber": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "1",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "14",
            "19",
            "8",
            "9",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "3",
            "14",
            "19",
            "30",
            "24",
            "25",
            "8",
            "26",
            "9",
            "7",
            "23",
            "10",
            "22",
            "13",
            "22",
            "13",
            "27",
            "5",
            "4",
            "12",
            "6",
            "31",
            "11",
            "20",
            "18",
            "29",
            "2",
            "16",
            "15",
            "17",
            "1",
            "32",
            "1",
            "5",
            "6",
            "10",
            "11",
            "12",
            "15",
            "16",
            "17",
            "20",
            "28",
            "51",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "7",
            "8",
            "9",
            "10",
            "11",
            "12",
            "13",
            "14",
            "15",
            "16",
            "17",
            "18",
            "19",
            "20",
            "52",
            "53",
            "54",
            "55",
            "56",
            "57",
            "58",
            "59",
            "60",
            "61",
            "62",
            "63",
            "64",
            "65",
            "66",
            "67",
            "68",
            "69",
            "70",
            "71",
            "72",
            "73",
            "74",
            "75",
            "76",
            "77",
            "78",
            "79",
            "81",
            "82"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSurface1": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSurface2": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSurface3": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSurface4": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strSurface5": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "not exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist",
            "exist"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "charPatientID": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strToothType": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Baby",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Adult",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Baby",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary",
            "Supernumerary"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "strStatus": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "InActive",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "InActive",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active",
            "Active"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "charPatientID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "tblpatient",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "charPatientID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "NoAction",
          "ON_UPDATE": "NoAction"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "tbltransactionheader": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "strTransactionID": {
          "TYPE": "Char",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
