{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/foxtrotzulu94/EchelonPlanner/blob/6408c615f933a792cacd99f6e2c8cc59d79bfdd5/misc/packaging/echelon_db_backup.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "app_academicprogram": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "credits": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "app_course": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            " FLIGHT CONTROL SYSTEMS",
            "<PERSON>",
            " INTRODUCTION TO CULTURE",
            " TECHNOLOGY & CONTEMP. ART",
            " ELEMENTARY GENETICS",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " MOLECULAR & GENERAL GENETICS",
            " DISCOVERING BIOTECHNOLOGY",
            " INTRO ANALYTICAL CHEMISTRY I",
            "<PERSON>",
            " PHYS.CHEM I:THERMODYNAMICS",
            " INTRO CLASSICAL ARCHAEOLOGY",
            " INTRO TO REAL-TIME SYSTEMS",
            " MATH. FOR COMPUTER SCIENCE",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " C++ ADVANCED PROGRAM DESIGN",
            " OPERATING SYSTEMS",
            " PRIN./PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES",
            " DATA STRUCTURES + ALGORITHMS",
            " DATABASES",
            " ELEMENTARY NUMERICAL METHODS",
            " COMPUTER GRAPHICS",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " MULTICORE PROGRAMMING",
            " PARALLEL PROGRAMMING",
            " COMPILER DESIGN",
            " DATA COMM + COMP NETWORKS",
            " DESIGN+ANALYSIS/ALGORITHMS",
            " ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE",
            " PATTERN RECOGNITION",
            " INTELLIGENT SYSTEMS",
            " ADVANCED GAME DEVELOPMENT",
            " ANIMATION FOR COMPUTER GAMES",
            " IMAGE PROCESSING",
            " INFO. RETRIEVAL & WEB SEARCH",
            " MASS COMMUNICATION",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " INTRODUCTION-MACROECONOMICS",
            " INTRO TO PHILOSOPHY OF EDUC",
            " PRINCIPLES OF ELEC. ENGG.",
            " TECH. WRITING + COMMUNIC N.",
            " INN.&CRITICL; THKNG SCI&TECH;",
            " PROFESS L. PRACTICE+RESPONS.",
            " SUSTAIN.DEV.+ENVIRO.STEWART.",
            " APP.ORDINARY DIFF.EQUATIONS",
            " APPLIED ADVANCED CALCULUS",
            " ENGR.MGMT.PRINCIP.+ECONOMICS",
            " PROBABILITY+STATISTICS/ENGR.",
            " NUMERICAL METHODS IN ENGR",
            " IMPACT/TECHNOLOGY ON SOCIETY",
            " SPECIAL TECHNICAL REPORT",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " LE CINEMA QUEBECOIS",
            " CANADIAN ENVIRONM TAL ISSUES",
            " GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUES",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            " INTRO:EUROPEAN 1789-PRESENT",
            "<PERSON>",
            " FILM IN HISTORY",
            " THE 20TH C: GLOBAL HISTORY",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " SOCIOLINGUISTICS",
            " PROBLEMS OF PHILOSOPHY",
            " CRITICAL THINKING",
            "<PERSON>",
            " BIOMEDICAL ETHICS",
            "<PERSON>",
            " CONTEMPORARY ETHICAL THEORY",
            " OPTICS",
            " ELECTRICITY & MAGNETISM I",
            " THERMODYNAMICS",
            " ELECTRICITY & MAGNETISM II",
            " INTRO TO POLITICAL SCIENCE",
            " RELIGIONS OF THE WEST",
            "<LOCATION>",
            " SELF/OTHER: IDTY & ETHICS",
            " JUSTICE & SOCIAL CONFLICT",
            " PUBLIC POLICY &INTEREST;",
            " ECON FOR PUB POL&COM; DEV",
            " INTRODUCTION TO SOCIETY",
            " SYSTEM HARDWARE",
            " WEB PROGRAMMING",
            " SYSTEM HARDWARE LAB",
            " INFORMATION SYSTEMS SECURITY",
            " INTRO TO FML MTHDS FOR SOEN",
            " SOFTWARE PROCESS",
            " SW REQUIREMENTS + SPECS.",
            " S.W. ARCHITECURE & DESIGN I",
            " S.W. ARCHITECURE & DESIGN II",
            " S.W. TESTING VERIF & QA",
            " USER INTERFACE DESIGN",
            " MGMT+QUALITY CTRL./SW DEV.",
            " CONTROL SYSTEMS+APPLICATIONS",
            " WEB-BASED ENTER. APP DESIGN",
            " SOFTWARE ENGR. TEAM PROJECT",
            " EMBEDDED SYSTEMS/SOFTWARE",
            " DISTRIBUTED SYSTEMS",
            " WEB SERVICES & APPLICATIONS",
            " CAPSTONE SW ENGR DESIGN PROJ",
            " INTRO. TO BIBLICAL STUDIES",
            " INTRO.TO CHRISTIAN ETHICS",
            " RELG. PLURALISM/SECULAR CULT",
            " INTRO TO HIST. PERSP. IN WS",
            " INTRO CONT.  PERSP.  IN WS"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "department": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "AERO",
            "AHSC",
            "ANTH",
            "ARTH",
            "BIOL",
            "BIOL",
            "BIOL",
            "CHEM",
            "CHEM",
            "CHEM",
            "CHEM",
            "CLAS",
            "COEN",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMP",
            "COMS",
            "ECON",
            "ECON",
            "EDUC",
            "ELEC",
            "ENCS",
            "ENCS",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "ENGR",
            "FLIT",
            "FMST",
            "FMST",
            "GEOG",
            "GEOG",
            "GEOG",
            "GEOG",
            "HIST",
            "HIST",
            "HIST",
            "HIST",
            "HIST",
            "INST",
            "LING",
            "LING",
            "PHIL",
            "PHIL",
            "PHIL",
            "PHIL",
            "PHIL",
            "PHIL",
            "PHYS",
            "PHYS",
            "PHYS",
            "PHYS",
            "POLI",
            "RELI",
            "RELI",
            "RELI",
            "RELI",
            "SCPA",
            "SCPA",
            "SOCI",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "SOEN",
            "THEO",
            "THEO",
            "THEO",
            "WSDB",
            "WSDB"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "number": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            480,
            242,
            202,
            353,
            206,
            226,
            261,
            209,
            217,
            221,
            234,
            266,
            320,
            232,
            248,
            249,
            335,
            345,
            346,
            348,
            352,
            353,
            361,
            371,
            376,
            426,
            428,
            442,
            445,
            465,
            472,
            473,
            474,
            476,
            477,
            478,
            479,
            360,
            201,
            203,
            230,
            275,
            282,
            483,
            201,
            202,
            213,
            233,
            301,
            371,
            391,
            392,
            411,
            230,
            214,
            215,
            203,
            204,
            210,
            220,
            201,
            202,
            205,
            281,
            283,
            250,
            222,
            300,
            201,
            210,
            232,
            235,
            275,
            330,
            252,
            253,
            334,
            354,
            202,
            214,
            215,
            310,
            312,
            201,
            215,
            203,
            228,
            287,
            298,
            321,
            331,
            341,
            342,
            343,
            344,
            345,
            357,
            384,
            385,
            387,
            390,
            422,
            423,
            487,
            490,
            202,
            204,
            233,
            290,
            291
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "deptnum": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "ANTH202",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "COMP335",
            "COMP345",
            "COMP346",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "COMP361",
            "COMP371",
            "COMP376",
            "COMP426",
            "<PERSON>",
            "COMP442",
            "COMP445",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "COMS360",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "FMST214",
            "FMST215",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "GEOG210",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "PHIL210",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "RELI214",
            "RELI215",
            "<PERSON>",
            "RELI312",
            "SCPA201",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "THEO202",
            "THEO204",
            "<PERSON>",
            "WSDB290",
            "WSDB291"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "type": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "credits": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            3.5,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3.5,
            3,
            3,
            1.5,
            1.5,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            1.5,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            3,
            1.5,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3.5,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            4,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "yearSpan": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15",
            "14-15"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "deptnum"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "app_option": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "option": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "type": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "academicprogram_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "course_id": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "course_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "app_course",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "deptnum"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "academicprogram_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "app_academicprogram",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "academicprogram_id"
        ],
        [
          "course_id"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "app_studentrecord": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "GPA": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "currentStanding": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "currentCredits": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "remainingCredits": {
          "TYPE": "Double",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "academicProgram_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "mainSchedule_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "academicProgram_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "app_academicprogram",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "academicProgram_id"
        ],
        [
          "mainSchedule_id"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "django_admin_log": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "action_time": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "object_id": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "object_repr": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "action_flag": {
          "TYPE": "UnsignedSmallInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "change_message": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "content_type_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "content_type_id"
        ],
        [
          "user_id"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "django_session": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "session_key": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "62u2kyytkr2y70upqzps8xk4f4cbcg4p",
            "999rdl93jv84fkzxibgn7h47jvwm75b5",
            "hsnm8x7he5ye70em7gju1i1pe7416uee",
            "m0v22wbm61n41holcs55t6lxe2qpo0yh",
            "oivtjppe7aruac47inyr0k9r7k1ybedw"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "session_data": {
          "TYPE": "longtext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "YjkzNDFjNDRlNWU2NTg4M2I2YjI1NjRhZjQ1ZjU0YzRhOWM1MzE4YTp7Il9hdXRoX3VzZXJfaWQiOjIsIl9hdXRoX3VzZXJfaGFzaCI6ImQ2ZGY5MDQwMGZjMjY0MzBiNWExZDlkM2YwMjAxNjU2ZTBmNjEyZTkiLCJfYXV0aF91c2VyX2JhY2tlbmQiOiJkamFuZ28uY29udHJpYi5hdXRoLmJhY2tlbmRzLk1vZGVsQmFja2VuZCJ9",
            "YTU4MGE5ODg5NzU0OGIyZjYxZGY3MGJhOTIxMWNlNTlkNGQzYjhhZTp7Il9hdXRoX3VzZXJfaGFzaCI6ImQ2ZGY5MDQwMGZjMjY0MzBiNWExZDlkM2YwMjAxNjU2ZTBmNjEyZTkiLCJfYXV0aF91c2VyX2JhY2tlbmQiOiJkamFuZ28uY29udHJpYi5hdXRoLmJhY2tlbmRzLk1vZGVsQmFja2VuZCIsIl9hdXRoX3VzZXJfaWQiOjJ9",
            "NDA4ZGZhMTQ3MjY3ZjRhOTIwNzA1MmQ1OTA3MmY5NTVlMjkyZTRhNDp7Il9hdXRoX3VzZXJfYmFja2VuZCI6ImRqYW5nby5jb250cmliLmF1dGguYmFja2VuZHMuTW9kZWxCYWNrZW5kIiwiX2F1dGhfdXNlcl9oYXNoIjoiZDZkZjkwNDAwZmMyNjQzMGI1YTFkOWQzZjAyMDE2NTZlMGY2MTJlOSIsIl9hdXRoX3VzZXJfaWQiOjJ9",
            "NTFlNWZhZTE2NDg2MWU4N2EyZTNhNTBjNzgyYmI1OGQyYTVkZTM0Mzp7Il9hdXRoX3VzZXJfaWQiOjIsIl9hdXRoX3VzZXJfYmFja2VuZCI6ImRqYW5nby5jb250cmliLmF1dGguYmFja2VuZHMuTW9kZWxCYWNrZW5kIiwiX2F1dGhfdXNlcl9oYXNoIjoiZDZkZjkwNDAwZmMyNjQzMGI1YTFkOWQzZjAyMDE2NTZlMGY2MTJlOSJ9",
            "YThmMjhhYzM5OTQ5MWY2ZjM4OWUwM2EwYWU4OTgwNTA1ODQ0NjJlNDp7Il9hdXRoX3VzZXJfYmFja2VuZCI6ImRqYW5nby5jb250cmliLmF1dGguYmFja2VuZHMuTW9kZWxCYWNrZW5kIiwiX2F1dGhfdXNlcl9pZCI6MiwiX2F1dGhfdXNlcl9oYXNoIjoiZDZkZjkwNDAwZmMyNjQzMGI1YTFkOWQzZjAyMDE2NTZlMGY2MTJlOSJ9"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "expire_date": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            "2015-04-13 03:16:56",
            "2015-04-13 01:43:52",
            "2015-04-13 18:44:07",
            "2015-04-13 03:20:56",
            "2015-04-13 19:19:15"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "session_key"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "expire_date"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}