{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/StephanieCzetli/Nanas_Greens/blob/e8ce54bde7efa7441f3026f76c81147a0fbd5e71/data/schema.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "customers": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "customer_Id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "customer_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "address1": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "123 South St.",
            "123 South St.",
            "123 South St.",
            "123 Oregon Pk.",
            "123 President Ave.",
            "123 Fruitville Pk.",
            "123 Roosevelt Blvd."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Georgetown",
            "Lewes"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "state": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE",
            "DE"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "zipCode": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            19709,
            19709,
            19709,
            19320,
            19320,
            19320,
            19335,
            19709,
            19709,
            17601
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "customer_Id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "orders": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "order_Id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "customer_Id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "order_date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-02-14",
            "2020-02-14",
            "2020-02-14",
            "2020-02-15",
            "2020-02-15",
            "2020-02-15",
            "2020-02-16",
            "2020-02-17",
            "2020-02-18",
            "2020-02-18"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "order_status": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Delivered",
            "Delivered",
            "Delivered",
            "Delivered",
            "Delivered",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Delivered",
            "Filled",
            "Filled",
            "Received"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "delivery_date": {
          "TYPE": "Date",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-02-14",
            "2020-02-14",
            "2020-02-14",
            "2020-02-15",
            "2020-02-15",
            "2020-02-15",
            "2020-02-16",
            "2020-02-17",
            "2020-02-17",
            "2020-02-18"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "order_Id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "customer_Id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "customers",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "customer_Id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}