{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/Maxence-M-M/Crime-Data-Management-SQL/blob/75aa9fc3c79f899745210a4ed881776ccbb2c4f9/Crime_database/Criminal_DB.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "Cases": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Case_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Brakage de Quartier",
            "Meutre pour Halloween",
            "Viol durant le COVID",
            "Feminicide",
            "A crazy father",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Pas d alcool",
            "COVID party",
            "Drugs are bad",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Officer": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Paul",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Paul",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Paul",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Opening_Date": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2016-02-02 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2018-03-02 00:00:00",
            "2019-04-09 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-01 00:00:00",
            "2020-04-09 00:00:00",
            "2020-12-12 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2014-04-09 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Closing_Date": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-02-05 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-16 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-16 00:00:00",
            null,
            "2021-01-15 00:00:00",
            null,
            "2020-05-10 00:00:00",
            "2021-12-12 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-05 00:00:00",
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Case_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "crime": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Crime_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Crime_type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Murder",
            "Theft",
            "Theft",
            "Rape",
            "Murder",
            "Assault",
            "Assault",
            "Assault",
            "Assault",
            "Murder",
            "Murder",
            "Murder",
            "Murder",
            "Murder",
            "Theft",
            "Rape",
            "Influence",
            "Unauthorized event",
            "Drug deal",
            "Rape",
            "Rape",
            "Rape",
            "Rape",
            "Rape"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Date_Crime": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2016-01-31 00:00:00",
            "2016-01-31 00:00:00",
            "2016-01-31 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2018-03-02 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-09 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-09 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-09 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-01 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-01 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-01 00:00:00",
            "2020-09-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-12-12 00:00:00",
            "2013-04-08 00:00:00",
            "2014-04-09 00:00:00",
            "2014-04-13 00:00:00",
            "2014-04-18 00:00:00",
            "2014-04-22 00:00:00",
            "2014-04-25 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Case_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            6,
            6,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Crime_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Case_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Cases",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Case_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Case_ID"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Evidence": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Evidence_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Weapon",
            "Weapon",
            "Biological Evidence",
            "Weapon",
            "Biological Evidence",
            "Weapon",
            "Biological Evidence",
            "Drug",
            "Drug",
            "Biological Evidence"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Collected_Date": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-02-02 00:00:00",
            "2019-03-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-04-03 00:00:00",
            "2018-03-03 00:00:00",
            "2018-03-03 00:00:00",
            "2019-04-09 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-02 00:00:00",
            "2013-09-04 00:00:00",
            "2013-09-04 00:00:00",
            "2014-06-09 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Gun",
            "Knife",
            "Sperm",
            "Gun",
            "Sperm",
            "Gun",
            "Sperm",
            "Canabis",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sperm"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Case_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            9,
            9,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Evidence_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Case_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Cases",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Case_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Case_ID"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Judgement": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Judgement_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Court_Type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "First Instance",
            "<PERSON>",
            "First Instance",
            "<PERSON>",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "First Instance",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Judge": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nani",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nani",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bob",
            "Bob",
            "Bob",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nani"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Decision": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Date_Judgement": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-05 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-05 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-03-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-03-04 00:00:00",
            "2020-07-09 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-18 00:00:00",
            "2020-02-05 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-20 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-20 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-20 00:00:00",
            "2020-10-09 00:00:00",
            "2021-02-03 00:00:00",
            "2020-03-05 00:00:00",
            "2021-01-25 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Crime_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            17
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Judgement_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Crime_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "crime",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Crime_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Crime_ID"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Penalty": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Penalty_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Penalty_Type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Jail",
            "Fine",
            "Jail",
            "Fine"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "10 Years",
            "10 Years",
            "20 Years",
            "20 Years",
            "20 Years",
            "20 Years",
            "99 years",
            "99 years",
            "99 years",
            "6 months",
            "10000 Dollars",
            "20 Years",
            "10000 Dollars"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "End_Penalty": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2030-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2030-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2030-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2030-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2030-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2030-02-04 00:00:00",
            "2120-01-20 00:00:00",
            "2120-01-20 00:00:00",
            "2120-01-20 00:00:00",
            "2021-10-03 00:00:00",
            null,
            "2040-03-05 00:00:00",
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Prison_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            1,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            5,
            10,
            10,
            10,
            2,
            null,
            2,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Judgement_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            3,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Penalty_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Judgement_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Judgement",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Judgement_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Prison_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Prison",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Prison_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Prison_ID"
        ],
        [
          "Judgement_ID"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Person": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Person_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "First_Name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Lol",
            "Ines",
            "Seni",
            "Nise",
            "June",
            "May",
            "Maxou",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Paul",
            "Juan",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Christian ",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Bob",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Yse",
            "Jenny",
            "Lars",
            "Chris",
            "Rocio",
            "Laura",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Toni",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Khaja",
            "Julia",
            "Valentina",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Frida",
            "Costanza",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kyra",
            "Raafi",
            "Sair",
            "Paolo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kyra",
            "Raafi",
            "Sair",
            "Paolo"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Last_Name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Ernac",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Maxi",
            "<PERSON>",
            "David",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Studt",
            "Brown",
            "Pant",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nemec",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Zhang",
            "Nemec",
            "Pant",
            "Wang",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lopez",
            "Resag",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Duro",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Studt",
            "Brown",
            "Pant"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Nationality": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "FR",
            "AN",
            "ES",
            "GE",
            "UK",
            "USA",
            "SW",
            "PO",
            "BE",
            "IT",
            "USA",
            "FR",
            "MA",
            "FR",
            "USA",
            "JN",
            "CH",
            "AN",
            "ES",
            "GE",
            "UK",
            "USA",
            "SW",
            "PO",
            "BE",
            "IT",
            "USA",
            "FR",
            "MA",
            "FR",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "USA",
            "ES",
            "GE",
            "SW",
            "PO",
            "BE",
            "USA",
            "ES",
            "GE",
            "SW",
            "PO"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Gender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "F",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M",
            "F",
            "M",
            "M",
            "M"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Adress": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "591 Memorial Dr, Chicopee MA 1020",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "137 Teaticket Hwy, East Falmouth MA 2536",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "677 Timpany Blvd, Gardner MA 1440",
            "337 Russell St, Hadley MA 1035",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "555 East Main St, Orange MA 1364",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "262 Swansea Mall Dr, Swansea MA 2777",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "550 Providence Hwy, Walpole MA 2081",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "3005 Cranberry Hwy Rt 6 28, Wareham MA 2538",
            "250 Rt 59, Airmont NY 10901",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Birth": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "1996-04-23 00:00:00",
            "1986-05-14 00:00:00",
            "1998-03-02 00:00:00",
            "1996-04-03 00:00:00",
            "1956-03-14 00:00:00",
            "1998-02-12 00:00:00",
            "1996-02-28 00:00:00",
            "1946-05-14 00:00:00",
            "1978-03-11 00:00:00",
            "1989-02-03 00:00:00",
            "1974-03-04 00:00:00",
            "1988-12-03 00:00:00",
            "1945-02-27 00:00:00",
            "1970-02-05 00:00:00",
            "1983-03-04 00:00:00",
            "1969-03-21 00:00:00",
            "1989-04-23 00:00:00",
            "1999-03-02 00:00:00",
            "1997-04-03 00:00:00",
            "1955-03-14 00:00:00",
            "1999-02-12 00:00:00",
            "1990-02-28 00:00:00",
            "1935-05-14 00:00:00",
            "1989-03-11 00:00:00",
            "1961-02-03 00:00:00",
            "1978-03-04 00:00:00",
            "1963-12-03 00:00:00",
            "1978-03-11 00:00:00",
            "1989-02-03 00:00:00",
            "1974-03-04 00:00:00",
            "1988-12-03 00:00:00",
            "1945-02-27 00:00:00",
            "1970-02-05 00:00:00",
            "1983-03-04 00:00:00",
            "1969-03-21 00:00:00",
            "1989-04-23 00:00:00",
            "1999-03-02 00:00:00",
            "1997-04-03 00:00:00",
            "1955-03-14 00:00:00",
            "1997-04-03 00:00:00",
            "1955-03-14 00:00:00",
            "1999-02-12 00:00:00",
            "1990-02-28 00:00:00",
            "1990-03-01 00:00:00"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Person_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Prison": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Prison_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Leavenworth Federal Penitentiary",
            "Folson State Prison",
            "Attica Correctional Facility",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "ADX Florence Facility"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "State": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Max_Capacity": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1000,
            14000,
            5000,
            2000,
            1813,
            2150,
            2000,
            1700,
            3302,
            490
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Prison_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Victim_Criminal": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Implicated_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            35,
            36,
            37,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43,
            44,
            45,
            46,
            47,
            48,
            49,
            50
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Implication_Type": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Victim",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal",
            "Criminal"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Questionning": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Status": {
          "TYPE": "Enum",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Dead",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Alive",
            "Unknown",
            "Unknown",
            "Unknown",
            "Unknown",
            "Unknown",
            "Unknown"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Crime_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Person_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            9,
            9,
            1,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            6,
            6,
            3,
            3,
            10,
            10,
            13,
            13,
            14,
            14,
            17,
            17,
            37,
            31,
            31,
            31,
            32,
            33,
            34,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            19,
            19,
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27,
            28,
            29,
            30,
            35,
            36,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Implicated_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Crime_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "crime",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Crime_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Person_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Person",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Person_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Crime_ID"
        ],
        [
          "Person_ID"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Witness": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Witness_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Questionning": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "slt",
            "tg",
            "slt ftg",
            "ouesh je me suis perdu",
            "bla",
            "bruit",
            "buot",
            "buits",
            "bri",
            "blon"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Person_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            7,
            4,
            11,
            7,
            38,
            39,
            40,
            41,
            42,
            43
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Case_ID": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            3,
            4,
            8,
            8,
            8,
            6,
            9
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Witness_ID"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Case_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Cases",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Case_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "Person_ID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Person",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Person_ID"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "Person_ID"
        ],
        [
          "Case_ID"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}