{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/nehalabubakar/online-cemetery-locator/blob/f4ab62d1ad17c3890ba6d9d2cb3dead1c5d54191/online-cemeter-locator.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "cemetery": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "title": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Crown Hill Memorial Park & Mausoleum",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "street": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "zip": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "OH 44087",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "longitude": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "latitude": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "39.482748",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "image": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Haven-Memorial.png",
            "County-Memorial.jpg",
            "Crown-Hill-Memorial.jpg",
            "Crown-Hill-Cemetery.jpg",
            "Highland-Memorial.jpg",
            "cbk.jpg",
            "Scranton_Cemetery.jpg"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "user_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "user",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "SetNull",
          "ON_UPDATE": "Cascade"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "obituary": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            52,
            53,
            54,
            55,
            56,
            57,
            58,
            59,
            60,
            61,
            62,
            63,
            64,
            65,
            66,
            67,
            68,
            69,
            70,
            71,
            72,
            73,
            74,
            75,
            76,
            77,
            78,
            79,
            80,
            81,
            82,
            83,
            84,
            85,
            86,
            87,
            88,
            89,
            90,
            91,
            92,
            93,
            94,
            95,
            96,
            97,
            98,
            99,
            100,
            101,
            102,
            103,
            104,
            105,
            106,
            107
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            4
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "person_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "dates": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "06/17/1946 - 11/29/2020",
            "02/16/1953 - 11/28/2020",
            "04/07/1956 - 11/28/2020",
            "11/16/1935 - 11/27/2020",
            "07/10/1947 - 11/27/2020",
            "06/30/1937 - 11/28/2020",
            "06/29/1992 - 11/27/2020",
            "07/27/1964 - 12/09/2020",
            "03/09/1933 - 12/07/2020",
            "03/16/1927 - 12/07/2020",
            "02/12/1956 - 12/06/2020",
            "01/16/1934 - 12/08/2020",
            "12/06/1965 - 12/09/2020",
            "06/30/1930 - 12/15/2020",
            "02/17/1969 - 12/17/2020",
            "08/17/1930 - 12/14/2020",
            "02/02/1940 - 12/12/2020",
            "05/23/1931 - 12/12/2020",
            "12/22/1947 - 12/14/2020",
            "04/19/1933 - 12/10/2020",
            "12/21/1985 - 12/10/2020",
            "12/12/1947 - 12/13/2020",
            "09/29/1938 - 12/11/2020",
            "03/01/1936 - 12/18/2020",
            "10/25/1950 - 12/16/2020",
            "08/03/1925 - 12/15/2020",
            "02/22/2001 - 12/11/2020",
            "10/11/1945 - 12/14/2020",
            "11/25/1952 - 12/17/2020",
            "10/27/1933 - 12/17/2020",
            "04/16/1950 - 12/17/2020",
            "03/26/1930 - 12/14/2020",
            "09/16/1953 - 12/15/2020",
            "01/27/1938 - 12/20/2020",
            "06/28/1968 - 12/21/2020",
            "12/03/1945 - 12/21/2020",
            "05/07/1932 - 12/20/2020",
            "01/31/1952 - 12/14/2020",
            "08/28/2000 - 12/14/2020",
            "09/03/1928 - 12/19/2020",
            "07/21/1939 - 12/19/2020",
            "07/08/1966 - 12/24/2020",
            "10/19/1952 - 12/18/2020",
            "05/31/1964 - 12/20/2020",
            "09/27/1961 - 12/20/2020",
            "07/27/1984 - 12/19/2020",
            "05/14/1926 - 12/23/2020",
            "09/03/1928 - 12/19/2020",
            "10/18/1942 - 12/21/2020",
            "05/05/1954 - 12/22/2020",
            "11/07/1935 - 12/19/2020",
            "07/20/1951 - 12/25/2020",
            "09/16/1957 - 12/13/2020",
            "02/06/1942 - 12/21/2020",
            "12/20/1942 - 12/20/2020",
            "07/29/1995 - 12/27/2020"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "prayers": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Celebration of Life will be held on Tuesday, December 22, 2020 Wake:12:30p.m. Service: 1:00p.m. at THE CALHOUN FUNERAL HOME 23000 Rockside Rd. Bedford Hts. OH, 44146.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Celebration of Life will be held on Wednesday, December 23, 2020 Wake:12:30p.m. Service: 1:00p.m. at THE CALHOUN FUNERAL HOME 23000 Rockside Rd. Bedford Hts. OH, 44146.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Memorial service to be held at a later date.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "image": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Angelette_Ledean_Colvin.jpg",
            "Joan_Warren.jpg",
            "Larry_Summerlin.jpg",
            "Evelyn_Lorine_Garden.jpg",
            "Roger_Lett.jpg",
            "Cordelia_Scott.jpg",
            "Arnise_S__Thrasher-Hickerson.jpeg",
            "Reginald_Lorenzo_Adams.jpg",
            "Beatrice_Elizabeth_Heard.jpg",
            "Mary_E__Burks.jpg",
            "Kenneth_C__Lard1.jpeg",
            "Ralph-Louis-Reese.jpg",
            "Rhonda-Y_-George.jpg",
            "mary-etta.jpg",
            "cover-edited.jpg",
            "Florence.jpg",
            "leefield.jpg",
            "albert.jpg",
            "candle-gallery.jpeg",
            "edna.jpg",
            "james.jpg",
            "bruce.jpg",
            "johnnie.jpg",
            "thomas.jpg",
            "candle-gallery1.jpeg",
            "jannie-m.jpg",
            "tylen.jpg",
            "James-Turner.jpg",
            "Linda-Ann-Slaughter.jpg",
            "Benjamin-McClendon-Jr.jpg",
            "Pamela-Harris.jpg",
            "Ruth-Ruthy.jpg",
            "Mildred-Renee.jpg",
            "Clyde-Goodman.jpg",
            "Traci-Lynette-Edwards.jpg",
            "Roberta-Shoates.jpg",
            "Jimmie-Lee-Burt-Sr.jpg",
            "Elaine-V-Smith.jpg",
            "Christopher-Robert-Maurice-Williams.jpg",
            "Nathaniel-Nate-Wilder.jpg",
            "Jean-C-Jubert.jpg",
            "Vincent-Lee-Grimes.jpg",
            "Linda-Charlier.jpg",
            "candle-gallery2.jpeg",
            "Kenneth-Shields.jpg",
            "Delontez-Lawrence.jpg",
            "Opher-Jackson.jpg",
            "candle-gallery3.jpeg",
            "Delores-A-Dunlop.jpg",
            "Mrs-Gloria-Ann-Coleman.jpg",
            "Betty-Mae-Roundtree.jpg",
            "Dianne-Naimah-Rashada.jpg",
            "Robert-Cory-Albert.jpg",
            "candle-gallery4.jpeg",
            "Frances-Louise-Williams.jpg",
            "web-46.jpg"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "user_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "user",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": "SetNull",
          "ON_UPDATE": "Cascade"
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "user": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            4
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "first_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Admin"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "last_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Admin"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "email": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "pwd_reset_token": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            ""
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "user_status": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "admin"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}