{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/MidgeOnGithub/Monster-Rancher-3-Lexicon/blob/ca1f132786c259c80d93665f2c249a4f2bec49c5/src/sql/build_reference_tables.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "Attack": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "DerivationID": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Attack": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "StatUsed": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "AttackType": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "ItemRequired": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "GutsUsed": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Damage": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "GutsDown": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Critical": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Hit": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "MaxLevel": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "AttackRange": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Growth": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Effect": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "DerivationID"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "Derivation",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "Id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Characteristic": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Characteristic": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Active",
            "Aggressive",
            "Aloof",
            "Aquaphobic",
            "Armor",
            "Arthritis",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Brave",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Burn",
            "Calm",
            "Careful",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Cheerful",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Chlorophyll",
            "Clean",
            "Cold",
            "Cold Limbs",
            "Combative",
            "Confident",
            "Contrary",
            "Cool",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Defense Roll",
            "Difficult",
            "Dim-witted",
            "Dimples",
            "Directionless",
            "Dry Skin",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Easygoing",
            "Eats Anything",
            "Energetic",
            "Extra Teeth",
            "Faithful",
            "Fast Footwork",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Flame Secrets",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gluttonous",
            "Gourmet",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Groovy Moves",
            "Hard Scales",
            "Hay Fever",
            "Heart Secrets",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Heat-Proofing",
            "<PERSON>",
            "High Output",
            "Honest",
            "Honorable",
            "Hypotension",
            "Hysterical",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Illusion Cape",
            "Impatient",
            "Independent",
            "Indifferent",
            "Indignant",
            "Injury",
            "Insulation",
            "Intuitive",
            "Iron Fists",
            "Iron Heart",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lazy",
            "Life Secrets",
            "Life Wisdom",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Loud Voice",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Lump",
            "Lung Capacity",
            "Magic Secrets",
            "Magic Wisdom",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Modest",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nearsighted",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Nice",
            "Normal",
            "Optimistic",
            "Passionate",
            "Perceptive",
            "Perfectionist",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pheromones",
            "Pride",
            "Quiet",
            "Radar",
            "Refined",
            "Relaxed",
            "Reliable",
            "Resists Cold",
            "Resists Heat",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Resists Magic",
            "Resists Water",
            "Resists Wind",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sensitive",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sharp Claws",
            "Sharp Ears",
            "Sharp Edge",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sharp Horns",
            "Show-off",
            "Shy",
            "Sleepless",
            "Slow",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sniper",
            "Snoring",
            "Soft Skin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Split Ends",
            "Spoiled",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Stoic",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Sweet Voice",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Timid",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Touchy",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Unfriendly",
            "Unselfish",
            "Vegetarian",
            "Water Secrets",
            "Water Wisdom",
            "Waterproofing",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Whimsical",
            "Wind Secrets",
            "Wind Wisdom"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Description": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "\"I can't just sit around all day...\"",
            "\"Something you wanted to say?\"",
            "\"Oh, nothing...\"",
            "Hates to even see water. Swimming is out of the question.",
            "Damage is decreased, but has a hard time dodging.",
            "Shoulders hurt, and is easily irritable.",
            "\".....\"",
            "\"I won't run from this battle.\"",
            "A bruise incurred in battle. Should heal by the next week.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "\"Let's calm down, and reassess things.\"",
            "\"Look both ways... Watch that step...\"",
            "<PERSON>",
            "\"Singing and dancing is pure paradise.\"",
            "\"Do I have to?\"",
            "Performs photo-synthesis during rest, to self-heal.",
            "\"I need to take a bath everyday.\"",
            "Wind bring many diseases. Let's be careful.",
            "Weak against cold. Hands and feet start to hurt.",
            "\"Doesn't anyone want to fight me?\"",
            "\"I won't lose. No matter what!\"",
            "\"What? I'd rather not do that.\"",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Traps soul in darkness. Less prone to enemy Heart attacks.",
            "Reduces damage from throwing attacks.",
            "\"... Yeah, what's your problem?\"",
            "\"Oh?... I didn't realize that...\"",
            "Charm point that can be seen when laughing.",
            "It's an adventure no matter where it goes.",
            "Fatigue and stress are the enemies of beauty.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Doesn't feel well, and gets tired easily than usual.",
            "\"I'm sure it'll turn out okay.\"",
            "Loses preference for foods, but any food eaten is okay.",
            "\"Yeah, that's the way!\"",
            "Charm point that can be seen when laughing.",
            "\"Please tell me anything you want me to do.\"",
            "Dodges attacks more often, but Hit damage increases.",
            "\"It's not that strong, is it?\"",
            "Increases the damage done by Flame attacks.",
            "Greatly increases the damage done by Flame attacks.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "\"I want to eat some more...\"",
            "Becomes picky with its food.",
            "\"I want this. Oh, and this too.\"",
            "Increases effects of Dance attacks",
            "Damage is decreased, but it has a hard time dodging.",
            "Sneezes a lot during the spring, and is easily stressed.",
            "Greatly increases the Guts damage from Heart attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the Guts damage done by Heart attacks.",
            "A special covering that blocks out heat.",
            "\"I don't think I'm ready just yet.\"",
            "Increases damage from Beam attacks.",
            "\"Yes, sir. I understand.\"",
            "\"I will swear upon my name.\"",
            "<PERSON>",
            "\"What!?!?!\"",
            "Greatly increases the damage done by Ice attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by Ice attacks.",
            "Confuses the enemy, making dodging easier.",
            "\"I don't believe",
            "\"I am unique. No one is quite like me.\"",
            "\"Say what you will.\"",
            "\"I don't know! Stop bothering me!\"",
            "Damage from battles. Should heal by the next week.",
            "A special covering that doesn't allow electricity through.",
            "\"You're not telling me everything...\"",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by fists.",
            "Toughens the monster so it doesn't get tired easily.",
            "Reduces damage from Hit attacks",
            "\"Let me sleep a little bit more...\"",
            "Significantly increases the damage from Life attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by Life attacks.",
            "Less susceptible to enemy Magic attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by voice attacks.",
            "Greatly increases the damage done by Lightning attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by Lightning attacks.",
            "A lump incurred in battle. Should heal by the next week.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Greatly increases the damage done by Magic attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by Magic attacks.",
            "A bad headache makes a monster irritable.",
            "\"No... I'm not very good...\"",
            "\"I am absolutely gorgeous, aren't I?\"",
            "Can see things up close, but can't see well far away.",
            "\"I'm still worried about that thing...\"",
            "\"May everyone live happily.\"",
            "\"Everything's fine. Just fine.\"",
            "\"Well, let's just give it a try, then\"",
            "\"Arrgh, let's do it!\"",
            "\"Hey, I found some money!\"",
            "\"Gotta do it right or not at all...\"",
            "\"Am... Am I going to be okay?\"",
            "<PERSON>",
            "\"I deserve better than most monsters.\"",
            "\"I like to avoid conflicts.\"",
            "Increases the chance of hitting opponent with attacks.",
            "\"If you'll excuse me, I must be going.\"",
            "\"Break time! Break time!\"",
            "\"No need to rush. Take it slowly.\"",
            "Perfectly fine, even in cold weather.",
            "Doesn't mind hot regions.",
            "Reduces damage from Lightning.",
            "Reduces damage from Magic attacks.",
            "Reduces damage from Water attacks.",
            "Reduces damage from Wind attacks.",
            "Increases damage from head attacks. No relation to IQ.",
            "\"I get mad when you don't listen to me.\"",
            "\"How cruel! My heart of glass has been shattered!\"",
            "\"I'll try my best.\"",
            "Slightly increases damage done by nail attacks.",
            "Doesn't miss a sound!",
            "Increases damage done by weapon attacks.",
            "Increases the chance attacks connecting.",
            "Slightly increases damage done by teeth attacks.",
            "Slightly increases damage done by horn attacks.",
            "\"Heh, heh, heh. Watch this one...\"",
            "\"..... Oh, nothing.\"",
            "Can't sleep well, so rest time does not help much.",
            "\"Uh...\"",
            "\"I don't have much of an appetite.\"",
            "Increases the chance of hitting the enemy with Throwing moves.",
            "Very troublesome to those asleep nearby, but not the snorer.",
            "Skin is soft and feels good to touch.",
            "\"I won't let you win [and] just walk away...\"",
            "Fatigue and stress are the enemies of beauty.",
            "\"Play with me, play with me...\"",
            "Kinda gross when you get kicked by it.",
            "\"I still need to train harder.\"",
            "Reduces damage, but makes dodging more difficult.",
            "Reduces damage from Heart attacks.",
            "\"I don't care. I know I'm right.\"",
            "Has a hard time breathing and is easily irritated.",
            "Doesn't like hot regions, but doesn't hate them, either.",
            "A strange sweet smell that clouds the minds of enemies.",
            "Increases the success rate of Singing attacks.",
            "Very warm-looking fur.",
            "Can't function right without humidity",
            "\"No way... that's scary.\"",
            "Decreases the success rate of Singing attacks.",
            "\"What'd you say?!\"",
            "Reduces damage, but makes dodging more difficult.",
            "\"What's so funny?\"",
            "\"'Something I want?' No, not really.\"",
            "Can eat meat, but chooses not to.",
            "Greatly increases the damage done by Water attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by Water attacks.",
            "A special covering that doesn't allow water through.",
            "More susceptible to Heart attacks.",
            "Hates cold regions.",
            "Prefers to avoid hot regions.",
            "Increases damage from Lightning.",
            "Increases damage from Magic attacks.",
            "Increases damage from Water attacks.",
            "Increases damage from Wind attacks",
            "\"?\"",
            "\"I don't feel like working this week.\"",
            "Greatly increases the damage done by Wind attacks.",
            "Slightly increases the damage done by Wind attacks."
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Derivation": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Derivation": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Baku",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Colorpandora",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Dakkung",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Gitan",
            "Golem",
            "Hare",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Jell",
            "Joker",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mew",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mogi",
            "Momo",
            "Naga",
            "Octopee",
            "Ogyo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Pixie",
            "Plant",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Raiden",
            "Suezo",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tiger",
            "Zan",
            "Zoom"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "Region": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "Id": {
          "TYPE": "Integer",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "Region": {
          "TYPE": "Text",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Goat",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Morx",
            "Special"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "Id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}