{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/shafiq97/DTS2/blob/61489d0371bd5eb2047ebea16bd11e1977d03fa2/phpmultiuserlogin.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "announcement": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1001,
            1002,
            1003,
            1005,
            1006,
            1013,
            1014,
            1023,
            1024,
            1027
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "message": {
          "TYPE": "mediumtext",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Tommorows meeting cancelled",
            "Good morning everyone",
            "Today ,we have meeting",
            "New announcement",
            "New Announcement",
            "Good morning",
            "Good afternoon",
            "meeting cancel tomorrow",
            "Please check all document",
            "Good morning, Please make sure all document details is correct"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date": {
          "TYPE": "Timestamp",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-19 13:44:40",
            "2020-12-28 07:53:51",
            "2020-12-28 09:07:37",
            "2021-01-12 12:59:04",
            "2021-01-12 12:59:14",
            "2021-01-14 03:13:53",
            "2021-01-14 06:28:33",
            "2021-01-14 07:26:38",
            "2021-01-14 08:27:33",
            "2021-01-15 09:17:58"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "centre_of_studies": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            15,
            1,
            16,
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "cos_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Centre for Foundation Studies (CFS)",
            "Kulliyyah of Allied Health Sciences (KAHS)",
            "Kulliyyah of Architecture and Environmental Design (KAED)",
            "Kulliyyah of Dentistry (KOD)",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kulliyyah of Education (KOED)",
            "Kulliyyah of Engineering (KOE)",
            "Kulliyyah of Information and Communication Technology (KICT)",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Kulliyyah of Languages and Management (KLM)",
            "Kulliyyah of Medicine (KOM)",
            "Kulliyyah of Nursing (KON)",
            "Kulliyyah of Pharmacy (KOP)",
            "Kulliyyah of Science (KOS)"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "documents": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1004,
            1005,
            1006,
            1009,
            1010,
            1011,
            1012,
            1013,
            1014,
            1015,
            1016,
            1017,
            1018,
            1019,
            1021,
            1022,
            1023,
            1025
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "MQA 02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "MQA 01 - for Bachelor in Mathematics",
            "New Curriculum Programme",
            "Trying purpose",
            "My Document",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "11123",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Nursing",
            "senate meeting",
            "MQA 01 - Bachelor of Dentistry",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Medicine",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Electrical Engineering",
            "MQA 03 KOS",
            "Testing Document",
            "test2",
            "testr",
            "23",
            "Testing Document"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_sender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Try",
            "try 3",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Me",
            "me",
            "me",
            "me",
            "Test Sender"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_responsibility": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_kulliyah": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "KICT",
            "KOS",
            "AIKOL",
            "CELPAD",
            "KOS",
            "KICT",
            "KOD",
            "KON",
            "KICT",
            "KOD",
            "KOM",
            "KOE",
            "KOS",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "",
            "Curriculum",
            "Other",
            "Other",
            "",
            "Other",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "other",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "other",
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Curriculum Review"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_receive": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2020-12-28 17:25:04",
            "2020-12-31 12:47:12",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2021-01-13 09:37:37",
            "2021-01-14 15:27:49",
            "2021-01-14 16:18:19",
            "2021-01-15 17:40:58",
            "2021-01-15 17:51:27",
            "2021-06-04 00:14:25",
            "2021-09-01 12:57:44",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:30",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:30",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:30",
            "2021-09-02 14:27:05"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_due": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-05 08:25:07",
            "2021-01-07 12:47:14",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-01-20 09:37:40",
            "2021-01-21 15:27:52",
            "2021-01-21 16:18:23",
            "2021-01-22 17:41:00",
            "2021-01-23 17:51:30",
            "2021-06-18 00:14:28",
            "2021-09-01 12:57:55",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:35",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:35",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:35",
            "2021-09-02 14:27:08"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_location": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "Document Desk",
            "Siti Amrin Desk",
            "",
            "youtube.com",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "youtube.com"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_attention": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "Others",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_characteristic": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_status": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Completed",
            "Completed",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_comment": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "To be reviewed",
            "For approval",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Return to sender",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Others",
            "Others",
            "Completed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "To be reviewed"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "owner": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "kict user"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "doc_category": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "doc_cat_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            11,
            25,
            7,
            8,
            3,
            4,
            9,
            5,
            6,
            10,
            34
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_cat_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Examination test",
            "Full Accreditation (MQA-02) - Self-Accreditation",
            "Full Accreditation (MQA-02)/Manual Professional Body",
            "Kertas Cadangan Permohonan Program Baharu (JPT)",
            "Kertas Cadangan Semakan Kurikulum (JPT)",
            "New Cycle Accreditation - Self-Accreditation",
            "Provisional Accreditation (MQA-01) - Self-Accreditation",
            "Provisional Accreditation (MQA-01)/Manual Professional Body",
            "Renewal of Accreditation (Professional Body)",
            "testing category"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "logs": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1086,
            1087,
            1088,
            1089,
            1090,
            1091,
            1092,
            1095,
            1096,
            1097,
            1098,
            1099,
            1100,
            1101,
            1102,
            1103,
            1104,
            1105,
            1106,
            1107,
            1108,
            1109,
            1110,
            1111,
            1112,
            1113,
            1114,
            1115,
            1116,
            1117,
            1118,
            1119,
            1120,
            1121,
            1122,
            1123,
            1124,
            1125,
            1126,
            1127,
            1128,
            1129,
            1130,
            1131,
            1132,
            1133,
            1134,
            1135,
            1136,
            1137,
            1138,
            1139,
            1140,
            1141,
            1142,
            1143,
            1144,
            1145,
            1146,
            1147,
            1148,
            1149,
            1150,
            1151,
            1153
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1004,
            1004,
            1004,
            1004,
            1005,
            1006,
            1005,
            1009,
            1006,
            1009,
            1009,
            1006,
            1004,
            1010,
            1005,
            1011,
            1004,
            1012,
            1012,
            1012,
            1011,
            1011,
            1011,
            1011,
            1011,
            1011,
            1013,
            1009,
            1010,
            1009,
            1009,
            1011,
            1012,
            1013,
            1004,
            1009,
            1006,
            1011,
            1013,
            1012,
            1005,
            1009,
            1006,
            1010,
            1010,
            1014,
            1014,
            1014,
            1012,
            1010,
            1015,
            1015,
            1015,
            1010,
            1016,
            1016,
            1016,
            1017,
            1017,
            1017,
            1018,
            1022,
            1023,
            1010,
            1025
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "date_logged": {
          "TYPE": "Timestamp",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-28 09:13:09",
            "2020-12-28 09:14:24",
            "2020-12-28 09:15:54",
            "2020-12-28 09:17:27",
            "2020-12-28 09:28:22",
            "2020-12-31 04:47:26",
            "2020-12-31 04:54:42",
            "2021-01-05 14:57:31",
            "2021-01-05 15:48:46",
            "2021-01-05 15:48:57",
            "2021-01-05 15:50:34",
            "2021-01-05 15:52:36",
            "2021-01-05 16:29:42",
            "2021-01-05 16:45:11",
            "2021-01-05 16:46:05",
            "2021-01-05 16:59:53",
            "2021-01-05 17:07:40",
            "2021-01-08 03:07:52",
            "2021-01-08 03:08:26",
            "2021-01-08 03:09:19",
            "2021-01-08 03:14:21",
            "2021-01-08 03:15:11",
            "2021-01-08 03:16:12",
            "2021-01-08 03:18:36",
            "2021-01-08 03:19:04",
            "2021-01-08 03:19:23",
            "2021-01-13 01:37:56",
            "2021-01-13 01:41:54",
            "2021-01-13 01:49:02",
            "2021-01-13 02:00:46",
            "2021-01-13 14:29:47",
            "2021-01-14 03:22:07",
            "2021-01-14 03:31:50",
            "2021-01-14 06:10:31",
            "2021-01-14 06:11:08",
            "2021-01-14 06:19:38",
            "2021-01-14 06:20:56",
            "2021-01-14 06:21:03",
            "2021-01-14 06:21:11",
            "2021-01-14 06:21:58",
            "2021-01-14 06:22:50",
            "2021-01-14 06:29:46",
            "2021-01-14 06:31:35",
            "2021-01-14 06:38:36",
            "2021-01-14 06:38:54",
            "2021-01-14 07:28:10",
            "2021-01-14 07:28:48",
            "2021-01-14 07:29:08",
            "2021-01-14 07:30:14",
            "2021-01-14 07:32:50",
            "2021-01-14 08:19:41",
            "2021-01-14 08:21:07",
            "2021-01-14 08:22:17",
            "2021-01-14 08:28:32",
            "2021-01-15 09:41:24",
            "2021-01-15 09:42:15",
            "2021-01-15 09:43:03",
            "2021-01-15 09:51:54",
            "2021-01-15 09:52:38",
            "2021-01-15 09:53:15",
            "2021-06-03 16:14:36",
            "2021-09-01 05:08:07",
            "2021-09-01 05:09:13",
            "2021-09-02 06:21:09",
            "2021-09-02 06:28:04"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "MK02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "MK02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "MK02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "MK02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "MQA 01 - for Bachelor in Mathematics",
            "New Curriculum Programme",
            "MQA 01 - for Bachelor in Mathematics",
            "ww",
            "New Curriculum Programme",
            "ww",
            "ww",
            "New Curriculum Programme",
            "MQA 02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "sdsa",
            "MQA 01 - for Bachelor in Mathematics",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "111",
            "111",
            "111",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Nursing",
            "ww",
            "sdsa",
            "ww",
            "wwwww",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "11123",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Nursing",
            "MQA 02 Document for the BSC programme",
            "wwwww",
            "New Curriculum Programme",
            "MQA 02 - Bachelor of Information Technology",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Nursing",
            "11123",
            "MQA 01 - for Bachelor in Mathematics",
            "Trying purpose",
            "New Curriculum Programme",
            "try 2",
            "try 3",
            "senate meeting",
            "senate meeting",
            "senate meeting",
            "11123",
            "try 3",
            "MQA 01 - Bachelor of Dentistry",
            "MQA 01 - Bachelor of Dentistry",
            "MQA 01 - Bachelor of Dentistry",
            "try 3",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Medicine",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Medicine",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Medicine",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Electrical Engineering",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Electrical Engineering",
            "MQA 01 Bachelor of Electrical Engineering",
            "MQA 03 KOS",
            "testr",
            "23",
            "My Document",
            "Testing Document"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_sender": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "w",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "w",
            "w",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "dasds",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1",
            "1",
            "1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "w",
            "dasds",
            "w",
            "w",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "w",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Try",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "try 2",
            "try 3",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "1",
            "try 3",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "try 3",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "me",
            "me",
            "try 3",
            "Test Sender"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_responsibility": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_kulliyah": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KOS",
            "AIKOL",
            "KOS",
            "CELPAD",
            "AIKOL",
            "CELPAD",
            "CELPAD",
            "AIKOL",
            "KICT",
            "KOS",
            "KOS",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KOD",
            "KOD",
            "KOD",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KON",
            "CELPAD",
            "KOS",
            "CELPAD",
            "CELPAD",
            "KICT",
            "KOD",
            "KON",
            "KICT",
            "CELPAD",
            "AIKOL",
            "KICT",
            "KON",
            "KOD",
            "KOS",
            "CELPAD",
            "AIKOL",
            "KOS",
            "KOS",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KICT",
            "KOD",
            "KOS",
            "KOD",
            "KOD",
            "KOD",
            "KOS",
            "KOM",
            "KOM",
            "KOM",
            "KOE",
            "KOE",
            "KOE",
            "KOS",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)",
            "KOS",
            "Academy of Graduate and Professional Studies (ACADEMY)"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "proposal",
            "proposal",
            "proposal",
            "",
            "MQA01",
            "Curriculum",
            "MQA01",
            "proposal",
            "Curriculum",
            "proposal",
            "proposal",
            "Curriculum",
            "",
            "MQA 02 Document",
            "MQA01",
            "MQA 02 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "Curriculum Review Document",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "",
            "Curriculum",
            "",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "",
            "",
            "Other",
            "Curriculum",
            "Other",
            "Other",
            "other",
            "other",
            "other",
            "Other",
            "Other",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "Other",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "MQA 01 Document",
            "other",
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Curriculum Review",
            "Other",
            "Curriculum Review"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_receive": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2020-12-28 17:25:04",
            "2020-12-31 12:47:12",
            "2020-12-28 17:25:04",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2020-12-31 12:47:12",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2020-12-31 12:47:12",
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2020-12-28 17:25:04",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-13 09:37:37",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2021-01-13 09:37:37",
            "2020-12-28 17:11:46",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2020-12-31 12:47:12",
            "2021-01-06 00:59:34",
            "2021-01-13 09:37:37",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2020-12-28 17:25:04",
            "2021-01-05 22:57:18",
            "2020-12-31 12:47:12",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-01-14 15:27:49",
            "2021-01-14 15:27:49",
            "2021-01-14 15:27:49",
            "2021-01-08 11:07:36",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-01-14 16:18:19",
            "2021-01-14 16:18:19",
            "2021-01-14 16:18:19",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-01-15 17:40:58",
            "2021-01-15 17:40:58",
            "2021-01-15 17:40:58",
            "2021-01-15 17:51:27",
            "2021-01-15 17:51:27",
            "2021-01-15 17:51:27",
            "2021-06-04 00:14:25",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:30",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:30",
            "2021-01-06 00:44:59",
            "2021-09-02 14:27:05"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_due": {
          "TYPE": "Datetime",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-05 08:25:07",
            "2021-01-07 12:47:14",
            "2021-01-05 08:25:07",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-07 12:47:14",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-07 12:47:14",
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-01-05 08:25:07",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-20 09:37:40",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-01-20 09:37:40",
            "2021-01-04 09:11:51",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-07 12:47:14",
            "2021-01-14 00:59:36",
            "2021-01-20 09:37:40",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-01-05 08:25:07",
            "2021-01-13 22:57:20",
            "2021-01-07 12:47:14",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-01-21 15:27:52",
            "2021-01-21 15:27:52",
            "2021-01-21 15:27:52",
            "2021-01-14 11:07:39",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-01-21 16:18:23",
            "2021-01-21 16:18:23",
            "2021-01-21 16:18:23",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-01-22 17:41:00",
            "2021-01-22 17:41:00",
            "2021-01-22 17:41:00",
            "2021-01-23 17:51:30",
            "2021-01-23 17:51:30",
            "2021-01-23 17:51:30",
            "2021-06-18 00:14:28",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:35",
            "2021-09-01 13:05:35",
            "2021-02-05 00:45:01",
            "2021-09-02 14:27:08"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_location": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk jjj",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk jjj",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk jl",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "Front Desk",
            "Siti Amrin Desk",
            "Document Desk",
            "Front Desk",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Siti Amrin Desk",
            "",
            "",
            "",
            "Front Desk, https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Mj5pflm7o18SmgMoHW-zgJ0Kk05_VM8C/view?usp=sharing ",
            "youtube.com"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_attention": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Others",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Others",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Others",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Others",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_characteristic": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy",
            "Softcopy and Hardcopy",
            "Softcopy"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_status": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Completed",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending",
            "Pending"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "doc_comment": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "For approval",
            "For approval",
            "For approval",
            "with approval by Dr A",
            "For approval",
            "Accept",
            "For approval",
            "yy",
            "Accept now",
            "yywww",
            "yywww",
            "Accept now",
            "with approval by Dr A",
            "Foward to director",
            "For approval",
            "Forward to director",
            "with approval by Dr A",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "To be reviewed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "Return to sender",
            "Reviewed",
            "Reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "yywww",
            "Foward to director",
            "yywww",
            "yywww",
            "Reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "To be reviewed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "Reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "For approval",
            "Reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "To be reviewed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Reviewed",
            "Reviewed",
            "Reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Others",
            "Return to sender",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Others",
            "Forward to director",
            "Reviewed",
            "Completed",
            "To be reviewed",
            "Forward to director",
            "Forward to director",
            "Return to sender",
            "To be reviewed"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "owner": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "kict user",
            null,
            "kict user",
            null,
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            "kict user",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            null,
            "kict user",
            null,
            "kict user",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "kict user",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "kict user",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PERSON>",
            null,
            null,
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "kict user",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "doc_id"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "documents",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "id"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "users": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1001,
            1013,
            1014,
            1015,
            1019
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "admin",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "kict user"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "login": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>",
            "<EMAIL_ADDRESS>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "password": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "12345",
            "12345",
            "12345",
            "12345",
            "12345"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "role": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "role_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "admin",
            "assistant",
            "officer",
            "director",
            "owner"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "staff_id": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "112233"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}