{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/USMC1941/CS336-Rutgers/blob/abe2a4a54bee9326dbc16701fe29b9753a7475b2/Project/Resources/BarBeerDrinkerSample.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "MIT",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "bars": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Blue Tattoo",
            "Britannia Arms",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Caravan",
            "Club 175",
            "Coconut Willie's Cocktail Lounge",
            "Eulipia",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Giza Hookah Lounge",
            "Hedley Club",
            "Il Fornaio",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Backbeat",
            "The Blank Club",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "license": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "MA12347",
            "CA45678",
            "CA45678",
            "MA12346",
            "CA45678",
            "IL12345",
            "CA45678",
            "CA45678",
            "IL12346",
            "IL12348",
            "IL12349",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "NY12347",
            "MA12348",
            "CA45678",
            "MA12349",
            "MA12345"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "addr": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            "1500 Market St.",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "beers": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Extra Gold",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Heiniken",
            "ICEHOUSE",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Michelob Golden Draft",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Original Premium",
            "Original Premium Lager",
            "Original Premium Lager Dog",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Stolichnaya Citrona",
            "Zima",
            "Zima Citrus"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "manf": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Coors Brewing Company",
            "Anheuser-Busch",
            "Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Company",
            "Coors Brewing Company",
            "Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Company",
            "Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Company",
            "Heiniken Inernational",
            "Plank Road Brewery",
            "Coors Brewing Company",
            "Anheuser-Busch",
            "Anheuser-Busch",
            "Anheuser-Busch",
            "Anheuser-Busch",
            "Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Company",
            "Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Company",
            "Plank Road Brewery",
            "Miller Brewing Company",
            "Plank Road Brewery",
            "Miller Brewing Company",
            "Coors Brewing Company",
            "Coors Brewing Company"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "drinkers": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Bob",
            "Erik",
            "Herb",
            "Jesse",
            "John",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mike",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tom",
            "Vince"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "city": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "phone": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<PHONE_NUMBER>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "addr": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            null,
            null,
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "name"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "frequents": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "drinker": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Mike",
            "Bob",
            "Erik",
            "Herb",
            "Jesse",
            "John",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Mike",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Tom",
            "Vince",
            "Mike",
            "John",
            "Tom",
            "Bob",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Herb",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Vince",
            "Mike"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "bar": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Caravan",
            "Caravan",
            "Coconut Willie's Cocktail Lounge",
            "Coconut Willie's Cocktail Lounge",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "drinker",
        "bar"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "bar"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "bars",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "drinker"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "drinkers",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "bar"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "likes": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "drinker": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "John",
            "Mike",
            "John",
            "Mike",
            "John",
            "Mike",
            "Mike",
            "John",
            "John",
            "Mike",
            "John",
            "Mike",
            "Jesse",
            "Mike",
            "John"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "beer": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Michelob Golden Draft",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Original Premium",
            "Original Premium Lager",
            "Original Premium Lager Dog",
            "Original Premium Lager Dog",
            "Stolichnaya Citrona"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "drinker",
        "beer"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "beer"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "beers",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "drinker"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "drinkers",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "beer"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "sells": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "bar": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Blue Tattoo",
            "Britannia Arms",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Caravan",
            "Caravan",
            "Caravan",
            "Club 175",
            "Coconut Willie's Cocktail Lounge",
            "Eulipia",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Giza Hookah Lounge",
            "Hedley Club",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "The Backbeat",
            "The Blank Club",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "beer": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": "",
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": true,
          "VALUES": [
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Original Premium Lager Dog",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Heiniken",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Heiniken",
            "Original Premium Lager Dog",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Stolichnaya Citrona",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Original Premium Lager Dog"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "price": {
          "TYPE": "Decimal",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            6.0,
            5.5,
            6.25,
            6.0,
            6.5,
            5.0,
            5.0,
            5.5,
            5.5,
            3.5,
            4.5,
            3.25,
            4.5,
            3.0,
            6.0,
            8.0,
            2.5,
            5.0,
            3.5,
            5.5,
            4.5,
            5.5
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "bar",
        "beer"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "bar"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "bars",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "beer"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "beers",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "name"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [
        [
          "beer"
        ]
      ],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}