{
  "INFO": {
    "URL": "https://github.com/Withergate/api/blob/fe1c3e2271de75d65533020be31a236bb235ec37/src/main/resources/db/migration/profile/V1_2__Achievements_1.sql?raw=true\n",
    "LICENSE": "APACHE-2.0",
    "PERMISSIVE": true
  },
  "TABLES": {
    "achievement_details": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "identifier": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "DEDICATED",
            "ON_FIRE",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "ARENA_NEWBIE",
            "ARENA_BADASS",
            "ARENA_PHANTOM",
            "BOB_BUILDER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "KEEPER_SECRETS",
            "WEB_LIES",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LOGISTICIAN",
            "NO_WORRY",
            "STEADY",
            "UNWAVERING",
            "HANDY",
            "ALIEXPRESS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "UNBENT",
            "MACKIE",
            "PUSCHKIN",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LUCKY_LOSER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "RIGHT_SIDE",
            "FOLLOW_ME",
            "<PERSON>",
            "WELL_PLAYED",
            "GOOD_JOB",
            "WTF",
            "ON_QUEST",
            "<PERSON>",
            "HERO"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "achievement_type": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "CONSECUTIVE_LOGINS",
            "CONSECUTIVE_LOGINS",
            "PREMIUM",
            "PREMIUM",
            "ARENA_WINS",
            "ARENA_WINS",
            "ARENA_WINS",
            "BUILDING_ALL",
            "BUILDING_DEFENSE",
            "BUILDING_TOP",
            "RESEARCH_COUNT",
            "INFORMATION_LEVEL",
            "INFORMATION_LEVEL",
            "CHARACTER_COUNT",
            "NO_STARVATION",
            "DISASTERS_AVERTED",
            "GAME_COUNT",
            "GAME_COUNT",
            "CRAFT_COUNT",
            "CRAFT_COUNT",
            "ATTACK_SUCCESS_COUNT",
            "DEFENSE_SUCCESS_COUNT",
            "COMBAT_KILL",
            "COMBAT_DEATH",
            "COMBAT_WIN_LUCKY",
            "COMBAT_FLEE_LUCKY",
            "TRADE_PRICE_MAX",
            "MEMBER_OF_TOP_FACTION",
            "TOP_FACTION_MEMBER",
            "GAME_WINNER",
            "GAME_FAME",
            "GAME_FAME",
            "GAME_FAME",
            "QUEST_COUNT",
            "QUEST_COUNT",
            "QUEST_COUNT"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "rarity": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "RARE",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "RARE",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "RARE",
            "RARE",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "RARE",
            "EPIC"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "image_url": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/dedicated.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/on-fire.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/supporter.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/patron.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/arena-newbie.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/arena-badass.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/arena-phantom.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/bob-builder.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/camper.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/brick-wall.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/mastermind.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/keeper-secrets.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/web-lies.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/hordes.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/logistician.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/no-worry.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/steady.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/unwavering.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/handy.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/aliexpress.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/no-sow.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/unbent.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/mackie.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/puschkin.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/lucky-winner.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/lucky-loser.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/dibbler.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/right-side.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/follow-me.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/master.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/well-played.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/good-job.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/wtf.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/on-quest.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/adventurer.png",
            "https://storage.googleapis.com/withergate-images/achievements/hero.png"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "value_number": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            5,
            21,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            7,
            20,
            0,
            4,
            6,
            8,
            5,
            7,
            10,
            0,
            0,
            3,
            8,
            5,
            15,
            10,
            5,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            0,
            1,
            0,
            0,
            200,
            350,
            500,
            1,
            6,
            10
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "value_string": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            null,
            null,
            "SILVER",
            "GOLD",
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null,
            null
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "identifier"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "achievements": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "achievement_id": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "identifier": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "profile_id": {
          "TYPE": "Int",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "award_date": {
          "TYPE": "Timestamp",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "achievement_id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "identifier"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "achievement_details",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "identifier"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    },
    "localized_texts": {
      "COLUMNS": {
        "text_id": {
          "TYPE": "BigInt",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": true,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": true,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "lang": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs",
            "en",
            "cs"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "text": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": false,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "Login to the game 5 days in a row.",
            "Přihlas se do hry 5 dnů v řadě.",
            "Login to the game 21 days in a row.",
            "Přihlas se do hry 21 dnů v řadě.",
            "Get a Silver account. This can be done by contributing to the game development of via Patreon.",
            "Získej Silver účet. Možné získat nefinanční podporou hry a nebo přes Patreon.",
            "Get a Gold account. This can be done via Patreon.",
            "Získej Gold účet. Možné získat přes Patreon.",
            "Win at least one fight in the arena.",
            "Vyhraj alespoň jeden zápas v aréně",
            "Win at least seven fight in the arena with a same character.",
            "Vyhraj alespoň sedm zápasů v aréně se stejnou postavou.",
            "Win at least twenty fights in the arena with a same character.",
            "Vyhraj alespoň dvacet zápasů v aréně se stejnou postavou.",
            "Build at least one level of every building.",
            "Postav alespoň jednu úroveň od každé budovy.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Build at least four levels of a defense building.",
            "Postav svou obrannou budovu alespoň na čtvrtou úroveň.",
            "Build at least six levels of a single building.",
            "Postav alespoň jednu ze svých budov na šestou úroveň.",
            "Complete at least eight research projects during a single game.",
            "Vynalezni alespoň osm výzkumů během jedinného věku.",
            "Reach information level five.",
            "Dosáhni úrovně informací pět.",
            "Reach information level seven.",
            "Dosáhni úrovně informací sedm.",
            "Have at least ten characters in your clan.",
            "Měj alespoň deset postav ve svém klanu.",
            "Your characters did not starve during a single era.",
            "Tvé postavy ani jednou za celý věk nehladověly.",
            "Avert every disaster during a single era.",
            "Úspěšně vyřeš všechny pohromy v jednom věku.",
            "Play at least three games.",
            "Odehraj alespoň tři herní věky.",
            "Play at least eight games.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Craft at least five items.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Craft at least fifteen items.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Perform at least ten successful attacks against other players.",
            "Podnikni alespoň deset úspěšných útoků proti ostatním hráčům.",
            "Successfully defend your clan base against at least five attacks from other players.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Kill another player`s character during combat.",
            "Zabij v souboji postavu jiného hráče.",
            "Lose a character during a combat.",
            "Přijď o postavu během souboje.",
            "Win a combat with one remaining health.",
            "Vyhraj souboj s posledním zbývajícím životem.",
            "Flee from combat with one remaining health.",
            "Uteč ze souboje s poledním zbývajícím životem.",
            "Sell item on marketplace for double its market price.",
            "Prodej předmět na tržišti za dvojnásobek jeho tržní hodnoty.",
            "Be a member of the winning faction with at least one influence point at the end of the game.",
            "Buď členem nejsilnější frakce s alespoň jedním vlivem na konci hry.",
            "Be the most influential clan of your faction at the end of the game..",
            "Buď nejvlivnějším klanem své frakce na konci hry.",
            "Win the whole game era.",
            "<PERSON>",
            "Have at least 200 fame at the end of the game.",
            "Měj na konci věku alespoň 200 slávy.",
            "Have at least 350 fame at the end of the game.",
            "Měj na konci věku alespoň 350 slávy.",
            "Have at least 500 fame at the end of the game.",
            "Měj na konci věku alespoň 500 slávy.",
            "Complete at lest one quest.",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "Complete at lest six quests.",
            "Splň alespoň šest úkolů.",
            "Complete at least ten quests.",
            "<LOCATION>"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "achievement_name": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "DEDICATED",
            "DEDICATED",
            "ON_FIRE",
            "ON_FIRE",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "ARENA_NEWBIE",
            "ARENA_NEWBIE",
            "ARENA_BADASS",
            "ARENA_BADASS",
            "ARENA_PHANTOM",
            "ARENA_PHANTOM",
            "BOB_BUILDER",
            "BOB_BUILDER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "KEEPER_SECRETS",
            "KEEPER_SECRETS",
            "WEB_LIES",
            "WEB_LIES",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LOGISTICIAN",
            "LOGISTICIAN",
            "NO_WORRY",
            "NO_WORRY",
            "STEADY",
            "STEADY",
            "UNWAVERING",
            "UNWAVERING",
            "HANDY",
            "HANDY",
            "ALIEXPRESS",
            "ALIEXPRESS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "UNBENT",
            "UNBENT",
            "MACKIE",
            "MACKIE",
            "PUSCHKIN",
            "PUSCHKIN",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LUCKY_LOSER",
            "LUCKY_LOSER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "RIGHT_SIDE",
            "RIGHT_SIDE",
            "FOLLOW_ME",
            "FOLLOW_ME",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "WELL_PLAYED",
            "WELL_PLAYED",
            "GOOD_JOB",
            "GOOD_JOB",
            "WTF",
            "WTF",
            "ON_QUEST",
            "ON_QUEST",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "HERO",
            "HERO"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        },
        "achievement_description": {
          "TYPE": "Varchar",
          "NULLABLE": null,
          "UNIQUE": null,
          "DEFAULT": null,
          "CHECKS": [],
          "IS_PRIMARY": false,
          "IS_INDEX": false,
          "VALUES": [
            "DEDICATED",
            "DEDICATED",
            "ON_FIRE",
            "ON_FIRE",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "ARENA_NEWBIE",
            "ARENA_NEWBIE",
            "ARENA_BADASS",
            "ARENA_BADASS",
            "ARENA_PHANTOM",
            "ARENA_PHANTOM",
            "BOB_BUILDER",
            "BOB_BUILDER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "<LOCATION>",
            "KEEPER_SECRETS",
            "KEEPER_SECRETS",
            "WEB_LIES",
            "WEB_LIES",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LOGISTICIAN",
            "LOGISTICIAN",
            "NO_WORRY",
            "NO_WORRY",
            "STEADY",
            "STEADY",
            "UNWAVERING",
            "UNWAVERING",
            "HANDY",
            "HANDY",
            "ALIEXPRESS",
            "ALIEXPRESS",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "UNBENT",
            "UNBENT",
            "MACKIE",
            "MACKIE",
            "PUSCHKIN",
            "PUSCHKIN",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "LUCKY_LOSER",
            "LUCKY_LOSER",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "RIGHT_SIDE",
            "RIGHT_SIDE",
            "FOLLOW_ME",
            "FOLLOW_ME",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "WELL_PLAYED",
            "WELL_PLAYED",
            "GOOD_JOB",
            "GOOD_JOB",
            "WTF",
            "WTF",
            "ON_QUEST",
            "ON_QUEST",
            "<PERSON>",
            "<PERSON>",
            "HERO",
            "HERO"
          ],
          "COMMENT": null
        }
      },
      "PRIMARY_KEYS": [
        "text_id"
      ],
      "FOREIGN_KEYS": [
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "achievement_name"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "achievement_details",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "identifier"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        },
        {
          "COLUMNS": [
            "achievement_description"
          ],
          "FOREIGN_TABLE": "achievement_details",
          "REFERRED_COLUMNS": [
            "identifier"
          ],
          "ON_DELETE": null,
          "ON_UPDATE": null
        }
      ],
      "CHECKS": [],
      "INDEXES": [],
      "COMMENT": null
    }
  }
}